<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Bangalore - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mysore Solo Trip plan (2 Days + 1 Night)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</link>
			<description>Two days Ride from&amp;nbsp;Bangalore to Mysore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for two days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Chamundeshwari</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kochi Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Kochi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Kochi and one couple more quick visits in Mysore, Ooty and Coimbatore on the way.  Kochi, called as Queen of the Arabian Sea, is one of the major port cities in the coast of India and also has trading from 14th century</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Srisailam Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Srisailam, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Srisailam and one more Shakti Peethas on the way.  Srisailam is one of the places where people get to visit Lord Mallikarjuna (one of the Jyotirlinga) and Goddess Bhramaramba (one of the Ashtadasa Shakti Peetha) in</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Pondicherry Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-pondicherry-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Pondicherry, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well.  Among the touristers Pondicherry is famous for its rich French essence of architecture of buildings in the White town area. Also it&amp;#39;s famous for beaches and it&amp;#39;s one of the good places for Solo travelers. Let&amp;#3</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 16:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-pondicherry-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Lepakshi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One day trip from Bangalore to Lepakshi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this one day plan works very well.  Lepakshi is a small village located in Anantapur district, Andhra Pradesh. It is around 120 KM from Bangalore. It is famous for Veerabhadra temple, one of the oldest temples in India. The temple has Ganesha, Nandi, Veerabhadra, Shiva, Bhadrak</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Everest Base Camp Trek, Start Trekking from Salleri and back to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of where you can start your trek. I have read through many articles &amp;amp; videos and found the best route for trekking.  Generally people all over the world will reach Kathmandu and then take a flight to Lukla and start the trek to Everest base camp from Lukla.  In case you are n</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, Bangalore to Kathmandu then to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to trek Solo to Everest Base Camp by yourself from Bangalore, then this article will help you to get a picture of how to reach Salleri from Bangalore, where Salleri will be the starting point of Trek to Everest Base Camp.  There are many possible routes to reach Kathmandu from Bangalore.   Flight  There are direct flights from Bangalore to Kathmandu and vice versa. You also hav</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Travel to Gokarna for Three Nights and Four Days</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</link>
			<description>You are planning to visit Gokarna solo then here is the article which will help you to plan your trip. And this plan in this article is for three days and four nights and for a person who wants to travel solo.  If you are traveling from Bangalore, overnight bus or a train will be the best option for travel to Gokarna. And if you wish to travel via flight, the nearest airport for people will be eit</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Makalidurga - Trekking</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</link>
			<description>One-day trek from Bangalore to Makalidurga to Bangalore. If you are a couple riding on a Bike or you are a Family driving in a Car, then this trek plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. Makalidurga is a hill fort situated 60 km north of Bangalore. The fort at the summit has an old temple of Shiva with Nandi and in legend, Markandeya Rishi performed penan</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Gandikota (Two Days and One Night, Trip Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-gandikota-two-days-one-night-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two Days Trip from Bangalore to Gandikota to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on a Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly.
                            A couple of the best places you can visit on the way or around are Lakshmi Narasimha Swamy temple in Kadiri &amp; Belum Caves in Kolimigundla.
  </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-gandikota-two-days-one-night-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tirumala (2 Days + 1 Night)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tirumala-two-days-trip.html</link>
			<description>Two days Trip from Bangalore to Tirumala to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on bike or you are a family driving in car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. You can book the Dharshna Tickets &amp; Stay via Online Booking or you can get it once you reach their based on the Crowd on Tirumala.
                                Tirumala </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tirumala-two-days-trip.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Rameswaram (3 Days + 2 Nights, Trip Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Three days Trip from Bangalore to Rameswaram to Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Rameshwaram is a small Hindu pilgrimage town a</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore -> Murdeshwar -> Gokarna -> Goa -> Dandeli -> Bangalore</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-murdeshwar-gokarna-goa-dandeli.html</link>
			<description>Ten days Ride from Bangalore  Murdeshwar  Gokarna  Goa  Dandeli  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for ten days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.
       </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-murdeshwar-gokarna-goa-dandeli.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>