<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Bangalore - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Bangalore to Talakadu Historical Site – A Couple Motorcycle Ride Travel Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-talakadu-historical-site-a-couple-motorcycle-ride-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Talakadu, on the banks of the river Kaveri, is a fascinating blend of history, mythology, and natural beauty. Once a flourishing city with more than 30 temples, Talakadu is today partly buried under shifting sand dunes, earning it the name &amp;ldquo;The Desert of Karnataka.&amp;rdquo; For a couple riding out of Bangalore on a motorcycle, this trip is the perfect mix of adventure, romance, and heritage. T</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-talakadu-historical-site-a-couple-motorcycle-ride-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kanipakam Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanipakam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Kanipakam, located in Chittoor district of Andhra Pradesh, is a renowned pilgrimage destination famous for the Sri Varasiddhi Vinayaka Temple. Known for its divine atmosphere and spiritual significance, the temple attracts devotees from across South India. A solo trip from Bangalore to Kanipakam is perfect for those seeking peace, devotion, and personal reflection.  Route from Bangalore to Kanipak</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 11:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanipakam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Savandurga Rock Trek – Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-savandurga-rock-trek-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Savandurga, known as one of the largest monolith hills in Asia, is a popular trekking destination located just 60 km from Bangalore. With its rugged trails, panoramic views, and historical ruins, it offers an ideal solo trekking experience for adventure lovers and nature enthusiasts alike. Whether you&amp;#39;re seeking a quick escape or a physical challenge, this guide will help you plan your solo ad</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-savandurga-rock-trek-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mekedatu Gorge Adventure Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mekedatu-gorge-adventure-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Mekedatu, meaning &amp;ldquo;Goat&amp;rsquo;s Leap&amp;rdquo; in Kannada, is a breathtaking gorge where the Cauvery River flows through narrow rock formations. Located about 100 km from Bangalore, it is an excellent destination for a solo adventure, offering stunning landscapes, river views, and an exciting trek. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for an escape into nature, this guide will help you plan a seamless journ</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mekedatu-gorge-adventure-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kanakapura, Kayaking Spot: A Perfect Day Trip Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanakapura-kayaking-spot-a-perfect-day-trip-guide.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re looking for an adventurous escape from Bangalore, Kanakapura is an ideal destination. Located just 55 kilometers from the city, this serene spot offers exciting kayaking experiences amid lush greenery and scenic landscapes.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll go over everything you need to know about making the most out of a day trip from Bangalore to Kanakapura, including the route, itine</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 15:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanakapura-kayaking-spot-a-perfect-day-trip-guide.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Trivandrum Solo Travel Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-trivandrum-solo-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo from Bangalore to Trivandrum offers a wonderful opportunity to explore the cultural richness, natural beauty and vibrant atmosphere of Kerala&amp;#39;s capital city.  Here&amp;#39;s a solo travel plan for your trip:   Day 1: Arrival in Trivandrum   Arrive in Trivandrum by flight, train, or bus. Check into your accommodation and freshen up. Explore local attractions like Padmanabhaswamy Temp</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:27:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-trivandrum-solo-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dandeli Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dandeli-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Dandeli promises an exciting adventure amidst nature, wildlife and thrilling activities.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Day 1: Bangalore to Dandeli   Morning: Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Dandeli is approximately 460 kilometers and the drive tak</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 12:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dandeli-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Sakleshpur Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-sakleshpur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Sakleshpur offers an ideal getaway amidst the serene Western Ghats, lush greenery and pleasant weather.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Sakleshpur   Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to avoid traffic and make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Sakleshpur is approximately 220 kilom</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-sakleshpur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Chikmagalur Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chikmagalur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Chikmagalur promises a perfect blend of natural beauty, serene landscapes and rejuvenating experiences.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Chikmagalur   Start your journey early in the morning to avoid traffic and reach Chikmagalur with ample time. The distance between Bangalore and Chikmagalur is approximately 240 kilometers and the dri</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chikmagalur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kovalam Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kovalam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kovalam offers a perfect blend of relaxation, beach vibes and cultural experiences.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Madurai -&amp;gt; Tirunelveli -&amp;gt; Nagercoil -&amp;gt; Kovalam  Bangalore to Kovalam   Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kovalam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tiruttani Solo Travel Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruttani-solo-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Tiruttani is a significant pilgrimage destination in Tamil Nadu, known for its ancient temple dedicated to Lord Murugan. As a solo traveler, you&amp;#39;ll have the opportunity to immerse yourself in the spiritual ambiance of the temple town, explore its cultural heritage and witness the rituals and traditions firsthand.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested solo travel plan:  Arrival in Tiruttani   Depart from Ban</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 07:39:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruttani-solo-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Jog Falls Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-jog-falls-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Jog Falls can be a refreshing experience, especially for nature lovers. Jog Falls, located in the Shimoga district of Karnataka, is one of the highest plunge waterfalls in India.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Jog Falls   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of the day. The distance between Bangalore and Jog Falls</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 14:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-jog-falls-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kollur Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kollur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kollur can be a serene and spiritually enriching experience, as Kollur is home to the famous Mookambika Temple.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Kollur   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Kollur is approximately 400 kilometers and the drive takes around 8-9 hours. R</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kollur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Anamudi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-anamudi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Anamudi, standing as the highest peak in the Western Ghats and South India, is a wonderful destination for nature lovers and trekkers. It&amp;#39;s situated in the Eravikulam National Park near Munnar, Kerala.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip from Bangalore to Anamudi:  Bangalore to Munnar   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-anamudi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Chitradurga Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chitradurga-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Chitradurga can be a rewarding experience, with Chitradurga being known for its historical fort and scenic landscapes.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Chitradurga   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Chitradurga is approximately 200 kilometers and it takes around 4-</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chitradurga-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Madurai Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-madurai-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Madurai can be a fascinating journey, rich in history, culture and spirituality. Madurai, often referred to as the Athens of the East, is famous for its Meenakshi Amman Temple and vibrant street life.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Madurai   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Ba</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-madurai-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Nagarahole Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-nagarahole-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Nagarahole promises an exciting adventure amidst the wildlife and natural beauty of the national park. Nagarahole, also known as Rajiv Gandhi National Park, is renowned for its diverse flora and fauna.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Nagarahole   Begin your journey early in the morning to allow ample time for exploration. The distance</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 09:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-nagarahole-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kudremukh Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kudremukh-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kudremukh promises an adventurous and nature-filled experience. Kudremukh is known for its scenic beauty, trekking trails and lush green landscapes.  The name&amp;nbsp;Kuduremukha&amp;nbsp;literally means &amp;quot;horse-faced&amp;quot; in&amp;nbsp;Kannada&amp;nbsp;and refers to a particular picturesque view of a side of the mountain that resembles a horse&amp;#39;s face. It was also referred to a</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 07:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kudremukh-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Srikalahasti Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srikalahasti-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Srikalahasti can be a spiritually enriching experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to visit the famous Srikalahasti Temple and explore the cultural heritage of this ancient town in Andhra Pradesh.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Chittoor -&amp;gt; Tirupati -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Srikalahasti -&amp;gt; Tirupati -&amp;gt; Chittoor -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 19:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srikalahasti-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Horanadu Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-horanadu-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Horanadu can be a serene and spiritual experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to visit the famous Horanadu Annapoorneshwari Temple and explore the natural beauty of the Western Ghats in Karnataka.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Belur -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Mudigere -&amp;gt; Kalasa -&amp;gt; Horanadu -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 09:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-horanadu-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Agumbe Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-agumbe-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Agumbe can be a thrilling adventure, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the rainforests, waterfalls and scenic beauty of the Western Ghats in Karnataka. Agumbe is also known as the &amp;quot;Cherrapunji of South India&amp;quot; due to its high rainfall and lush greenery.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Belur -&amp;gt; Sringeri -&amp;gt; A</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-agumbe-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mangalore Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mangalore-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Mangalore can be an exciting journey, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the pristine beaches, ancient temples and vibrant culture of this coastal city in Karnataka.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Belur -&amp;gt; Charmady Ghat -&amp;gt; Mangaluru -&amp;gt; Sakleshpura -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Mangalore   Star</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mangalore-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Udupi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-udupi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Udupi can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the pristine beaches, ancient temples and delicious cuisine of this coastal town in Karnataka.  Udupi is one of the top tourist attractions in Karnataka and has various educational institutions. It is notable for the&amp;nbsp;Krishna Temple&amp;nbsp;and is also known as the temple city.[3]&amp;nbsp;It also lends its</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 20:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-udupi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Bheemeshwari Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-bheemeshwari-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Bheemeshwari can be a peaceful and adventurous experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the serene nature, engage in activities like fishing and river rafting and enjoy the tranquility of this riverside destination in Karnataka. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Ramanagara -&amp;gt; Channapatna -&amp;gt; Halagur -&amp;gt; Channapatna -&amp;gt; Rama</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Aug 2023 07:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-bheemeshwari-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Thekkady Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-thekkady-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Thekkady can be an exciting adventure, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the wildlife, spice plantations and beautiful landscapes of this scenic destination in Kerala.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Dindigul -&amp;gt; Thekkady -&amp;gt; Dindigul -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Thekkady   Start your trip early in </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-thekkady-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Alleppey Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-alleppey-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Alleppey (Alappuzha) can be a memorable experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the backwaters, houseboat cruises and serene beauty of the famous backwater destination in Kerala. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Coimbatore -&amp;gt; Kochi -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Alleppey  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Maddur -&amp;gt; Chamarajanagar -&amp;gt; Coimbatore -&amp;g</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-alleppey-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mahabalipuram Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mahabalipuram-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Mahabalipuram can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the UNESCO World Heritage Site with its ancient temples, rock-cut sculptures and beautiful beach.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Krishnagiri -&amp;gt; Vellore -&amp;gt; Kanchipuram -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Mahabalipuram  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Kolar -&amp;gt; Chittoor -&amp;gt; Kanchipuram -</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mahabalipuram-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Hampi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hampi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Hampi can be a fascinating journey, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the historical ruins, ancient temples and unique rock formations of this UNESCO World Heritage Site. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Chitradurga -&amp;gt; Hampi -&amp;gt; Chitradurga -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Hampi   Start your trip early in the morning from </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 19:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hampi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Varkala Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-varkala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Varkala can be a rejuvenating experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the stunning beaches, cliffs and spiritual charm of this coastal town in Kerala.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Coimbatore -&amp;gt; Trivandrum -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Varkala -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Madurai -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Salem -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Mysore -&amp;</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-varkala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Coorg Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-coorg-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Coorg can be a wonderful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the lush green landscapes, coffee plantations and serene natural beauty of this hill station in Karnataka. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Mysore -&amp;gt; Coorg -&amp;gt; Madikeri -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Mysore -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Coorg   Start your trip early </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-coorg-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kanyakumari Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanyakumari-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kanyakumari can be a fascinating journey, as you&amp;#39;ll get to experience the diverse landscapes, cultural heritage and the meeting point of the Arabian Sea, the Indian Ocean and the Bay of Bengal. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Madurai -&amp;gt; Kanyakumari -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Salem -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Madur</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 16:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanyakumari-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Munnar Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-munnar-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Munnar can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the picturesque tea plantations, misty hills and serene lakes of this charming hill station in Kerala. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey,  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Dindigul -&amp;gt; Munnar -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Salem -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Munnar   Start your trip early in</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-munnar-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kodaikanal Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kodaikanal-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Kodaikanal can be a wonderful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the misty hills, scenic landscapes and serene lakes of this charming hill station.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Dindigul -&amp;gt; Kodaikanal -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Salem -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Kodaikanal   Start your trip early in the mo</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kodaikanal-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Wayanad Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-wayanad-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Wayanad can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the natural beauty and tranquility of this hill station in Kerala. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Mysuru -&amp;gt; Gundlupete -&amp;gt; Wayanad -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Mysuru -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Wayanad   Start your journey early in the morning from Bangal</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-wayanad-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Hyderabad Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hyderabad-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Planning a trip from Bangalore to Hyderabad can be an exciting adventure! One day trip or Two day trip from Bangalore to Hyderabad, If you are&amp;nbsp;Solo&amp;nbsp;riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in Hyderabad.  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Anantapur -&amp;gt; Kurnool -&amp;gt; Hyderabad -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hyderabad-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kukke-subramanya-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Planning a trip from Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya? That&amp;#39;s a great choice! One day trip or Two day trip from Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in Kukke Subramanya.  Kukke Subramanya is a popular pilgrimage destination in Karnataka known for its ancient templ</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kukke-subramanya-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bengaluru to BR Hills and KGudi Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bengaluru-to-br-hills-and-kgudi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One day trip or Two day trip from Bangalore to BR Hills and KGudi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in BR Hills and KGudi.  BR Hills is a Hill range, also a tiger reserve, also a temple of Lord Ranganathaswamy which attracts people to visit BR Hills. Once in two years, the Soliga Tribals pre</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bengaluru-to-br-hills-and-kgudi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Ghati Subramanya Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/short-trip-from-bangalore-to-ghati.html</link>
			<description>One day trip from&amp;nbsp;Bangalore&amp;nbsp;to Ghati Subramanya, If you are&amp;nbsp;Solo&amp;nbsp;riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this plan works very well to cover places in Ghati Subramanya.  Ghati Subramanya&amp;nbsp;is an ancient Hindu temple, 50 kms away from Bangalore towards Doddaballapur situated on the outskirts of Bangalore. Ghati Subramanya has a recorded&amp;nbsp;history of</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 17:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/short-trip-from-bangalore-to-ghati.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mysore Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</link>
			<description>Two days Ride from&amp;nbsp;Bangalore to Mysore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for two days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Chamundeshwari</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kochi Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from&amp;nbsp;Bangalore&amp;nbsp;to Kochi, If you are&amp;nbsp;Solo&amp;nbsp;riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Kochi and one couple more quick visits in Mysore, Ooty and Coimbatore on the way.  Kochi, called as&amp;nbsp;Queen of the Arabian Sea, is one of the major port cities in the coast of India and also has </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Srisailam Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Srisailam, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Srisailam and one more Shakti Peethas on the way.  Srisailam is one of the places where people get to visit Lord Mallikarjuna (one of the Jyotirlinga) and Goddess Bhramaramba (one of the Ashtadasa Shakti Peetha) in</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Pondicherry Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-pondicherry-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Pondicherry, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well.  Among the touristers Pondicherry is famous for its rich French essence of architecture of buildings in the White town area. Also it&amp;#39;s famous for beaches and it&amp;#39;s one of the good places for Solo travelers. Let&amp;#3</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 16:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-pondicherry-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Lepakshi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One day trip from Bangalore to Lepakshi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this one day plan works very well.  Lepakshi is a small village located in Anantapur district, Andhra Pradesh. It is around 120 KM from Bangalore. It is famous for Veerabhadra temple, one of the oldest temples in India. The temple has Ganesha, Nandi, Veerabhadra, Shiva, Bhadrak</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Everest Base Camp Trek, Start Trekking from Salleri and back to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of where you can start your trek. I have read through many articles &amp;amp; videos and found the best route for trekking.  Generally people all over the world will reach Kathmandu and then take a flight to Lukla and start the trek to Everest base camp from Lukla.  In case you are n</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, Bangalore to Kathmandu then to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to trek Solo to Everest Base Camp by yourself from Bangalore, then this article will help you to get a picture of how to reach Salleri from Bangalore, where Salleri will be the starting point of Trek to Everest Base Camp.  There are many possible routes to reach Kathmandu from Bangalore.   Flight  There are direct flights from Bangalore to Kathmandu and vice versa. You also hav</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Gokarna Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</link>
			<description>You are planning to visit Gokarna solo then here is the article which will help you to plan your trip. And this plan in this article is for three days and four nights and for a person who wants to travel solo.  If you are traveling from Bangalore, overnight bus or a train will be the best option for travel to Gokarna. And if you wish to travel via flight, the nearest airport for people will be eit</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Makalidurga - Trekking</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</link>
			<description>One-day trek from Bangalore to Makalidurga to Bangalore. If you are a couple riding on a Bike or you are a Family driving in a Car, then this trek plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. Makalidurga is a hill fort situated 60 km north of Bangalore. The fort at the summit has an old temple of Shiva with Nandi and in legend, Markandeya Rishi performed penan</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Gandikota Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-gandikota-two-days-one-night-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two Days Trip from Bangalore to Gandikota to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on a Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly.                            A couple of the best places you can visit on the way or around are Lakshmi Narasimha Swamy temple in Kadiri &amp; Belum Caves in Kolimigundla.    </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-gandikota-two-days-one-night-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tirumala Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tirumala-two-days-trip.html</link>
			<description>Two days Trip from Bangalore to Tirumala to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on bike or you are a family driving in car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. You can book the Dharshna Tickets &amp; Stay via Online Booking or you can get it once you reach their based on the Crowd on Tirumala.                                Tirumala i</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tirumala-two-days-trip.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>