<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Book - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/book.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to make your content more Accessible with plain language</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-your-content-more-accessible-with-plain-language.html</link>
			<description>Making your content more accessible with plain language is a valuable practice that ensures your information is easily understood by a wide range of readers. Here are some tips to make your content more accessible and reader-friendly:   Use Clear and Simple Language: Use plain, straightforward language that is easy to understand. Avoid jargon, technical terms and overly complex vocabulary. Write i</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-your-content-more-accessible-with-plain-language.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Things to know about Proofreading</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-about-proofreading.html</link>
			<description>Proofreading is the process of looking for and correcting errors in your work i.e. finding and correcting spelling, grammar, punctuation, consistency and errors.                            Proofreading is the last step in your writing and editing process.                            You should have written and edited your work for general coherence and flow before proofreading.                     </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-about-proofreading.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Benefits of Reading - Why You Should Read?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/benefits-of-reading-why-you-should-read.html</link>
			<description>By the way, when was the last time you read a book, or read an article on internet? Or you generally tend to look across tweets, facebook updates etc. If you are one of them who is not having an habit of reading regularly, you are missing out few things. Actually reading has few benefits and i'm gona share few of the benefits of reading, so that you start reading!                                Me</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/benefits-of-reading-why-you-should-read.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Reading a book, it's not my thing; is it your instant reply?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reading-a-book-its-not-my-thing-is-it-your-instant-reply.html</link>
			<description>Reading a book expands your thinking dimensions and gives a better perspective about things going on around you. If you agree with what you read just now, Let's have a look at two books which make significant changes to one's life.                                Life is what you make it by Preeti Shenoy                                This is a wonderful fictional story and it revolves around the p</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reading-a-book-its-not-my-thing-is-it-your-instant-reply.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>