<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Business - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/business.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>What is a Customer Data Platform and which one is best for your Business?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-a-customer-data-platform-and-which-one-is-best-for-your-business.html</link>
			<description>Customer Data Platform (CDP) is a sophisticated software system that aggregates and manages customer data across various touchpoints and channels. Its primary purpose is to create a unified and comprehensive view of individual customers or segments of customers. This centralized data is then made accessible to other systems and tools for marketing, analytics and customer engagement.  Key features </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-a-customer-data-platform-and-which-one-is-best-for-your-business.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Drupal Paragraphs?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</link>
			<description>Paragraphs can be used as a way for Content Creation in Drupal. It actually allows the site builders to do their stuff a bit cleanly and for the end users this will be pretty easy to manage the content, meaning people get more control on the Editing side.  Paragraphs is one of the&amp;nbsp; popular modules in Drupal, for handling content. It is more or less very similar to the fields and will provide </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Migrate your site from Drupal 7 To Drupal 9?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate-your-site-from-drupal-seven-to-drupal-nine.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see what are the important things you need to understand for the migration of your Drupal 7 site to the Drupal 9 site. And if you see from your Business perspective, Drupal 7 was launched nine years ago and this is the perfect time for some reassessment of the needs of site users &amp; content managers. And if you see from Drupal’s end, Initially, Drupal 7 end of lif</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate-your-site-from-drupal-seven-to-drupal-nine.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>