<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Chikmagalur - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/chikmagalur.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Ten best hill stations to Travel Solo in South India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in South India offers a unique blend of tranquility, adventure and scenic beauty.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in South India for solo travelers:   Munnar, Kerala   Known for its tea gardens, rolling hills and pleasant weather, Munnar is a great destination for solo travelers. The serene environment and numerous trekking trails make it ideal for exploring</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 08:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Chikmagalur Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chikmagalur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Chikmagalur promises a perfect blend of natural beauty, serene landscapes and rejuvenating experiences.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Chikmagalur   Start your journey early in the morning to avoid traffic and reach Chikmagalur with ample time. The distance between Bangalore and Chikmagalur is approximately 240 kilometers and the dri</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chikmagalur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in Karnataka to travel solo in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-karnataka-to-travel-solo-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo in Karnataka during hot summers can be a delightful experience, especially when you explore destinations with cooler climates or indoor attractions. Karnataka offers a diverse range of destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers.  Here are some of the best places to visit in Karnataka during the hot summer months:   Coorg (Kodagu):   Known as the &amp;quot;Scotland of</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-karnataka-to-travel-solo-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>