<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Children - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/children.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Abhaya Kshethram: A Shelter of Hope and Dignity</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/abhaya-kshethram-a-shelter-of-hope-and-dignity.html</link>
			<description>Nestled near Renigunta Road in Tirupati, Andhra Pradesh, Abhaya Kshethram is a charitable home dedicated to providing care, dignity, and hope to those society often overlooks: physically and mentally challenged orphans, destitute women, and the elderly. (Abhaya Kshethram)  Founding &amp;amp; Vision  Founded in 2007, Abhaya Kshethram was launched on the occasion of Mother Teresa&amp;rsquo;s birthday, symbo</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Oct 2025 17:18:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/abhaya-kshethram-a-shelter-of-hope-and-dignity.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ant Farm Observation, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ant-farm-observation-discovering-the-secret-life-of-ants.html</link>
			<description>Have you ever wondered what ants do underground, where we cannot see them? By making a simple DIY ant farm, you can peek into their busy little world and learn how they live, work, and build amazing colonies. This experiment is not only fun but also teaches us about teamwork, survival, and nature&amp;rsquo;s tiny engineers.  Materials You Will Need   A clear glass jar or plastic container Clean sand o</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ant-farm-observation-discovering-the-secret-life-of-ants.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Nature Scavenger Hunt, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/nature-scavenger-hunt-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>A nature scavenger hunt is a delightful and educational science experiment that encourages children to explore the outdoors while learning about their natural environment. This activity combines adventure with observation, helping children develop their understanding of nature, enhance their observational skills and foster a sense of curiosity. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to organizing a nat</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/nature-scavenger-hunt-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rain Gauge, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rain-gauge-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a DIY rain gauge is a fantastic science experiment for children to understand meteorology and hydrology. A rain gauge measures the amount of precipitation that falls over a period of time. This simple project allows children to observe and record rainfall, helping them learn about weather patterns and data collection. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to making a basic rain gauge.  Materi</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rain-gauge-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Shadow Tracing, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/shadow-tracing-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Shadow tracing is an excellent way for children to explore concepts related to the Earth&amp;#39;s rotation, the position of the sun and how these factors affect shadow length and direction. This simple science experiment demonstrates how the position of the sun in the sky changes throughout the day and how this affects the shadows cast by objects. Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed guide on how to conduct this </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/shadow-tracing-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Geodesic Dome, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-geodesic-dome-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a geodesic dome is an exciting and educational science experiment that helps children understand geometric principles, engineering concepts and structural design. A geodesic dome is a spherical structure composed of interconnected triangles, which provides a strong and stable framework.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide for creating a DIY geodesic dome using paper or straws.  Materials N</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-geodesic-dome-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pi Day Celebration, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pi-day-celebration-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Pi Day, celebrated on March 14th (3/14, reflecting the first three digits of pi, 3.14), is a perfect opportunity to engage children in learning about the mathematical constant pi (&amp;pi;). This activity involves measuring the circumference and diameter of circles to understand how pi relates to these measurements.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a fun and educational science experiment to celebrate Pi Day and explore</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 08:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pi-day-celebration-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tesselation Art, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tesselation-art-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Tessellation art is a wonderful way for children to explore geometry and symmetry through creative expression. Tessellations involve creating patterns that cover a surface without any gaps or overlaps using geometric shapes. This activity helps children understand concepts such as shape, symmetry and repetition in a fun and engaging way.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to creating tessellation </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 08:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tesselation-art-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Math Board Games, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-math-board-games-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating and playing math-based board games is a fantastic way for children to learn math concepts while having fun. These DIY games can be tailored to various age groups and skill levels, making math practice engaging and interactive.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to designing and playing your own math board games.  Materials Needed:   Cardboard or Poster Board: For the game board. Markers o</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-math-board-games-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Origami Geometry, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/origami-geometry-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Origami is a fantastic way to explore and understand geometric concepts through hands-on activity. By folding paper to create different shapes and structures, children can visualize and learn about various geometric principles.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed article to a &amp;quot;Origami Geometry&amp;quot; science experiment for children, focusing on basic geometric shapes and concepts.  Materials Needed:   Or</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/origami-geometry-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Wind Vane, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/wind-vane-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple wind vane is a fun and educational science experiment for children that helps them understand wind direction and meteorological concepts. A wind vane, or weather vane, indicates the direction from which the wind is blowing.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to building a basic wind vane using common materials:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Straw or Wooden Dowel: For the central a</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 12:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/wind-vane-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Barometer, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/barometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a homemade barometer is a great science experiment for children to understand how atmospheric pressure is measured and how it changes with weather conditions. A barometer measures air pressure, which can indicate weather changes such as approaching storms or fair weather.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple guide to building a basic barometer using easily available materials:  Materials Needed:   Glas</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 09:51:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/barometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mini Wind Turbine, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mini-wind-turbine-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a mini wind turbine is a great science experiment for children that demonstrates the principles of wind energy and how it can be converted into electricity.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to creating a simple mini wind turbine using easily available materials:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Bottle: For the turbine&amp;#39;s body. Cardboard or Plastic Sheets: For the turbine blades. Wooden D</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 20:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mini-wind-turbine-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Hydropower Experiment, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hydropower-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple water wheel is an excellent hands-on experiment to understand the principles of hydropower. A waterwheel converts the kinetic energy of flowing water into mechanical energy, which can then be used to perform work or generate electricity.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to building a basic waterwheel to explore the fundamentals of hydropower:  Materials Needed:   Plastic or Cardb</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 20:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hydropower-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Potato Battery, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-potato-battery-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a DIY potato battery is a fascinating and educational experiment that demonstrates the basics of electrochemical cells and how chemical energy can be converted into electrical energy.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to building a potato battery using zinc and copper electrodes:  Materials Needed:   Potatoes: 2-3 medium-sized potatoes (or more if you want to create a battery with higher v</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-potato-battery-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solar Still Experiment, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-still-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Solar still is a simple yet effective device for purifying water using solar energy. It works on the principle of evaporation and condensation to separate clean water from impurities.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to conducting a solar still experiment to demonstrate the process of water purification:  Materials Needed:   Clear Plastic Sheet: To cover the solar still and capture the evaporated </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 20:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-still-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Borax Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/borax-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating Borax slime is a classic and fun science experiment that helps children understand the properties of polymers and cross-linking.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to making Borax slime:  Materials:   White school glue (PVA glue) Borax powder (sodium borate) Water Food coloring (optional) Mixing bowls Measuring cups and spoons Mixing spoon or spatula    Google Ad 1   Procedure:   Prepare th</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/borax-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Magnetic Slime, science experiment for childrens</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-childrens.html</link>
			<description>Creating magnetic slime is an exciting and educational science experiment that combines chemistry and physics to demonstrate magnetism and polymer properties.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how to make magnetic slime step-by-step:  Materials:   White school glue (PVA glue) Liquid starch Iron oxide powder (can be found online or at some craft stores) Water Strong neodymium magnets Mixing bowl Mixing spoon or spatul</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-childrens.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Fluffy Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fluffy-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating fluffy slime is a fun and educational science experiment that engages children with hands-on learning about chemistry and the properties of materials.  Here&amp;#39;s how to make fluffy slime step-by-step:  Materials:   White school glue (PVA glue) Shaving cream (foam, not gel) Baking soda Contact lens solution (containing boric acid and sodium borate) Food coloring (optional) Mixing bowl Mix</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fluffy-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Edible Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/edible-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating edible slime is a fun and safe science experiment for children, combining sensory play with a touch of culinary creativity.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to making edible slime using simple ingredients:  Materials:   Marshmallows (large or mini) Cornstarch Vegetable oil Food coloring (optional) Microwave-safe bowl Mixing spoons    Google Ad 1   Procedure:   Melt the Marshmallows:  Plac</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 11:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/edible-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rainbow Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainbow-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating rainbow slime is a fun and colorful science experiment that helps children learn about chemistry, specifically the concepts of polymers and non-Newtonian fluids.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Clear school glue (PVA glue) Liquid starch Food coloring (red, orange, yellow, green, blue, purple) Small mixing bowls (one for each color) Mixing spoons Measuring cups and spoons  </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainbow-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Salt Crystal Garden, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/salt-crystal-garden-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a salt crystal garden is a fascinating and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about solubility, saturation and crystallization.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Wide-mouthed glass or plastic container (such as a jar or bowl) String, yarn, or pipe cleaners Scissors Salt (Epsom salt or table salt) Water Food coloring (op</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/salt-crystal-garden-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Borax Crystal Snowflakes, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/borax-crystal-snowflakes-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating Borax crystal snowflakes is a captivating and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about solubility, saturation and crystallization. Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Borax powder (available in the laundry aisle of most supermarkets) Pipe cleaners (white or blue works well for snowflakes) String or yarn Pencil or stick Sci</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/borax-crystal-snowflakes-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Alum Crystal Geodes, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/alum-crystal-geodes-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating alum crystal geodes is a captivating and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about solubility, saturation and crystallization.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Alum powder (aluminum potassium sulfate) Eggshells or small hollow egg-shaped molds Water Food coloring (optional) String or fishing line Scissors Stirring spoon</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/alum-crystal-geodes-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rock Candy Crystal Sticks, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rock-candy-crystal-sticks-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating rock candy crystal sticks is a fun and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about solubility and saturation.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Granulated sugar Water Glass or plastic jars or cups Wooden skewers or bamboo sticks Clothespins Food coloring (optional) Flavor extracts (optional) Saucepan Stirring spoon Scissor</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rock-candy-crystal-sticks-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Epsom Salt Crystal Shapes, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/epsom-salt-crystal-shapes-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating Epsom salt crystal shapes is a captivating and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about crystal structures.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Epsom salt (magnesium sulfate) Water Heat source (stove or microwave) Glass or plastic containers (jars, bowls, or cups) String or pipe cleaners Pencil or stick Food coloring (opt</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/epsom-salt-crystal-shapes-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Balloon and Bottle Experiment, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-and-bottle-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The balloon and bottle experiment is a simple yet effective way to demonstrate the effects of air pressure.  Here&amp;#39;s how to conduct the experiment:  Materials Needed:   Empty plastic bottle with a narrow neck (such as a soda bottle) Balloon Scissors Tape (optional)    Google Ad 1   Instructions:   Start by removing the cap from the plastic bottle. If the bottle has any labels or stickers on it,</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-and-bottle-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Crushing Can Experiment, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/crushing-can-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The crushing can experiment is a fascinating demonstration of air pressure in action.  Here&amp;#39;s how to conduct the experiment:  Materials Needed:   Empty aluminum soda can Heat-resistant tongs or a pair of pliers Stovetop or hot plate Bowl or container of cold water Safety goggles (optional but recommended)    Google Ad 1   Instructions:    Prepare the Can:   Begin by rinsing out the empty alumi</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/crushing-can-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cartesian Diver, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cartesian-diver-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a Cartesian diver is a simple and fun science experiment that allows children to explore the concepts of buoyancy and pressure.  Here&amp;#39;s how to make one:  Materials Needed:   Clear plastic bottle with a screw-on cap Small plastic eye dropper or pipette Water Optional: Food coloring    Google Ad 1   Instructions:   Fill the plastic bottle with water almost to the top. Leave a small air </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cartesian-diver-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ping Pong Ball Hovercraft, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ping-pong-ball-hovercraft-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a ping pong ball hovercraft is a fun and educational science experiment that children can enjoy while learning about the principles of air pressure and friction.  Here&amp;#39;s how to make a simple ping pong ball hovercraft:  Materials Needed:   A sturdy, smooth-surfaced CD or DVD A large balloon (preferably round) A hot glue gun and glue sticks A bottle cap (with a flat bottom) A ping pong </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:03:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ping-pong-ball-hovercraft-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a water fountain using air pressure, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-water-fountain-using-air-pressure-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a water fountain using air pressure can be an engaging and educational project.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple way to make a small-scale water fountain using air pressure:  Materials Needed:   Plastic bottle Drinking straw Hot glue gun and glue sticks Scissors Tape Water Optional: Food coloring (for colored water)    Google Ad 1   Instructions:   Prepare the Bottle:   Take a plastic bottle and remo</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-water-fountain-using-air-pressure-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Build a Worm Farm, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-a-worm-farm-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a worm farm is a fantastic way to teach children about ecology, decomposition and the importance of worms in soil health.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide to creating a worm farm:  Materials:   Large, clear plastic container with a lid Small container for drainage (with holes) Soil Sand Vegetable scraps (fruit and vegetable peels, coffee grounds, etc.) Red wiggler worms (available at garden cen</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-a-worm-farm-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Gummy Bear Osmosis, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gummy-bear-osmosis-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The Gummy Bear Osmosis experiment is a simple and engaging way to demonstrate the concept of osmosis, which is the movement of water across a selectively permeable membrane.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Gummy bears (different colors if possible) Water Salt Clear cups or containers Tablespoon Timer or clock Paper and pen for recording observations      (adsbygoogle = window.adsby</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 19:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gummy-bear-osmosis-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg in a Bottle, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The Egg in a Bottle experiment is a classic demonstration of the principles of air pressure.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide for conducting this experiment:  Materials:   Hard-boiled egg (peeled) Glass bottle with a narrow neck (a milk bottle works well) Sheet of paper Matches or lighter   Procedure:   Peel the hard-boiled egg so that it easily fits through the neck of the bottle. Ensure that the bottl</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leaf Chromatography, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-chromatography-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Leaf chromatography is a simple and fascinating experiment that introduces children to the concept of chromatography, which separates different pigments in leaves.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Fresh green leaves (different types if possible) Coffee filters or chromatography paper Pencil Small glasses or jars Rubbing alcohol or isopropyl alcohol Water Tape Small weights or paperc</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-chromatography-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Seed Germination science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/seed-germination-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Germination experiment is a wonderful way to teach children about plant life cycles and the process of seed germination.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple experiment that can be done at home:  Materials:   Seeds (e.g., bean seeds, sunflower seeds, or radish seeds) Small containers or pots Potting soil Water Plastic wrap or a clear plastic bag Labels or markers for labeling      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogl</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/seed-germination-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Simple Circuits, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/simple-circuits-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple circuit is an excellent way to introduce children to the basics of electricity and electronics.  Here&amp;#39;s a straightforward experiment for making a simple circuit:  Materials:   AA batteries (1 or 2, depending on the circuit) Battery holder LED (Light Emitting Diode) Copper tape or aluminum foil Cardboard or paper Insulating tape or masking tape      (adsbygoogle = window.adsby</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/simple-circuits-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Magnetic Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating magnetic slime is a fun and educational science experiment that combines elements of chemistry and physics.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide for making magnetic slime:  Materials:   White school glue (like Elmer&amp;#39;s glue) Liquid starch Iron oxide powder (magnetic powder) Disposable mixing bowl Stirring stick or spoon Strong neodymium magnets (optional, for interactive play) Ziplock bag or air</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Pulley System, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-it-yourself-pulley-system-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple DIY pulley system is a great way to introduce children to basic physics concepts like force and mechanical advantage.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can conduct a pulley system science experiment for children:  Materials:   Two sturdy hooks or fixed points (e.g., a door frame, tree branches, or any secure anchor points) String or rope Small bucket or container Objects with varying weights (</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-it-yourself-pulley-system-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Balloon Rocket science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The balloon rocket experiment is a simple and exciting way to explore the principles of action and reaction, or Newton&amp;#39;s Third Law of Motion.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can conduct the balloon rocket science experiment for children:  Materials:   Balloon String or thread (about 10-15 feet) Drinking straw Tape Scissors      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    Procedure:   Prepare the</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 11:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a volcanic eruption with baking soda and vinegar</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-volcanic-eruption-with-baking-soda-and-vinegar.html</link>
			<description>Creating a volcanic eruption with baking soda and vinegar is a classic and safe science experiment that demonstrates the reaction between an acid (vinegar) and a base (baking soda) to produce carbon dioxide gas.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Baking soda Vinegar Dish soap (optional) Red food coloring (optional) Container or plastic bottle Modeling clay or playdough Tray or </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 12:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-volcanic-eruption-with-baking-soda-and-vinegar.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Color cabbage, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-cabbage-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Colorful Cabbage - Exploring pH Indicators Experiment  Objective: To use red cabbage as a natural pH indicator and observe color changes in different solutions.  Materials:   Red cabbage Blender or knife and cutting board Water Small bowls or containers Various household liquids to test (e.g., lemon juice, vinegar, baking soda solution, soapy water, milk, orange juice) Optional: Pipettes or</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 08:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-cabbage-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tornado in bottle, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tornado-in-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Tornado in a Bottle - Exploring Vortex Formation Experiment  Objective: To create a vortex or &amp;quot;tornado&amp;quot; effect in a bottle and explore the concept of fluid dynamics.  Materials:   Clear plastic bottle with a tight-fitting cap (e.g., 2-liter soda bottle) Water Dishwashing liquid or liquid soap Glitter or small pieces of paper (optional for visual effect) Optional: Food coloring   P</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 08:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tornado-in-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Can you have a good life without kids?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/can-you-have-a-good-life-without-kids.html</link>
			<description>Absolutely, you can have a very fulfilling and happy life without having children. The idea that having children is a requirement for a good life is a societal norm, but it&amp;#39;s important to remember that happiness and fulfillment are deeply personal and can be achieved through a variety of paths.  Here are some reasons why you can have a good life without kids:   Personal Freedom: Not having chi</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/can-you-have-a-good-life-without-kids.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Sundial, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sundial-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Sundial - Exploring Time and Shadows Experiment  Objective: To construct a sundial and explore the concept of using shadows to measure time.  Materials:   Paper plate or circular cardboard Pencil or pen Ruler Small stick or dowel Compass (or any circular object for tracing) Clock or watch Sunny outdoor location   Procedure:   Begin by discussing the concept of a sundial with the children. E</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sundial-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lava lamp, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lava-lamp-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Homemade Lava Lamp - Exploring Density and Immiscible Liquids Experiment  Objective: To create a homemade lava lamp and explore the concepts of density and immiscible liquids.  Materials:   Clear plastic bottle or glass container Water Vegetable oil Food coloring Alka-Seltzer tablet or effervescent antacid tablet Flashlight or small LED light (optional for illuminating the lava lamp)   Proc</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lava-lamp-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Self inflating balloon, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/self-inflating-balloon-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Self-Inflating Balloon - Investigating Gas Generation Experiment  Objective: To create a self-inflating balloon using a simple chemical reaction and explore the concept of gas generation.  Materials:   Small empty plastic water or soda bottle Balloon Baking soda (sodium bicarbonate) Vinegar Funnel Optional: Safety goggles (recommended during the experiment)   Procedure:   Begin by discussin</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 13:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/self-inflating-balloon-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Instant hot ice, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/instant-hot-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>To create a fascinating instant hot ice reaction and explore the concept of exothermic reactions.  Materials:   Sodium acetate trihydrate (available online or in some specialty stores) Heat-resistant container or beaker Spoon or stirring rod Hot plate or stove Optional: Food coloring for visual effect Optional: Safety goggles and gloves (recommended when handling chemicals)   Procedure:   Begin by</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/instant-hot-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pencils through a bag of water, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pencils-through-a-bag-of-water-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Pencils Through a Bag of Water - Investigating Properties of Polymers Experiment  Objective: To demonstrate the unique properties of polymers and the concept of surface tension through the &amp;quot;pencils through a bag of water&amp;quot; experiment.  Materials:   Ziplock bag (gallon size or larger) Water Pencils (unsharpened) Optional: Food coloring   Procedure:   Begin by discussing the concept </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pencils-through-a-bag-of-water-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Things that a teacher should tell their students?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-that-a-teacher-should-tell-their-students.html</link>
			<description>Teachers play a vital role in shaping the lives of their students. Here are ten important things that teachers should convey to their students:   You are capable: Encourage students to believe in their abilities and potential. Remind them that with effort, perseverance and a growth mindset, they can achieve great things. Mistakes are part of learning: Teach students that making mistakes is a natur</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-that-a-teacher-should-tell-their-students.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>