<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Children - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/children.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Build a Worm Farm, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-a-worm-farm-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a worm farm is a fantastic way to teach children about ecology, decomposition, and the importance of worms in soil health.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide to creating a worm farm:  Materials:   Large, clear plastic container with a lid Small container for drainage (with holes) Soil Sand Vegetable scraps (fruit and vegetable peels, coffee grounds, etc.) Red wiggler worms (available at garden ce</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-a-worm-farm-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Gummy Bear Osmosis, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gummy-bear-osmosis-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The Gummy Bear Osmosis experiment is a simple and engaging way to demonstrate the concept of osmosis, which is the movement of water across a selectively permeable membrane.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Gummy bears (different colors if possible) Water Salt Clear cups or containers Tablespoon Timer or clock Paper and pen for recording observations      (adsbygoogle = window.adsby</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 19:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gummy-bear-osmosis-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg in a Bottle, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The Egg in a Bottle experiment is a classic demonstration of the principles of air pressure.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide for conducting this experiment:  Materials:   Hard-boiled egg (peeled) Glass bottle with a narrow neck (a milk bottle works well) Sheet of paper Matches or lighter      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    Procedure:   Peel the hard-boiled egg so that it easily f</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 18:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leaf Chromatography, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-chromatography-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Leaf chromatography is a simple and fascinating experiment that introduces children to the concept of chromatography, which separates different pigments in leaves.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Fresh green leaves (different types if possible) Coffee filters or chromatography paper Pencil Small glasses or jars Rubbing alcohol or isopropyl alcohol Water Tape Small weights or paperc</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-chromatography-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Seed Germination science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/seed-germination-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Germination experiment is a wonderful way to teach children about plant life cycles and the process of seed germination.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple experiment that can be done at home:  Materials:   Seeds (e.g., bean seeds, sunflower seeds, or radish seeds) Small containers or pots Potting soil Water Plastic wrap or a clear plastic bag Labels or markers for labeling      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogl</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/seed-germination-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Simple Circuits, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/simple-circuits-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple circuit is an excellent way to introduce children to the basics of electricity and electronics.  Here&amp;#39;s a straightforward experiment for making a simple circuit:  Materials:   AA batteries (1 or 2, depending on the circuit) Battery holder LED (Light Emitting Diode) Copper tape or aluminum foil Cardboard or paper Insulating tape or masking tape      (adsbygoogle = window.adsby</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/simple-circuits-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Magnetic Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating magnetic slime is a fun and educational science experiment that combines elements of chemistry and physics.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide for making magnetic slime:  Materials:   White school glue (like Elmer&amp;#39;s glue) Liquid starch Iron oxide powder (magnetic powder) Disposable mixing bowl Stirring stick or spoon Strong neodymium magnets (optional, for interactive play) Ziplock bag or air</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Pulley System, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-it-yourself-pulley-system-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple DIY pulley system is a great way to introduce children to basic physics concepts like force and mechanical advantage.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can conduct a pulley system science experiment for children:  Materials:   Two sturdy hooks or fixed points (e.g., a door frame, tree branches, or any secure anchor points) String or rope Small bucket or container Objects with varying weights (</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-it-yourself-pulley-system-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Balloon Rocket science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The balloon rocket experiment is a simple and exciting way to explore the principles of action and reaction, or Newton&amp;#39;s Third Law of Motion.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can conduct the balloon rocket science experiment for children:  Materials:   Balloon String or thread (about 10-15 feet) Drinking straw Tape Scissors      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    Procedure:   Prepare the</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 11:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a volcanic eruption with baking soda and vinegar</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-volcanic-eruption-with-baking-soda-and-vinegar.html</link>
			<description>Creating a volcanic eruption with baking soda and vinegar is a classic and safe science experiment that demonstrates the reaction between an acid (vinegar) and a base (baking soda) to produce carbon dioxide gas.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Baking soda Vinegar Dish soap (optional) Red food coloring (optional) Container or plastic bottle Modeling clay or playdough Tray or </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 12:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-volcanic-eruption-with-baking-soda-and-vinegar.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Color cabbage, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-cabbage-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Colorful Cabbage - Exploring pH Indicators Experiment  Objective: To use red cabbage as a natural pH indicator and observe color changes in different solutions.  Materials:   Red cabbage Blender or knife and cutting board Water Small bowls or containers Various household liquids to test (e.g., lemon juice, vinegar, baking soda solution, soapy water, milk, orange juice) Optional: Pipettes or</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Sep 2023 08:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-cabbage-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tornado in bottle, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tornado-in-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Tornado in a Bottle - Exploring Vortex Formation Experiment  Objective: To create a vortex or &amp;quot;tornado&amp;quot; effect in a bottle and explore the concept of fluid dynamics.  Materials:   Clear plastic bottle with a tight-fitting cap (e.g., 2-liter soda bottle) Water Dishwashing liquid or liquid soap Glitter or small pieces of paper (optional for visual effect) Optional: Food coloring   P</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Aug 2023 08:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tornado-in-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Can you have a good life without kids?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/can-you-have-a-good-life-without-kids.html</link>
			<description>Absolutely, you can have a very fulfilling and happy life without having children. The idea that having children is a requirement for a good life is a societal norm, but it&amp;#39;s important to remember that happiness and fulfillment are deeply personal and can be achieved through a variety of paths.  Here are some reasons why you can have a good life without kids:   Personal Freedom: Not having chi</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/can-you-have-a-good-life-without-kids.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Sundial, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sundial-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Sundial - Exploring Time and Shadows Experiment  Objective: To construct a sundial and explore the concept of using shadows to measure time.  Materials:   Paper plate or circular cardboard Pencil or pen Ruler Small stick or dowel Compass (or any circular object for tracing) Clock or watch Sunny outdoor location   Procedure:   Begin by discussing the concept of a sundial with the children. E</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 10:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sundial-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lava lamp, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lava-lamp-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Homemade Lava Lamp - Exploring Density and Immiscible Liquids Experiment  Objective: To create a homemade lava lamp and explore the concepts of density and immiscible liquids.  Materials:   Clear plastic bottle or glass container Water Vegetable oil Food coloring Alka-Seltzer tablet or effervescent antacid tablet Flashlight or small LED light (optional for illuminating the lava lamp)   Proc</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Aug 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lava-lamp-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Self inflating balloon, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/self-inflating-balloon-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Self-Inflating Balloon - Investigating Gas Generation Experiment  Objective: To create a self-inflating balloon using a simple chemical reaction and explore the concept of gas generation.  Materials:   Small empty plastic water or soda bottle Balloon Baking soda (sodium bicarbonate) Vinegar Funnel Optional: Safety goggles (recommended during the experiment)   Procedure:   Begin by discussin</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 19 Aug 2023 13:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/self-inflating-balloon-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Instant hot ice, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/instant-hot-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Instant Hot Ice - Exploring Exothermic Reactions Experiment  Objective: To create a fascinating instant hot ice reaction and explore the concept of exothermic reactions.  Materials:   Sodium acetate trihydrate (available online or in some specialty stores) Heat-resistant container or beaker Spoon or stirring rod Hot plate or stove Optional: Food coloring for visual effect Optional: Safety g</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 19:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/instant-hot-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pencils through a bag of water, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pencils-through-a-bag-of-water-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Pencils Through a Bag of Water - Investigating Properties of Polymers Experiment  Objective: To demonstrate the unique properties of polymers and the concept of surface tension through the &amp;quot;pencils through a bag of water&amp;quot; experiment.  Materials:   Ziplock bag (gallon size or larger) Water Pencils (unsharpened) Optional: Food coloring   Procedure:   Begin by discussing the concept </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pencils-through-a-bag-of-water-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Things that a teacher should tell their students?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-that-a-teacher-should-tell-their-students.html</link>
			<description>Teachers play a vital role in shaping the lives of their students. Here are ten important things that teachers should convey to their students:   You are capable: Encourage students to believe in their abilities and potential. Remind them that with effort, perseverance, and a growth mindset, they can achieve great things. Mistakes are part of learning: Teach students that making mistakes is a natu</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 08:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-that-a-teacher-should-tell-their-students.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solar oven, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-oven-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Solar Oven - Harnessing Solar Energy Experiment  Objective: To construct and use a solar oven to demonstrate the conversion of solar energy into heat energy.  Materials:   Cardboard box (preferably with a lid) Aluminum foil Plastic wrap or oven-safe glass Black construction paper Scissors Tape Pencil or marker Ruler Thermometer Food items for heating (e.g., marshmallows, chocolate) Optional</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-oven-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Grow crystals, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-crystals-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Grow Your Own Crystals - Exploring Crystal Formation Experiment  Objective: To grow crystals and observe the process of crystal formation in a fun and interactive science experiment.  Materials:   Borax (available in the laundry section of most stores) Pipe cleaners (chenille stems) String or yarn Pencil or popsicle stick Wide-mouthed glass jar or container Boiling water Optional: Food colo</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-crystals-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Sunscreen test, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sunscreen-test-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Sunscreen Test - Exploring Sun Protection Experiment  Objective: To test and compare the effectiveness of different sunscreens in blocking harmful UV rays.  Materials:   Several brands of sunscreen with varying SPF levels (make sure they are appropriate for children&amp;#39;s use) Small squares of white construction paper or cardboard Marker or pen Tape Stopwatch or timer Access to sunlight   P</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 20:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sunscreen-test-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Walking water, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/walking-water-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Walking Water - Capillary Action Experiment  Objective: To observe and investigate capillary action by creating a &amp;quot;walking water&amp;quot; effect between two cups.  Materials:   6 clear plastic cups Water Food coloring (different colors) Paper towels Optional: Tray or plastic container to catch any spills   Procedure:   Gather the materials required for the walking water experiment. Line u</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/walking-water-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Coffee ground fossils, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coffee-ground-fossils-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Coffee Ground Fossils - Introduction to Paleontology Experiment  Objective: To create coffee ground fossils and introduce children to the concept of paleontology and the process of fossilization.  Materials:   Coffee grounds White flour Salt Water Mixing bowl Measuring cups and spoons Small objects (e.g., plastic dinosaurs, shells, small toys) Plastic wrap or parchment paper Optional: Paint</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 16:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coffee-ground-fossils-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Coin inertia, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coin-inertia-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Coin Inertia - Exploring Inertia Experiment  Objective: To investigate the concept of inertia using coins and explore how objects tend to resist changes in motion.  Materials:   Coins of different sizes and denominations Flat surface (table or countertop) Index card or piece of cardboard Optional: Ruler or measuring tape for measuring distances   Procedure:   Begin by discussing the concept</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 18:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coin-inertia-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Film canister rocket, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/film-canister-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Film Canister Rocket - Exploring Chemical Reactions and Propulsion Experiment  Objective: To create a film canister rocket and investigate the principles of chemical reactions and propulsion.  Materials:   Film canister with a tight-fitting lid Alka-Seltzer tablets Water Safety goggles Optional: Decorative materials (markers, stickers) for customization   Procedure:   Begin by discussing th</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/film-canister-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Hoop and straw airplane, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hoop-and-straw-airplane-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Hoop and Straw Aeroplane - Exploring Aerodynamics Experiment  Objective: To build and test a hoop and straw aeroplane, investigating the principles of aerodynamics and flight.  Materials:   Drinking straw Lightweight paper (such as construction paper or printer paper) Scissors Tape Hoop or circular object (e.g., a plastic lid, a small hoop made from a pipe cleaner) Optional: Decorative mate</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 10:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hoop-and-straw-airplane-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leaf breathing, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-breathing-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Leaf Breathing - Investigating Transpiration Experiment  Objective: To explore the process of transpiration in plants by observing &amp;quot;leaf breathing&amp;quot; through the movement of water in a plant stem.  Materials:   Freshly cut leafy plant stem (e.g., a leafy branch from a tree or a herbaceous plant) Clear glass or container Water Food coloring (optional) Optional: Plastic wrap or transp</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-breathing-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Marshmallow catapult, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marshmallow-catapult-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Marshmallow Catapult - Exploring Projectile Motion Experiment  Objective: To build and test a marshmallow catapult, exploring principles of force, motion, and projectile trajectory.  Materials:   Popsicle sticks or craft sticks Rubber bands Plastic spoon Small marshmallows or soft projectiles Tape Optional: Decorative materials (markers, stickers) for customization   Procedure:   Begin by d</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marshmallow-catapult-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Sticky ice, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sticky-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Sticky Ice - Exploring Surface Tension Experiment  Objective: To investigate surface tension by creating &amp;quot;sticky&amp;quot; ice cubes that can cling to various surfaces.  Materials:   Ice cube tray Water Salt String or thread Various surfaces to test (e.g., plastic, glass, metal, fabric) Optional: Food coloring for visual effect   Procedure:   Fill the ice cube tray with water, leaving some</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sticky-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Paper bridge, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/paper-bridge-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Paper Bridge - Engineering and Structural Strength Experiment  Objective: To design and build a paper bridge that can support the weight of objects and explore the concept of structural strength.  Materials:   Sheets of paper (construction paper or printer paper) Scissors Rulers Books or other small objects to serve as weights Optional: Tape or glue (to reinforce the bridge)   Procedure:   </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/paper-bridge-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Color changing invisible ink, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-changing-invisible-ink-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Color-Changing Invisible Ink - Chemical Reaction Experiment  Objective: To create and reveal color-changing invisible ink using a simple chemical reaction.  Materials:   Lemon juice or white vinegar Water White paper or a blank sheet of paper Cotton swabs or small paintbrushes Heat source (hairdryer or iron) Optional: Food coloring for additional color effects   Procedure:   Create the invi</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-changing-invisible-ink-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Make a compass, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/make-a-compass-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Make Your Own Compass - Magnetism Experiment  Objective: To create a simple compass and explore the principles of magnetism.  Materials:   Small, lightweight magnet (e.g., a bar magnet or a refrigerator magnet) Cork or a small piece of Styrofoam Small bowl or dish filled with water Sewing needle (must be made of steel, not stainless steel) Optional: Tape or glue (to secure the magnet to the</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 17:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/make-a-compass-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Elephant toothpaste, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/elephant-toothpaste-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Elephant Toothpaste - Chemical Reaction Experiment  Objective: To demonstrate an exothermic chemical reaction by creating a foamy eruption known as &amp;quot;elephant toothpaste.&amp;quot;  Materials:   1/2 cup hydrogen peroxide (6% or higher concentration) Dish soap (liquid) Dry yeast Warm water Empty plastic soda bottle (16-ounce or larger) Funnel Safety goggles Tray or large container (to catch </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/elephant-toothpaste-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Milk bottle xylophone, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/milk-bottle-xylophone-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Milk Bottle Xylophone - Sound and Pitch Experiment  Objective: To explore sound and pitch by creating a milk bottle xylophone.  Materials:   Empty glass milk bottles (varying sizes) Water Wooden sticks or metal spoons (for striking the bottles) Optional: Food coloring or colored tape (for visual effect)   Procedure:   Gather a set of empty glass milk bottles. You can use bottles of differen</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/milk-bottle-xylophone-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Floating fish, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Floating Fish - Density and Buoyancy Experiment  Objective: To explore the concepts of density and buoyancy by creating a floating fish.  Materials:   Clay or playdough Plasticine or modeling clay Plastic toy fish or small plastic object A basin, tub, or container filled with water   Procedure:   Start by shaping the plasticine or modeling clay into a small ball or disc shape. This will ser</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Craft stick chain reaction, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/craft-stick-chain-reaction-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Craft Stick Chain Reaction - Potential and Kinetic Energy Experiment  Objective: To explore potential and kinetic energy by creating a chain reaction using craft sticks.  Materials:   Craft sticks (popsicle sticks) Small binder clips or clothespins Optional: Decorative materials (markers, stickers, paint) for customization A wide, flat surface for the experiment (e.g., table, floor)   Proce</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/craft-stick-chain-reaction-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Grow an avocado tree, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-an-avocado-tree-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Grow an Avocado Tree - Seed Germination Experiment  Objective: To explore the process of seed germination and observe the growth of an avocado tree.  Materials:   An avocado pit (seed) Toothpicks Glass or jar Water Optional: Notebook or journal for recording observations and measurements   Procedure:   Carefully remove the pit (seed) from a ripe avocado. Rinse off any remaining fruit flesh </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 18:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-an-avocado-tree-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Amplify a Smartphone, Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/amplify-a-smartphone-science-experiment-for-kids.html</link>
			<description>Amplifying the sound of a smartphone can indeed be turned into a science experiment, allowing kids to explore the principles of acoustics and sound amplification. Here&amp;#39;s a simple science experiment idea:  Title: Investigating Sound Amplification with Everyday Materials  Objective: To explore different materials and their effects on amplifying the sound of a smartphone.  Materials:   Smartphone</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/amplify-a-smartphone-science-experiment-for-kids.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a Mini Baking Soda Rocket?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-mini-baking-soda-rocket.html</link>
			<description>Creating a mini baking soda rocket can be a fun and educational experiment. Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide to making one:  Materials you will need:   A film canister with a tight-fitting lid Baking soda (sodium bicarbonate) Vinegar Tissue or toilet paper Safety goggles (optional but recommended for eye protection)                      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});        Instructio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-mini-baking-soda-rocket.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>