<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Chutney - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/chutney.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Jonna roti with chili chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jonna-roti-with-chili-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Jonna Roti (Sorghum Roti) with Chilli Chutney in Andhra style:  For Jonna Roti:  Ingredients:   2 cups jowar flour (sorghum flour) Water as needed Salt to taste Oil or ghee for cooking   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the jowar flour and salt. Gradually add water and knead the flour to form a soft and pliable dough. Add water as needed to achieve the right consis</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 09:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jonna-roti-with-chili-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ragi roti with tomato chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ragi-roti-with-tomato-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Ragi Roti with Tomato Chutney in Andhra style:  #1 For Ragi Roti:   1 cup ragi flour (finger millet flour) 1/4 cup finely chopped onions 1/4 cup grated carrots 2 green chilies, finely chopped 2 tablespoons chopped coriander leaves Salt to taste Water as needed Oil for cooking   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the ragi flour, chopped onions, grated carrots, green c</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ragi-roti-with-tomato-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pudina chutney Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Pudina Chutney is a flavorful condiment and aromatic chutney to serve with rice, mudde, idli, dosa. Pudina Chutney can also be served with snacks like bonda, bajji too.  People sometimes are confused pudina chutney with mint chutney or green chutney that is served along with chats and tandoori platter, but it&amp;#39;s not the same which we serve with rice or mudde or idle and this chutney is more aut</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Raw Mango Chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Raw mango chutney is a flavorful condiment made with raw mangos, coriander leaves, onions and some spices. Raw Mango Chutney is a must-try recipe when raw mangoes are in season. Raw mangoes are packed with minerals and vitamins and are good to beat the summer heat.  This raw mango chutney aids digestion and enhances the taste, aroma and nutrition of any dish. We usually have this raw mango chutney</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 13:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>