<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Coorg - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coorg.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Ten best hill stations to Travel Solo in South India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in South India offers a unique blend of tranquility, adventure and scenic beauty.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in South India for solo travelers:   Munnar, Kerala   Known for its tea gardens, rolling hills and pleasant weather, Munnar is a great destination for solo travelers. The serene environment and numerous trekking trails make it ideal for exploring</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 08:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in Karnataka to travel solo in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-karnataka-to-travel-solo-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo in Karnataka during hot summers can be a delightful experience, especially when you explore destinations with cooler climates or indoor attractions. Karnataka offers a diverse range of destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers.  Here are some of the best places to visit in Karnataka during the hot summer months:   Coorg (Kodagu):   Known as the &amp;quot;Scotland of</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-karnataka-to-travel-solo-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in South India to travel in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>South India offers several destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers due to their cooler climates, hill stations and coastal areas.  Here are some of the best places to visit in South India during the hot summer months, along with reasons, ways to travel and the best time to visit:    Ooty, Tamil Nadu:   Why: Ooty, also known as the &amp;quot;Queen of Hill Stations,&amp;quot; offers c</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 08:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Coorg Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-coorg-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Coorg can be a wonderful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the lush green landscapes, coffee plantations and serene natural beauty of this hill station in Karnataka. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Mysore -&amp;gt; Coorg -&amp;gt; Madikeri -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Mysore -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Coorg   Start your trip early </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-coorg-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>