<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Couple - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/couple.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to find out that your partner has a toxic personality?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-find-out-that-your-partner-has-a-toxic-personality.html</link>
			<description>Identifying a toxic personality in a partner can be challenging, as toxic behavior often manifests gradually and may be disguised by other traits. However, there are some signs and red flags that may indicate that your partner has a toxic personality.  Here&amp;#39;s how to recognize and address toxic behavior in a partner:   Trust Your Gut:   Pay attention to your instincts and feelings about the rel</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2024 19:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-find-out-that-your-partner-has-a-toxic-personality.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>For what reasons do relationships fail?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-what-reasons-do-relationships-fail.html</link>
			<description>Relationships can fail for various reasons and the dynamics of each relationship are unique.  However, there are some common factors that can contribute to relationship failure:   Poor Communication:   Communication breakdown is one of the primary reasons relationships fail. Lack of effective communication can lead to misunderstandings, unresolved conflicts and feelings of resentment.   Lack of Tr</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-what-reasons-do-relationships-fail.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>UnConditional Love in a Couples Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>It is commonly said that Women are complex in mental nature while Men remain easy to understand and simple. Whatever be the reasons that backup this comment,&amp;nbsp;in relationships both Men and Women follow slightly diverted paths.&amp;nbsp;What Men look for in a relationship is not what motivates Women to fall in relationships. The differences in desires, mentalities, passion, expression levels etc., </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 08:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Expectations and Freedom in a Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>People having expectations in a relationship and willing to have freedom in relationships are few of the main reasons for not having a peaceful and healthy relationship with each other.  Having or Setting some unrealistic expectations to have in a relationship can contribute to ending their marriage.  Honestly both the people should be open in communication to each other in terms of the expectatio</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lessons Learnt from three years of Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-learnt-from-three-years-of-relationship.html</link>
			<description>Living together for almost three years is a good amount of journey in your life. For me atleast like, part of me feels like time is absolutely flying and the other half feels like we have been married for three years. We have certainly not been perfect, but I'm gonna share fews lessons which I learnt out of these three years which I spent in my relationship.                            1. Importanc</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-learnt-from-three-years-of-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Ooty Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</link>
			<description>Three days Trip from Bangalore  Ooty  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Ooty known as the Queen of the hill stations in South In</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Openness in a Couples Relationships can be Secret/Private</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/openness-in-relationships-secret-or-private.html</link>
			<description>In a healthy romantic relationship, as time goes on trust is earned and we eventually open up more &amp; more. Based on each others mutual respect &amp; valuing, couples are sometimes unclear in how much they should or want to share within each other. Each of them have right to privacy and each decide, how much to share or how much to open up.                                Few are too open or soon offer </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/openness-in-relationships-secret-or-private.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>