<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>COVID - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/covid.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Studies estimate long COVID-19 has over two hundred Symptoms</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</link>
			<description>According to a Lancet's journal EClinicalMedicine, In the Coronavirus (Covid-19) patients who are facing prolonged symptoms have reported more than 200 symptoms across 10 organ systems.                            They have analysed the responses of 3,762 peoples from 56 different countries with confirmed or suspected Covid-19. And the data were collected from September 6, 2020, to November 25, 202</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Black Fungus - Detected in Coronavirus Patients</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</link>
			<description>Black fungus is an infection caused by a fungus named mucormycosis. This fungal infection is being reported in a few Corona-affected patients during or post-recovery.                                People catch mucormycosis when they come in contact with the fungal spores in the environment. It can also be contacted through skin contact through a cut, burn, or any other form of skin trauma.       </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>COVID-19 Vaccination in India, Covishield and Covaxin</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/covid--vaccination-in-india.html</link>
			<description>In January 2021 India started National Vaccination programme against the SARS-CoV-2 virus which has caused the COVID-19 pandemic. The drive prioritises healthcare and frontline workers and then those over the age of 60 and then those over the age of 45 and suffering from certain comorbidities.                                In January 2021 Secretary-General of the United Nations Antonio Guterres s</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/covid--vaccination-in-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Coronavirus, Discovered in the 1960s, Serious Respiratory Tract Infections</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coronavirus-discovered-in-the-s-serious-respiratory-tract-infections.html</link>
			<description>Coronaviruses are a group of viruses that cause diseases in mammals and birds that include diarrhea in cows and pigs and upper respiratory disease in chickens. In humans, the virus causes respiratory infections, which are often mild, but in rare cases are potentially lethal.                                There are no vaccines or antiviral drugs that are approved for prevention or treatment.      </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coronavirus-discovered-in-the-s-serious-respiratory-tract-infections.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>