<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Crime - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/crime.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Be Aware of Chain Snatchers &amp; Tips to Prevent Chain Snatching</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/be-aware-of-chain-snatchers-tips-to-prevent-chain-snatching.html</link>
			<description>Chain Snatching is one of the crime happening across India by different individuals or gangs. One should be aware while being in public places and should be cautious always. Chain snatching an easy job unlike burglaries, robberies or dacoities. These chain snatchers mostly will be from different places, They will often go to a new places and do their job and leave within hours.                    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/be-aware-of-chain-snatchers-tips-to-prevent-chain-snatching.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Reduce the Risk of Becoming a Sexual Assault Victim!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</link>
			<description>To Reduce the risk for you to becoming a sexual victim, you have to take some preventative measures, which will help you to avoid a risky situations from escalating. Anyone can be the target of sexual assault, regardless of age, gender, race, ethnicity, sexual orientation, sexual history, or social class. There is no stereotypical victim or rapist.                                What's bad? - Near</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prime accused in gang-rape case nabbed after two decades</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prime-accused-in-gang-rape-case-nabbed-after-two-decades.html</link>
			<description>Prime accused Bibekananda Biswal in a sensational gangrape that shook Odisha in its aftermath in 1999 is now caught by Police from Aamby Valley in Lonavala in Maharashtra.                                The incident, that occurred in 1999, had created a state-wide outrage. A total of three persons were accused in the case. Two of them - Pradeep Sahi and Dhirendra Mohanty, were arrested and convict</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prime-accused-in-gang-rape-case-nabbed-after-two-decades.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>