<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Dentist - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Is Banking Dental Stem Cells today is important?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-banking-dental-stem-cells-today-is-important.html</link>
			<description>At the time of child birth, preserving and banking umbilical cord stem cells is important. These cells are the mesenchymal cells which differentiate to develop human organs like Brain, heart, liver, kidney, muscles etc at the developing stage of a baby in the mother womb.  In case you miss collecting or preserving stem cells at the time of birth? Then the best choice is to collect Dental stem cell</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-banking-dental-stem-cells-today-is-important.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dentist Inputs on Diabetes and Oral Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-inputs-on-diabetes-and-oral-health.html</link>
			<description>In diabetes people, due to increased glycaemic state, there will be more glucose and nutrients available for bacteria to keep alive and flourish. And this results in an increase in the bacterial load, as they can live and flourish well. And diabetic people take insulin, which is a hormone that is necessary to keep the level of blood glucose under check. And Diabetes mellitus (DM), is a group of me</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-inputs-on-diabetes-and-oral-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dental Fluorosis: Types, Prevention, and Treatments</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dental-fluorosis-types-prevention-and-treatments.html</link>
			<description>In this article you will find what is Dental fluorosis, how this will affect your teeth, different types of dental fluorosis, how you can prevent this and what treatments are available for dental fluorosis. Generally, Fluoride content in water is more in few places, so drinking this water may lead to dental fluorosis. What is Dental fluorosis? Dental fluorosis is the hypomineralization of tooth en</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dental-fluorosis-types-prevention-and-treatments.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why do dentists suggest Clear aligners (invisalign)?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-dentists-suggest-clear-aligners-invisalign.html</link>
			<description>Every patient wants their teeth to be in the proper correct position. In young patients they go for orthodontist braces treatment for the correction of their teeth. Patients demand for esthetic orthodontic appliances as made for clear aligners into mainstream modern orthodontics. Clear aligners actually began in 1926, by Orrin Remensydre’s Flex-o-Tite, the gum massage appliance which has side ef</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-dentists-suggest-clear-aligners-invisalign.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dentist suggestions on Teeth Cleaning</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-teeth-cleaning.html</link>
			<description>As we brush our teeth twice a day in such cases as well, do we really need teeth cleaning? And why does the Dentist say to have teeth cleaning in such cases also?.
                            Let’s understand what it is actually from a Dentist.
                            In Dental terminology, teeth cleaning is referred to as "Scaling". So what is this "Scaling"? While you visit a Dentist for S</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-teeth-cleaning.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>