<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Dental - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dental.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Is Banking Dental Stem Cells today is important?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-banking-dental-stem-cells-today-is-important.html</link>
			<description>At the time of child birth, preserving and banking umbilical cord stem cells is important. These cells are the mesenchymal cells which differentiate to develop human organs like Brain, heart, liver, kidney, muscles etc at the developing stage of a baby in the mother womb.  In case you miss collecting or preserving stem cells at the time of birth? Then the best choice is to collect Dental stem cell</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 May 2022 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-banking-dental-stem-cells-today-is-important.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dentist Inputs on Diabetes and Oral Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-inputs-on-diabetes-and-oral-health.html</link>
			<description>In diabetes people, due to increased glycaemic state, there will be more glucose and nutrients available for bacteria to keep alive and flourish. And this results in an increase in the bacterial load, as they can live and flourish well. And diabetic people take insulin, which is a hormone that is necessary to keep the level of blood glucose under check. And Diabetes mellitus (DM), is a group of me</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Mar 2022 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-inputs-on-diabetes-and-oral-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dental Fluorosis: Types, Prevention, and Treatments</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dental-fluorosis-types-prevention-and-treatments.html</link>
			<description>In this article you will find what is Dental fluorosis, how this will affect your teeth, different types of dental fluorosis, how you can prevent this and what treatments are available for dental fluorosis. Generally, Fluoride content in water is more in few places, so drinking this water may lead to dental fluorosis. What is Dental fluorosis? Dental fluorosis is the hypomineralization of tooth en</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dental-fluorosis-types-prevention-and-treatments.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why do dentists suggest Clear aligners (invisalign)?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-dentists-suggest-clear-aligners-invisalign.html</link>
			<description>Every patient wants their teeth to be in the proper correct position. In young patients they go for orthodontist braces treatment for the correction of their teeth. Patients demand for esthetic orthodontic appliances as made for clear aligners into mainstream modern orthodontics. Clear aligners actually began in 1926, by Orrin Remensydre’s Flex-o-Tite, the gum massage appliance which has side ef</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-dentists-suggest-clear-aligners-invisalign.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dentist suggestions on Teeth Cleaning</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-teeth-cleaning.html</link>
			<description>As we brush our teeth twice a day in such cases as well, do we really need teeth cleaning? And why does the Dentist say to have teeth cleaning in such cases also?.
                            Let’s understand what it is actually from a Dentist.
                            In Dental terminology, teeth cleaning is referred to as "Scaling". So what is this "Scaling"? While you visit a Dentist for S</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Aug 2021 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-teeth-cleaning.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why Dental Implants?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-dental-implants.html</link>
			<description>Advanced dental treatments all over the world led to new advanced solutions for dental problems, one such is Implant. An implant is a medical device manufactured to replace a missing biological structure, support a damaged biological structure, or enhance an existing biological structure.
                                In cases a like, 
                                    A person’s teeth missi</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Jun 2021 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-dental-implants.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dentist suggestions on Quit Smoking &amp; Breathe Healthy</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-quit-smoking-breathe-healthy.html</link>
			<description>We have heard many times that smoking causes cancer. Smoking kills! but how? Let's know about facts about smoking and it's harmful causes to our body.
                                Each one cigarette contains nicotine (the main ingredient) and more than 5000 chemical compounds of which many are cancerous. The nicotine gets you addicted to smoking as every time you smoke a cigarette, you get a go</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-quit-smoking-breathe-healthy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tooth Sensitivity? What to do &amp; What not to do?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tooth-sensitivity-what-to-do-what-not-to-do.html</link>
			<description>Are you afraid of eating any food which is hot or cold or sweet or sour? If yes, then u might be suffering from tooth sensitivity. In this article, we're gonna get dentist advice for, What causes tooth sensitivity? And What should you do if you have tooth sensitivity? And what should you not do if you have tooth sensitivity?
                                So, let's see what our dentist says..
   </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Mar 2021 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tooth-sensitivity-what-to-do-what-not-to-do.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to keep your Kids Teeth Healthy and Strong?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-keep-your-kids-teeth-healthy-strong.html</link>
			<description>Good smiles from kids makes us smile more and keep us happy. But how to make your kids teeth healthy from initial stages. Within this  article, I will be sharing a few basic tips to keep your kids teeth healthy &amp; strong.
                                Here are few basic measures to be taken by every parent to keep their kids teeth healthy &amp; strong.
                                - &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 27 Feb 2021 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-keep-your-kids-teeth-healthy-strong.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Choosing the best Toothbrush</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/choosing-the-best-toothbrush.html</link>
			<description>Every day your mouth is at war, fighting off harmful bacteria and dangerous invaders like plaque. Believe it or not, your best line of defense in this war against decay is your toothbrush. Weaponized with a fluoridated toothpaste, your toothbrush can ensure victory every time you visit your dentist. But which is the best kind of toothbrush? Next time you arm yourself with a plaque-busting toothbru</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 21 Feb 2021 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/choosing-the-best-toothbrush.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What to Eat &amp; What to Avoid, after a Tooth Extraction</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-eat-and-what-to-avoid-after-a-tooth-extraction.html</link>
			<description>Tooth extraction is a long chain of steps where you have to take care of the area of the extraction for weeks of extration steps. Means you need to take care of brushing and cleaning the area properly &amp; avoiding too much activity right after the extraction.
                                Since you have to consume food everyday, you can do by taking certain restrictions like what you can eat and w</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-eat-and-what-to-avoid-after-a-tooth-extraction.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>