<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Dharmasthala - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Ugrappa Committee Report, on Unnatural Deaths in and around Dharmasthala (Belthangady taluk, Dakshina Kannada)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ugrappa-committee-report-on-unnatural-deaths-in-and-around-dharmasthala-belthangady-taluk-dakshina-kannada.html</link>
			<description>The Ugrappa Committee Report, submitted on 24 March 2018, has gained renewed attention following the recent Dharmasthala mass burial investigation (2025). The committee was formed to examine the alarming number of unnatural deaths and missing women reported in Belthangady taluk of Dakshina Kannada, an area that includes and surrounds Dharmasthala.  Background of the Committee  The committee was ch</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Sep 2025 11:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ugrappa-committee-report-on-unnatural-deaths-in-and-around-dharmasthala-belthangady-taluk-dakshina-kannada.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Recovers Five More Skeletons, Suspected Black Magic Items at Bangle Gudde</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-recovers-five-more-skeletons-suspected-black-magic-items-at-bangle-gudde.html</link>
			<description>Belthangady | September 11, 2025  The Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the Dharmasthala mass burial case has recovered five more sets of skeletal remains during its second mahajar (spot inspection) at Bangle Gudde in Belthangady on Wednesday, September 10, 2025. The discovery comes just four days after the SIT found skeletal remains of two individuals during the first mahajar conducted on </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Sep 2025 13:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-recovers-five-more-skeletons-suspected-black-magic-items-at-bangle-gudde.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Seeks Custody Extension, Villagers Step Forward, ED Begins Probe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-seeks-custody-extension-villagers-step-forward-ed-begins-probe.html</link>
			<description>Bengaluru | September 2, 2025  The Special Investigation Team (SIT), formed on July 19, 2025, to probe the Dharmasthala mass burial allegations, continues to tighten its investigation. On Tuesday, September 2, 2025, a series of key developments unfolded involving custody proceedings, local cooperation, and new financial scrutiny.  Custody Extension of Complainant  The complainant, a former sanitat</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-seeks-custody-extension-villagers-step-forward-ed-begins-probe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Investigations Latest Developments (August 31, 2025 – September 1, 2025)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-investigation-s-latest-developments-augustseptember--.html</link>
			<description>Bengaluru / Mangaluru &amp;ndash; The Special Investigation Team (SIT), probing the Dharmasthala mass burial allegations, has made significant headway in its investigation over the past two days:    Search Operations &amp;amp; Mahazars in Bengaluru    On August 31, 2025, the SIT brought the complainant&amp;mdash;known as &amp;ldquo;mask-man&amp;rdquo; Chinnaiah&amp;mdash;to Bengaluru to conduct coordinated search operati</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Sep 2025 08:18:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-investigation-s-latest-developments-augustseptember--.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Arrests Whistleblower Bheema on Perjury Charges</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-arrests-whistleblower-bheema-on-perjury-charges.html</link>
			<description>Belthangady  In a significant development in the ongoing Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case investigation, the Special Investigation Team (SIT) has arrested Bheema, the whistleblower whose allegations triggered the probe. He was taken into custody on Saturday after two consecutive days of intense questioning.  According to SIT sources, Bheema was interrogated late into the night on Friday, with questio</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:18:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-arrests-whistleblower-bheema-on-perjury-charges.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Arrest of Bheema Reignites Questions in Soujanya Case</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-crimes-arrest-of-bheema-reignites-questions-in-soujanya-case.html</link>
			<description>23 August 2025  The arrest of Bheema, a former sanitation worker, by the Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the Dharmasthala mass burial case has taken a dramatic turn. According to highly placed sources, investigators now suspect his involvement in the disposal of Soujanya&amp;rsquo;s body, a case that has remained unresolved for over a decade.  Allegations of Involvement in Soujanya&amp;rsquo;s Ca</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 10:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-crimes-arrest-of-bheema-reignites-questions-in-soujanya-case.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>SIT Reviewing Key Documents, Questions Key Witness in Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sit-reviewing-key-documents-questions-key-witness-in-dharmasthala-mass-burial-case.html</link>
			<description>August 22, 2025  The Special Investigation Team (SIT) formed to probe the Dharmasthala mass burial case has begun a &amp;ldquo;Reverse Investigation,&amp;rdquo; re-examining earlier records and questioning key witnesses to strengthen the inquiry.  According to official sources, the SIT is currently reviewing the Unnatural Death Report (UDR) and missing-persons documents related to the case. Investigators </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sit-reviewing-key-documents-questions-key-witness-in-dharmasthala-mass-burial-case.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Crimes: Justice for Sowjanya Activist Mahesh Shetty Thimarodi Detained</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-crimes-sowjanya-justice-activist-mahesh-shetty-thimarodi-detained.html</link>
			<description>In a dramatic turn of events, Brahmavara police detained activist Mahesh Shetty Thimarodi from his residence on Thursday morning. Thimarodi, a well-known face in the ongoing struggle for justice in the Soujanya rape and murder case of 2012, has long been vocal against political interference and systemic failures in the case.  According to reports, the action against him came after he spoke on a Yo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-crimes-sowjanya-justice-activist-mahesh-shetty-thimarodi-detained.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Has Full Liberty to Probe and Conduct Exhumations</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-has-full-liberty-to-probe-and-conduct-exhumations.html</link>
			<description>The Special Investigation Team (SIT) investigating the Dharmasthala mass burial case has been given complete freedom to continue its probe, including further exhumation operations. Karnataka Home Minister G. Parameshwara, speaking on Monday (August 18, 2025), clarified that the State government will not interfere in the investigation and that the SIT alone will decide the next course of action.  S</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-has-full-liberty-to-probe-and-conduct-exhumations.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT to Submit Full Report, No Interim Findings</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-to-submit-full-report-no-interim-findings.html</link>
			<description>Bengaluru: The Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the Dharmasthala mass burial case will submit its full investigation report directly to the court after completing the probe. Officials have clarified that the SIT will not provide any interim report to the State government.  The report will be placed before the Principal Civil Judge and Judicial Magistrate First Class (JMFC) in Belthangady t</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 09:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-to-submit-full-report-no-interim-findings.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT to Continue Exhumation with Enhanced Preparations</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-to-continue-exhumation-with-enhanced-preparations.html</link>
			<description>The Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the alleged mass burials linked to the Dharmasthala Temple Administration has confirmed that it will continue the exhumation operations, contrary to certain media reports suggesting a possible halt. Officials have stated that the process will move forward with extra preparation before any new digging begins.  Current Status of the Operation  On Wednesda</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 11:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-to-continue-exhumation-with-enhanced-preparations.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Granted Police Station Status, Investigation Gains Legal Edge</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-granted-police-station-status-investigation-gains-legal-edge.html</link>
			<description>Bengaluru/Mangaluru  The Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the alleged Dharmasthala mass burial and murder case has now been officially granted the status of a police station, a move expected to significantly strengthen the investigation and prevent legal hurdles during trial proceedings.  Empowered Status  According to Home Ministry sources, the order was issued on Thursday (August 7, 2025</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-granted-police-station-status-investigation-gains-legal-edge.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>YouTubers Attacked by Alleged Dharmasthala D-Gang: A Blow to Press Freedom</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/youtubers-attacked-by-alleged-dharmasthala-d-gang-a-blow-to-press-freedom.html</link>
			<description>Dharmasthala, Karnataka &amp;ndash; 6th August 2025  In a shocking incident that has sparked widespread outrage, two independent YouTubers were reportedly attacked while covering ongoing developments around the mysterious deaths and criminal allegations in and around the Dharmasthala region. The attack, allegedly carried out by what locals and media sources are calling the &amp;quot;Dharmasthala D-Gang&amp;qu</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/youtubers-attacked-by-alleged-dharmasthala-d-gang-a-blow-to-press-freedom.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 09:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>