<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Dharmasthala - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Murder Case Escalates to Delhi: Grievance Seeks NIA Probe, Alleges State Government Obstruction</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-murder-case-escalates-to-delhi-grievance-seeks-nia-probe-alleges-state-government-obstruction.html</link>
			<description>Dharmasthala / New Delhi &amp;mdash; A formal grievance submitted through the Central Government&amp;rsquo;s CPGRAMS portal has raised serious concerns about the handling of the Dharmasthala mass murder case. The petitioner has urged the Ministry of Home Affairs to transfer the case to the National Investigation Agency (NIA), citing international dimensions and obstruction by senior Karnataka political fi</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-murder-case-escalates-to-delhi-grievance-seeks-nia-probe-alleges-state-government-obstruction.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>YouTubers Attacked by Alleged Dharmasthala D-Gang: A Blow to Press Freedom</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/youtubers-attacked-by-alleged-dharmasthala-d-gang-a-blow-to-press-freedom.html</link>
			<description>Dharmasthala, Karnataka &amp;ndash; 6th August 2025  In a shocking incident that has sparked widespread outrage, two independent YouTubers were reportedly attacked while covering ongoing developments around the mysterious deaths and criminal allegations in and around the Dharmasthala region. The attack, allegedly carried out by what locals and media sources are calling the &amp;quot;Dharmasthala D-Gang&amp;qu</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/youtubers-attacked-by-alleged-dharmasthala-d-gang-a-blow-to-press-freedom.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2024 18:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>