<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Dharmasthala - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>SIT Reviewing Key Documents, Questions Key Witness in Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sit-reviewing-key-documents-questions-key-witness-in-dharmasthala-mass-burial-case.html</link>
			<description>August 22, 2025  The Special Investigation Team (SIT) formed to probe the Dharmasthala mass burial case has begun a &amp;ldquo;Reverse Investigation,&amp;rdquo; re-examining earlier records and questioning key witnesses to strengthen the inquiry.  According to official sources, the SIT is currently reviewing the Unnatural Death Report (UDR) and missing-persons documents related to the case. Investigators </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 16:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sit-reviewing-key-documents-questions-key-witness-in-dharmasthala-mass-burial-case.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Crimes: Justice for Sowjanya Activist Mahesh Shetty Thimarodi Detained</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-crimes-sowjanya-justice-activist-mahesh-shetty-thimarodi-detained.html</link>
			<description>In a dramatic turn of events, Brahmavara police detained activist Mahesh Shetty Thimarodi from his residence on Thursday morning. Thimarodi, a well-known face in the ongoing struggle for justice in the Soujanya rape and murder case of 2012, has long been vocal against political interference and systemic failures in the case.  According to reports, the action against him came after he spoke on a Yo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-crimes-sowjanya-justice-activist-mahesh-shetty-thimarodi-detained.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Has Full Liberty to Probe and Conduct Exhumations</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-has-full-liberty-to-probe-and-conduct-exhumations.html</link>
			<description>The Special Investigation Team (SIT) investigating the Dharmasthala mass burial case has been given complete freedom to continue its probe, including further exhumation operations. Karnataka Home Minister G. Parameshwara, speaking on Monday (August 18, 2025), clarified that the State government will not interfere in the investigation and that the SIT alone will decide the next course of action.  S</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 11:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-has-full-liberty-to-probe-and-conduct-exhumations.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT to Submit Full Report, No Interim Findings</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-to-submit-full-report-no-interim-findings.html</link>
			<description>Bengaluru: The Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the Dharmasthala mass burial case will submit its full investigation report directly to the court after completing the probe. Officials have clarified that the SIT will not provide any interim report to the State government.  The report will be placed before the Principal Civil Judge and Judicial Magistrate First Class (JMFC) in Belthangady t</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 09:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-to-submit-full-report-no-interim-findings.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: D K Shivakumar’s statement will have No Impact on SIT probe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-d-k-shivakumar-s-statement-will-have-no-impact-on-sit-probe.html</link>
			<description>The ongoing investigation into the Dharmasthala mass burial case remains unaffected by Karnataka Deputy Chief Minister and Bengaluru Development Minister D.K. Shivakumar&amp;rsquo;s recent comments, according to sources within the Karnataka Home Ministry.  Political Statements vs. Investigative Process  Shivakumar, on August 14, 2025, alleged that a &amp;ldquo;highly organised conspiracy&amp;rdquo; had been c</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-d-k-shivakumar-s-statement-will-have-no-impact-on-sit-probe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT to Continue Exhumation with Enhanced Preparations</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-to-continue-exhumation-with-enhanced-preparations.html</link>
			<description>The Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the alleged mass burials linked to the Dharmasthala Temple Administration has confirmed that it will continue the exhumation operations, contrary to certain media reports suggesting a possible halt. Officials have stated that the process will move forward with extra preparation before any new digging begins.  Current Status of the Operation  On Wednesda</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Aug 2025 11:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-to-continue-exhumation-with-enhanced-preparations.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Baliga murder accused ‘funded SDPI leaders’ to spin Hindu–Muslim narrative in Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/baliga-murder-accused-funded-sdpi-leaders-to-spin-hindu-muslim-narrative-in-dharmasthala-mass-burial-case.html</link>
			<description>Mangaluru &amp;ndash; A senior source in the Karnataka state intelligence department has revealed that an accused in the 2016 Vinayak Baliga murder case allegedly funded certain leaders of the Social Democratic Party of India (SDPI) to inject a communal Hindu&amp;ndash;Muslim narrative into the ongoing Dharmasthala mass burial investigation.  Vinayak Baliga, an RTI activist, was brutally hacked to death n</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Aug 2025 10:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/baliga-murder-accused-funded-sdpi-leaders-to-spin-hindu-muslim-narrative-in-dharmasthala-mass-burial-case.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Granted Police Station Status, Investigation Gains Legal Edge</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-granted-police-station-status-investigation-gains-legal-edge.html</link>
			<description>Bengaluru/Mangaluru  The Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the alleged Dharmasthala mass burial and murder case has now been officially granted the status of a police station, a move expected to significantly strengthen the investigation and prevent legal hurdles during trial proceedings.  Empowered Status  According to Home Ministry sources, the order was issued on Thursday (August 7, 2025</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-granted-police-station-status-investigation-gains-legal-edge.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Murder Case Escalates to Delhi: Grievance Seeks NIA Probe, Alleges State Government Obstruction</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-murder-case-escalates-to-delhi-grievance-seeks-nia-probe-alleges-state-government-obstruction.html</link>
			<description>Dharmasthala / New Delhi &amp;mdash; A formal grievance submitted through the Central Government&amp;rsquo;s CPGRAMS portal has raised serious concerns about the handling of the Dharmasthala mass murder case. The petitioner has urged the Ministry of Home Affairs to transfer the case to the National Investigation Agency (NIA), citing international dimensions and obstruction by senior Karnataka political fi</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-murder-case-escalates-to-delhi-grievance-seeks-nia-probe-alleges-state-government-obstruction.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>YouTubers Attacked by Alleged Dharmasthala D-Gang: A Blow to Press Freedom</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/youtubers-attacked-by-alleged-dharmasthala-d-gang-a-blow-to-press-freedom.html</link>
			<description>Dharmasthala, Karnataka &amp;ndash; 6th August 2025  In a shocking incident that has sparked widespread outrage, two independent YouTubers were reportedly attacked while covering ongoing developments around the mysterious deaths and criminal allegations in and around the Dharmasthala region. The attack, allegedly carried out by what locals and media sources are calling the &amp;quot;Dharmasthala D-Gang&amp;qu</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/youtubers-attacked-by-alleged-dharmasthala-d-gang-a-blow-to-press-freedom.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 12:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>