<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Docker - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/docker.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Multisite Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</link>
			<description>As we have seen in the earlier article to setup the Local environment with Lando &amp; Drupal, Now let's see how we set up the multisite with the lando.
                            And hope you are already aware of Drupal Multisite. If not, It is a feature of Drupal that allows you to run multiple Drupal installs off of a common codebase. This allows you to share themes and modules between a collectio</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 09:22:52 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</link>
			<description>We developers always choose to have some tools or setup, which makes our lives easier during the development process whether it might be a local environment or higher environments. Not only will lives be easier with such a setup, even the productivity of the individual or team will be increased. And today we are gonna see how Lando will help the drupal developer or drupal development much more qui</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 09:22:52 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Locally Setup and Scan your Docker images via Clair</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/locally-setup-and-scan-your-docker-images-via-clair.html</link>
			<description>Docker Images contain not only application code, but a OS and additional utilities to make application run as expected. Images can also be vulnerable its better not have any CVE's in image. Running scans are one of the way to protect from CVE's. These container scanning tools scan for known vulnerabilities in the image.
                                In this article, We use Clair to scan a Docker</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Mar 2021 09:22:52 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/locally-setup-and-scan-your-docker-images-via-clair.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>