<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Drupal - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Drupal.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Usage of Local Php Security Checker for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how the Local PHP Security Checker library will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated security review. Here comes the Local PHP Security Checker library, which checks for any known vulnerabilities in the package dependencies.  Th</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Jul 2022 14:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Read Data to Paragraph Template in Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/read-data-to-paragraph-template-in-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how to read the dynamic data of the node or entity or field values to the template file, which are specific to the paragraph template.  Generally while the Paragraph module is used, default template suggestions given by the paragraph module or the template suggestions provided by the hooks are used and further template design is done. Here&amp;rsquo;s the article wh</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 17 Jul 2022 12:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/read-data-to-paragraph-template-in-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Drupal Paragraphs?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</link>
			<description>Paragraphs can be used as a way for Content Creation in Drupal. It actually allows the site builders to do their stuff a bit cleanly and for the end users this will be pretty easy to manage the content, meaning people get more control on the Editing side.  Paragraphs is one of the&amp;nbsp; popular modules in Drupal, for handling content. It is more or less very similar to the fields and will provide </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 19:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PhpStan on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development and code review process. We have a similar helpful article related to Phpcs, have a check of this.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here come</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Twig Templates in Drupal?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how a developer can work with Twig templates, and how to override templates (if needed) and create template suggestions with hooks, so that templates could be easily managed.  Basically drupal allows people to override the existing twig templates, so that people can fully have control on the html generated via the custom theme.  First thing, we need to make sur</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 19:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Quick reference of Code Reviews for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how your Drupal team can do code reviews and available tools or libraries which help people in the team to do the code reviews seamlessly.  It&amp;rsquo;s pretty important to follow a few guidelines as well, so that all people or developers in the team are on the same page.  Firstly, for the code reviews to be at their best, the committed code should be more organis</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PHPCS on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  And to make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here comes the PHP codesniffer and Drupal coder module.  If you are maintaini</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Store Secrets Securely on Pantheon for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-secrets-securely-on-pantheon-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how people can store access keys and tokens securely, in the case of your drupal application that is managed on pantheon.  Generally, all the Access keys or Tokens or any Secret third party auth information should not be stored in the database or within the project web root, Its safe to store it encrypted and within a file, and keep the file outside of the proj</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-secrets-securely-on-pantheon-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Configuration management via Quicksilver on Pantheon</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuration-management-via-quicksilver-on-pantheon.html</link>
			<description>As we saw in the earlier article, like how we manage the configuration across the environments.  In this article we are going to see how Drupal configurations can be deployed or imported across the environments with the help of Quicksilver which hooks into platform workflows to automate your Pantheon WebOps workflow across the environments.  In the pantheon environment&amp;rsquo;s drupal code base, yo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuration-management-via-quicksilver-on-pantheon.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal Configuration management (Local, Dev, Test and Live)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-configuration-management-local-dev-test-and-live.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how Drupal serves configurations across the environments, which can be well maintained with help of some contributed modules and version control.  Drupal 8 onwards configuration has been saved in the yml files in a consistent manner, which includes all the enabled modules, all the content types, vocabularies, fields &amp;amp; views.  Making the configurations direct</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 15:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-configuration-management-local-dev-test-and-live.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Migrate your site from Drupal 7 To Drupal 9?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate-your-site-from-drupal-seven-to-drupal-nine.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see what are the important things you need to understand for the migration of your Drupal 7 site to the Drupal 9 site. And if you see from your Business perspective, Drupal 7 was launched nine years ago, and this is the perfect time for some reassessment of the needs of site users &amp; content managers. And if you see from Drupal’s end, Initially, Drupal 7 end of li</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate-your-site-from-drupal-seven-to-drupal-nine.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Improve Drupal Search with Solr, Locally configured via Lando</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Improve-Drupal-Search-with-Solr-Locally-configured-via-Lando.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn how Drupal search can be improved with Solr which provides great performance, and is suitable even for use on large commercial websites. And along with this using the search_api &amp; search_api_solr modules, helps to configure the Facets &amp; Multilingual content can be handled in an improved manner. And let's see how we can configure this locally with the help of </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 19:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Improve-Drupal-Search-with-Solr-Locally-configured-via-Lando.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>When to use hook_update_N &amp; hook_post_update_NAME?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/When-to-use-hook_update_N-and-hook_post_update_NAME.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn when to use hook_update_N and hook_post_update_NAME. In general, I was using hook_update_N for any database-related changes or with any configuration additions or updates. And I was using hook_post_update_NAME for any content creation or updating or for the creation or updating any taxonomy terms etc, sometimes for clearing site caches as well. But, let’s h</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/When-to-use-hook_update_N-and-hook_post_update_NAME.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Improvements for Editor Experience in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Improvements-for-Editor-Experience-in-Drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn what Drupal offers for text editors or content managers as a content management framework within Drupal Core &amp; Contributed modules. Earlier versions of Drupal have several useful features to help content editors to manage their content on a daily basis. And in the newer versions of Drupal (from when Symfony was introduced), there are a few more improvements i</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Improvements-for-Editor-Experience-in-Drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Core</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/What-Drupal-offers-as-Responsive-Web-Design-within-Core.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we gonna see What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Drupal Core for developers. While Drupal 8 was out and it had a buzz of being responsive, mobile friendly. And yes, the Internet is on the verge of being dominated by smartphones &amp; Drupal needs to be prepared.Mobile friendly will also mean the content is first. From a big screen to a little screen, elements would look</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Oct 2021 16:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/What-Drupal-offers-as-Responsive-Web-Design-within-Core.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Know why Symfony framework was picked by Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Know-why-Symfony-framework-was-picked-by-Drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we gonna see why Symfony was picked for Drupal and what it changes for developers. As we all know PHP evolved rapidly in the past years, and unfortunately, Drupal adjustment to this development was not satisfying, especially in the case of software engineering patterns adoption. And that is one of the reasons why Drupal Developers had to come up with creative ways to deal with suc</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 22 Aug 2021 10:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Know-why-Symfony-framework-was-picked-by-Drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understand why Twig is replacing PHP Template in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Understand-why-Twig-is-replacing-PHP-Template-in-Drupal.html</link>
			<description>A completely new template engine is introduced in Drupal. The templating system in all previous versions of Drupal is using theme_* functions and PHP-based *.tpl.php files. Now, this has been completely replaced in Drupal 8. Instead of using theme functions and theme template files, Drupal is now using the Twig templating system.
                            Twig is a PHP-based compiled templating </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 14 Aug 2021 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Understand-why-Twig-is-replacing-PHP-Template-in-Drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>In layman's terms, Services &amp; Dependency Injection in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/In-laymans-terms-Services-and-Dependency-Injection-in-Drupal.html</link>
			<description>If we look into the basis of Software engineering, Dependency Injection is an approach in which one object get another object that it depends on. And these other objects are called dependencies. And Injection refers to the passing of a dependency (as a service) into the client object that would use it.
                            With Dependency Injection, the class is no longer responsible for in</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/In-laymans-terms-Services-and-Dependency-Injection-in-Drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal Cache Clear &amp; Cache Rebuild</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Drupal-Cache-Clear-and-Cache-Rebuild.html</link>
			<description>In order to render a page via Drupal, Drupal will need to make several database queries and get the data to render. This process of making queries can be reduced by storing the web pages in a cache, which is what Drupal does.
                            And developers during developments may use this cache clear or cache rebuild quite often, like after installing a new module or theme. The site wo</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Jul 2021 15:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Drupal-Cache-Clear-and-Cache-Rebuild.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Multisite Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Multisite-Local-environment-setup-with-Lando-and-Drupal.html</link>
			<description>As we have seen in the earlier article to setup the Local environment with Lando &amp; Drupal, Now let's see how we set up the multisite with the lando.
                            And hope you are already aware of Drupal Multisite. If not, It is a feature of Drupal that allows you to run multiple Drupal installs off of a common codebase. This allows you to share themes and modules between a collectio</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jul 2021 14:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Multisite-Local-environment-setup-with-Lando-and-Drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Local-environment-setup-with-Lando-and-Drupal.html</link>
			<description>We developers always choose to have some tools or setup, which makes our lives easier during the development process whether it might be a local environment or higher environments. Not only will lives be easier with such a setup, even the productivity of the individual or team will be increased. And today we are gonna see how Lando will help the drupal developer or drupal development much more qui</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Local-environment-setup-with-Lando-and-Drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Security Hardening - Nginx Response Headers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Security-Hardening-Nginx-Response-Headers.html</link>
			<description>Now-a-days, web based attacks are one of the most common types of cybercrime, and in most cases, the attacked protocol is the HTTP, while the component that receives the attacks is the web server. Hardening Nginx HTTP headers becomes necessary for reducing any attacks to the web server.
                                And how to harden Nginx response HTTP headers? - HTTP headers are pieces of info</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Jun 2021 11:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Security-Hardening-Nginx-Response-Headers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal 7 to Drupal 8/9 Audits</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Drupal--to-DrupalAudits.html</link>
			<description>Migration from Drupal 7 to Drupal 8/9 is more of a re-build than a simple upgrade. We can move the content. users and other configuration with the help of core system, But still their will be a need to re-write custom modules or themes and some times contrib ones as well. By having a list which helps us to Audit any D7 Project to Drupal 8/9 migration would help start quick.
                       </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Drupal--to-DrupalAudits.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal JSON API, Deep Dive - Part 2</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-deep-dive-part-two.html</link>
			<description>In Part 2, Let's see about the Core concepts like Types, URL structure, HTTP methods, Request headers, Response codes and Document structure i.e Data in the request body. JSON:API module will provide the APIs for Drupal entity types and bundles, where every bundle will have its own unique url path, which will have a shared pattern.
                                Types
                            </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-deep-dive-part-two.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Monitoring Web Application with ELK Stack</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Monitoring-Web-Application-with-ELK-Stack.html</link>
			<description>For Auditing &amp; Troubleshooting issues in an application, log data is very useful. And to make it easy to read the log data via some kind of tool will make developers &amp; maintainers happy. However, not all the log data for any event is not needed to be stored in the log record. Means, Each log record should have only the information needed for further notice or further debugging. Strictly all sensit</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 19 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Monitoring-Web-Application-with-ELK-Stack.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal JSON API, Deep Dive - Part 1</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-deep-dive-part-one.html</link>
			<description>JSON:API module is implemented based on JSON:API Specification. Means, a specification that says how client should request the resources to be fetched or modified, &amp; also how server should respond to such requests. This JSON:API is designed to minimize the number of requests and also minimize the amount of data transmitted between clients &amp; servers. And such efficiency is achieved without compromi</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-deep-dive-part-one.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Send Mail with Custom Email Template &amp; with Dynamic values via Drupal Mail Service</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Send-Mail-with-Custom-Email-Template-and-with-Dynamic-values-via-Drupal-Mail-Service.html</link>
			<description>Sending an email works with defining an email template (subject, text and possibly email headers) and the replacement values to use in the appropriate places in the template. Processed email templates are requested from hook_mail() from the module sending the email. Any module can modify the composed email message array using hook_mail_alter(). Finally \Drupal::service('plugin.manager.mail')->mail</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Send-Mail-with-Custom-Email-Template-and-with-Dynamic-values-via-Drupal-Mail-Service.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>API Docs Drupal Module simple way to show OAS Docs on Drupal Portal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/API-Docs-Drupal-Module-simple-way-to-show-OAS-API-Docs-on-Drupal-Portal.html</link>
			<description>If you want to show API Documents on your Drupal Portal and you want to do it do it quickly, Here's the module API Docs which solves your purpose. API Docs is a simple module which will will provide a content type for the API Doc and User will be able to create API Documents by just uploading Open API Spec. Each API Doc is a content with this API Docs module.
                                Prereq</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/API-Docs-Drupal-Module-simple-way-to-show-OAS-API-Docs-on-Drupal-Portal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal JSON:API GET, POST, PATCH and DELETE Samples</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-get-post-patch-and-delete-samples.html</link>
			<description>The API that the JSON:API module makes available is centered on Drupal's entity types and bundles. Every bundle receives its own, unique URL path, which all follow a shared pattern
                                HTTP Methods
                                JSON:API specifies what HTTP Methods to accept. Those are: GET, POST, PATCH, and DELETE. Notably, PUT is not included.
                       </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2019 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-get-post-patch-and-delete-samples.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cache Set, Get and Invalidate per User in Drupal 7</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cache-set-get-and-invalidate-user-drupal-.html</link>
			<description>How to Set, Get and Invalidate the caches per user in Drupal 7, this blog article will explain a brief of how to do such implementation on Drupal using the default drupal cache functions.
                                Here, we go with the steps
                                
                                    Initially, create the custom functions for Get, Set and Invalidate the caches per us</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Jun 2019 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cache-set-get-and-invalidate-user-drupal-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Store Drupal logs on Amazon S3</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-drupal-logs-amazon-s.html</link>
			<description>Store Drupal logs on Amazon S3 via hook_watchdog, so that you can get rid of heavy logs on your drupal database and can later read from the S3.
                                For this todo on Drupal
                                
                                    You should use the "hook_watchdog" hook, where this hook allows modules to route log events to custom destinations.
               </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2019 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-drupal-logs-amazon-s.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Sites Still Vulnerable to Drupalgeddon 2</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sites-still-vulnerable-drupalgeddon-.html</link>
			<description>Attackers are exploiting Drupalgeddon 2 critical vulnerability in Drupal to compromise systems &amp; secretly turn them into malicious cryptocurrency mining machines like cryptojacking malware, mine for Monero.
                                The only side effects a victim might notice is that their system is running slower or doing more work than usual.
                                Still most of t</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2018 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sites-still-vulnerable-drupalgeddon-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Secure Website running on Apache with Let's Encrypt on Linux</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-website-running-apache-lets-encrypt-linux.html</link>
			<description>Website security is generally most complicated and expensive task for every Linux admin. Let's Encrypt is a free, automated, and open certificate authority that provides free X.509 certificates for Transport Layer Security encryption via an automated process. It's very complex process to install and add SSL certificate to a web server.
                                Let's make it easier with the </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2018 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-website-running-apache-lets-encrypt-linux.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Aegir on Docker - Develop, Test, With Easier Deployment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aegir-docker-develop-test-easier-deployment.html</link>
			<description>Aegir with Docker would be one of the brilliant option for Better Drupal Development and Faster Deployments.
                                Docker, which solves the overhead of virtualization layer. And Aegir, which gives the best possible approach for Drupal Multisite hosting.
                                Here you go???
                                Better Task Queue..! This process is usua</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2017 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aegir-docker-develop-test-easier-deployment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Integrating Codeception with Drupal to have added support for TDD</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/integrating-codeception-drupal-have-added-support-tdd.html</link>
			<description>Getting Codeception into Drupal, will have added support for Test Driven Development.. Specifically in having the Acceptance Tests in the project.. Since Test Driven Development would be one the most integral part of the project.. And also internal team and vendor team would be having more confidence in the version releases of their project.. one can prefer TDD.
                                Tes</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Mar 2017 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/integrating-codeception-drupal-have-added-support-tdd.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Creating a Twitter Share block programmatically in Drupal 8</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/creating-twitter-share-block-programmatically-drupal-.html</link>
			<description>How to Create a Twitter Share block programmatically in Drupal 8. Which includes few minor stuff like
                                
                                    Accessing the Current Node data in Block.
                                    How do we create the link programmatically.
                                    Disable cache for particular block.
                                
  </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Mar 2017 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/creating-twitter-share-block-programmatically-drupal-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Auto Tagging of Taxonomy terms in Drupal7</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/auto-tagging-taxonomy-terms-drupal.html</link>
			<description>This article help you to create the way to implement the autotagging of the taxonomy terms based on the other field of the node page. This can be implemented by using the hook_node_presave().
                                In our case lets consider the field_tags is the taxonomy field, and we are autotagging based on the content present in title and body fields.
                                Al</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2015 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/auto-tagging-taxonomy-terms-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Configuring &amp; Debugging Drupal 7 on PHPStorm with XDebug on Ubuntu14</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuring-debugging-drupal--phpstorm-xdebug-ubuntu.html</link>
			<description>Debugging the code is one of the important process for a developer, So now this article will help you to configure the Phpstorm for debugging the Drupal 7 application with the help of xDebug.
                                The configuration made in this article refers specifically to the Ubuntu machine, which has Apache2 webserver running and xDebug installed.
                                Init</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 17:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuring-debugging-drupal--phpstorm-xdebug-ubuntu.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Custom Batch processing in Drupal 7 to update Nodes - Batch API</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/custom-batch-processing-drupal--update-nodes-batch-api.html</link>
			<description>Drupal's batch API processing is very nice and provides few benifits, We can break long tasks into smaller batches, and by this we will be able to prevent maximum execution time errors.
This article will show how to Build a batch routine in a custom module, its more straight forward approach, you can follow up below code, which is been explained with required comments.
Create your custom module, w</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Aug 2015 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/custom-batch-processing-drupal--update-nodes-batch-api.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal7 Simple Test case in Custom Module</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-simple-test-case-custom-module.html</link>
			<description>Why to write test case? Very simple, in one word, Its waste of time and effort of checking something we changed in code and that effects other part, and to make sure every time what change we make that should not effect any other code, so this task can be done by our test cases
                                In this article, giving a simple test example to create a drupal test case
              </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-simple-test-case-custom-module.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Filter content between Date ranges in Drupal 7</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/filter-content-between-date-ranges-drupal.html</link>
			<description>It is tempting to believe that using the is between on a date fields will work. However, this option is used only in the case of events Starting on a range of date.
                                This tutorial requires that you already have a content type with a date field . It is not necessary to have two fields to adjust an 'end date' for the event, only a date field with the 'Collect an end da</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/filter-content-between-date-ranges-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create Related Content of Different Content Types through Taxonomy in Drupal7</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-related-content-different-content-types-through-taxonomy-drupal.html</link>
			<description>Step 1 Create a Taxonomy term field for the content type, In this article lets take example for Basic Page content type as shown in the below image. with the Autocomplete selected as settings of the term reference field.
                                
                                Step 2 And next create/resue the Taxonomy term field for the other content type, In this article lets take example</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 11 Jul 2015 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-related-content-different-content-types-through-taxonomy-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal Multisite development environment Configuration in Ubuntu14</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-multisite-development-environment-configuration-ubuntu.html</link>
			<description>Prerequisite Requires a working drupal installation
                                Set up your hosts file Add the following lines to /etc/hosts:
                                127.0.0.1    testsite.localhost
127.0.0.1    testsite2.localhost
Set up Virtual Hosts
                                Add the following code to /etc/apache2/sites-available:
                                Goto to the fold</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 Mar 2021 10:45:07 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-multisite-development-environment-configuration-ubuntu.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>