<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Environment - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/environment.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>What percentage of Indians are vegetarian?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</link>
			<description>Approximately 30-40% of the population in India is estimated to follow a vegetarian diet. However, this percentage can vary depending on the region, cultural practices and religious beliefs.  Why Indians Follow Vegetarianism:   Religious Beliefs:   Hinduism: Many Hindus follow a vegetarian diet as part of their religious beliefs, which promote compassion and non-violence (ahimsa). They believe in </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to make a compost without worm/kitchen composting/organic composting</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</link>
			<description>Composting is a great way to reduce waste and create nutrient-rich soil for your garden. While worm composting and kitchen composting are popular methods, there are other ways to make compost without using worms or organic kitchen waste. Here are some options:   Leaf Composting: Fallen leaves are an excellent source of carbon and can be used to create a nutrient-rich compost. Simply pile up the le</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Checklist for building an Eco-Friendly Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</link>
			<description>To build a home, which makes low-impact environmentally. And built using materials &amp;amp; technology that lowers its energy needs in future. And also make sure built home is reliable for few decades with minimal energy spent on it.  To do this, you have to consider Energy? what Sustainable materials to be used? how it impacts on our health? And what is costs  Before getting into the details of each</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cooking Food with Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
			<description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why to have a Green roof or Eco friendly roof on a building</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-to-have-a-green-roof-or-eco-friendly-roof-on-a-building.html</link>
			<description>A roof of a building that is partially or completely covered with vegetation, that is planted over a waterproofing membrane. It may also include additional layers such as a root barrier and drainage and irrigation systems. Rooftop ponds are another form of green roofs which are used to treat greywater.                                Vegetation, soil, drainage layer, roof barrier and irrigation sys</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 26 Aug 2023 16:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-to-have-a-green-roof-or-eco-friendly-roof-on-a-building.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rainwater Collection, Storage &amp; Purification</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rain-water-collection-storage-purification.html</link>
			<description>Rainwater Harvesting is the collection &amp; storage of rain water, rather than allowing it to run off. Rainwater is collected from a roof-like surface and redirected to a tank, cistern, deep pit (well, shaft, or borehole), aquifer, or a reservoir with percolation. We can utilize this water for many purposes like, include watering gardens, livestock, irrigation, domestic use with proper treatment and </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rain-water-collection-storage-purification.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Construction materials for Thermal Resistance Walls, Earth Bricks</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/construction-materials-for-thermal-resistant-walls.html</link>
			<description>Construction process can be tedious, time consuming and expensive. To overcome this during construction, varied methods of construction is being considered and developed. Also, materials and equipment used for construction are also being fabricated to enhance the quality of construction and furthermore minimize the time and cost. Interlocking bricks are one such advancement in construction industr</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 18:59:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/construction-materials-for-thermal-resistant-walls.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>