<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Experiment - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/experiment.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Marshmallow catapult, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marshmallow-catapult-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Marshmallow Catapult - Exploring Projectile Motion Experiment  Objective: To build and test a marshmallow catapult, exploring principles of force, motion, and projectile trajectory.  Materials:   Popsicle sticks or craft sticks Rubber bands Plastic spoon Small marshmallows or soft projectiles Tape Optional: Decorative materials (markers, stickers) for customization   Procedure:   Begin by d</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marshmallow-catapult-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Sticky ice, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sticky-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Sticky Ice - Exploring Surface Tension Experiment  Objective: To investigate surface tension by creating &amp;quot;sticky&amp;quot; ice cubes that can cling to various surfaces.  Materials:   Ice cube tray Water Salt String or thread Various surfaces to test (e.g., plastic, glass, metal, fabric) Optional: Food coloring for visual effect   Procedure:   Fill the ice cube tray with water, leaving some</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sticky-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Paper bridge, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/paper-bridge-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Paper Bridge - Engineering and Structural Strength Experiment  Objective: To design and build a paper bridge that can support the weight of objects and explore the concept of structural strength.  Materials:   Sheets of paper (construction paper or printer paper) Scissors Rulers Books or other small objects to serve as weights Optional: Tape or glue (to reinforce the bridge)   Procedure:   </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/paper-bridge-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Color changing invisible ink, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-changing-invisible-ink-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Color-Changing Invisible Ink - Chemical Reaction Experiment  Objective: To create and reveal color-changing invisible ink using a simple chemical reaction.  Materials:   Lemon juice or white vinegar Water White paper or a blank sheet of paper Cotton swabs or small paintbrushes Heat source (hairdryer or iron) Optional: Food coloring for additional color effects   Procedure:   Create the invi</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-changing-invisible-ink-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Make a compass, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/make-a-compass-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Make Your Own Compass - Magnetism Experiment  Objective: To create a simple compass and explore the principles of magnetism.  Materials:   Small, lightweight magnet (e.g., a bar magnet or a refrigerator magnet) Cork or a small piece of Styrofoam Small bowl or dish filled with water Sewing needle (must be made of steel, not stainless steel) Optional: Tape or glue (to secure the magnet to the</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 17:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/make-a-compass-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Elephant toothpaste, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/elephant-toothpaste-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Elephant Toothpaste - Chemical Reaction Experiment  Objective: To demonstrate an exothermic chemical reaction by creating a foamy eruption known as &amp;quot;elephant toothpaste.&amp;quot;  Materials:   1/2 cup hydrogen peroxide (6% or higher concentration) Dish soap (liquid) Dry yeast Warm water Empty plastic soda bottle (16-ounce or larger) Funnel Safety goggles Tray or large container (to catch </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/elephant-toothpaste-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Milk bottle xylophone, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/milk-bottle-xylophone-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Milk Bottle Xylophone - Sound and Pitch Experiment  Objective: To explore sound and pitch by creating a milk bottle xylophone.  Materials:   Empty glass milk bottles (varying sizes) Water Wooden sticks or metal spoons (for striking the bottles) Optional: Food coloring or colored tape (for visual effect)   Procedure:   Gather a set of empty glass milk bottles. You can use bottles of differen</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/milk-bottle-xylophone-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Floating fish, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Floating Fish - Density and Buoyancy Experiment  Objective: To explore the concepts of density and buoyancy by creating a floating fish.  Materials:   Clay or playdough Plasticine or modeling clay Plastic toy fish or small plastic object A basin, tub, or container filled with water   Procedure:   Start by shaping the plasticine or modeling clay into a small ball or disc shape. This will ser</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Craft stick chain reaction, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/craft-stick-chain-reaction-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Craft Stick Chain Reaction - Potential and Kinetic Energy Experiment  Objective: To explore potential and kinetic energy by creating a chain reaction using craft sticks.  Materials:   Craft sticks (popsicle sticks) Small binder clips or clothespins Optional: Decorative materials (markers, stickers, paint) for customization A wide, flat surface for the experiment (e.g., table, floor)   Proce</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/craft-stick-chain-reaction-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Grow an avocado tree, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-an-avocado-tree-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Grow an Avocado Tree - Seed Germination Experiment  Objective: To explore the process of seed germination and observe the growth of an avocado tree.  Materials:   An avocado pit (seed) Toothpicks Glass or jar Water Optional: Notebook or journal for recording observations and measurements   Procedure:   Carefully remove the pit (seed) from a ripe avocado. Rinse off any remaining fruit flesh </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 18:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-an-avocado-tree-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Watch the Water Rise, Kids Science Experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/watch-the-water-rise-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Watch the Water Rise - Absorption Experiment  Objective: To demonstrate the concept of absorption and observe how different materials absorb water.  Materials:   Clear cups or containers Water Various absorbent materials (e.g., paper towels, sponges, cotton balls, fabric scraps, tissue paper) Optional: Food coloring, markers, or colored paper for visual effect   Procedure:   Set up a worksp</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/watch-the-water-rise-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Amplify a Smartphone, Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/amplify-a-smartphone-science-experiment-for-kids.html</link>
			<description>Amplifying the sound of a smartphone can indeed be turned into a science experiment, allowing kids to explore the principles of acoustics and sound amplification. Here&amp;#39;s a simple science experiment idea:  Title: Investigating Sound Amplification with Everyday Materials  Objective: To explore different materials and their effects on amplifying the sound of a smartphone.  Materials:   Smartphone</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/amplify-a-smartphone-science-experiment-for-kids.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a Mini Baking Soda Rocket?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-mini-baking-soda-rocket.html</link>
			<description>Creating a mini baking soda rocket can be a fun and educational experiment. Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide to making one:  Materials you will need:   A film canister with a tight-fitting lid Baking soda (sodium bicarbonate) Vinegar Tissue or toilet paper Safety goggles (optional but recommended for eye protection)                      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});        Instructio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-mini-baking-soda-rocket.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>