<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Experiment - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/experiment.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Floating fish, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Floating Fish - Density and Buoyancy Experiment  Objective: To explore the concepts of density and buoyancy by creating a floating fish.  Materials:   Clay or playdough Plasticine or modeling clay Plastic toy fish or small plastic object A basin, tub, or container filled with water   Procedure:   Start by shaping the plasticine or modeling clay into a small ball or disc shape. This will ser</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Craft stick chain reaction, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/craft-stick-chain-reaction-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Craft Stick Chain Reaction - Potential and Kinetic Energy Experiment  Objective: To explore potential and kinetic energy by creating a chain reaction using craft sticks.  Materials:   Craft sticks (popsicle sticks) Small binder clips or clothespins Optional: Decorative materials (markers, stickers, paint) for customization A wide, flat surface for the experiment (e.g., table, floor)   Proce</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/craft-stick-chain-reaction-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Grow an avocado tree, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-an-avocado-tree-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Grow an Avocado Tree - Seed Germination Experiment  Objective: To explore the process of seed germination and observe the growth of an avocado tree.  Materials:   An avocado pit (seed) Toothpicks Glass or jar Water Optional: Notebook or journal for recording observations and measurements   Procedure:   Carefully remove the pit (seed) from a ripe avocado. Rinse off any remaining fruit flesh </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 18:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-an-avocado-tree-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Watch the Water Rise, Kids Science Experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/watch-the-water-rise-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Watch the Water Rise - Absorption Experiment  Objective: To demonstrate the concept of absorption and observe how different materials absorb water.  Materials:   Clear cups or containers Water Various absorbent materials (e.g., paper towels, sponges, cotton balls, fabric scraps, tissue paper) Optional: Food coloring, markers, or colored paper for visual effect   Procedure:   Set up a worksp</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/watch-the-water-rise-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Amplify a Smartphone, Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/amplify-a-smartphone-science-experiment-for-kids.html</link>
			<description>Amplifying the sound of a smartphone can indeed be turned into a science experiment, allowing kids to explore the principles of acoustics and sound amplification. Here&amp;#39;s a simple science experiment idea:  Title: Investigating Sound Amplification with Everyday Materials  Objective: To explore different materials and their effects on amplifying the sound of a smartphone.  Materials:   Smartphone</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/amplify-a-smartphone-science-experiment-for-kids.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a Mini Baking Soda Rocket?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-mini-baking-soda-rocket.html</link>
			<description>Creating a mini baking soda rocket can be a fun and educational experiment. Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide to making one:  Materials you will need:   A film canister with a tight-fitting lid Baking soda (sodium bicarbonate) Vinegar Tissue or toilet paper Safety goggles (optional but recommended for eye protection)                      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});        Instructio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-mini-baking-soda-rocket.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>