<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Family - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/family.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>What are some of the most messed up family secrets?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-of-the-most-messed-up-family-secrets.html</link>
			<description>Family secrets can range from the benign to the deeply troubling. While some secrets are relatively harmless, others can have profound and lasting impacts on family members.  Here are some examples of deeply troubling family secrets, often considered among the most &amp;quot;messed up&amp;quot;:  1. Hidden Abuse:   When physical, emotional, or sexual abuse is hidden within a family, it creates a toxic env</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Aug 2024 19:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-of-the-most-messed-up-family-secrets.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Optimal placement of solar panels for better observation of solar energy</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimal-placement-of-solar-panels-for-better-observation-of-solar-energy.html</link>
			<description>Optimal panel placement is crucial for maximizing energy production from your solar panel system. Here are some key considerations:   Orientation: In the Northern Hemisphere, panels should face true south to capture the maximum amount of sunlight throughout the day. In the Southern Hemisphere, panels should face true north. Tilt Angle: The tilt angle of the panels should be approximately equal to </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimal-placement-of-solar-panels-for-better-observation-of-solar-energy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Choose the Inverters which are more efficient to work with Solar panels?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/choose-the-inverters-which-are-more-efficient-to-work-with-solar-panels.html</link>
			<description>Selecting an efficient inverter is crucial for maximizing the energy production of your solar panel system.  Here are key considerations for choosing an efficient solar inverter:   Type of Inverter:   String Inverters: These are connected to multiple solar panels in a series. They are cost-effective but the performance of the whole string can be affected if one panel is shaded or underperforming. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/choose-the-inverters-which-are-more-efficient-to-work-with-solar-panels.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to choose solar panels which are more efficient?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-choose-solar-panels-which-are-more-efficient.html</link>
			<description>Choosing efficient solar panels is crucial for maximizing the energy production of your solar system.  Here are some key factors to consider when selecting high-efficiency solar panels:   Conversion Efficiency:   Look for panels with a high conversion efficiency. This indicates the percentage of sunlight that the panel can convert into electricity. Higher efficiency panels will generate more power</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 13:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-choose-solar-panels-which-are-more-efficient.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Technical information to know about the Solar energy setup for your home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/technical-information-to-know-about-the-solar-energy-setup-for-your-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a solar power system for your home is a sustainable and environmentally-friendly way to generate electricity  Here are some key technical details to understand when setting up a solar energy system for your home:   Solar Panels (Photovoltaic Modules):   Capacity (Wattage): The power output of each panel, typically ranging from 250 to 400 watts. Efficiency: The percentage of sunlight tha</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/technical-information-to-know-about-the-solar-energy-setup-for-your-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to setup solar power for you home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-setup-solar-power-for-you-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a solar power system for a family of four in India involves several steps. Please note that the costs provided are approximate and can vary based on factors like location, system size, quality of components and labor costs.  Additionally, government incentives and rebates can affect the final cost.  Step-by-Step Guide:  Step 1: Assess Your Energy Needs   Determine Your Energy Consumptio</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-setup-solar-power-for-you-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kukke-subramanya-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Planning a trip from Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya? That&amp;#39;s a great choice! One day trip or Two day trip from Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in Kukke Subramanya.  Kukke Subramanya is a popular pilgrimage destination in Karnataka known for its ancient templ</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kukke-subramanya-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Brown rice vs White rice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/brown-rice-vs-white-rice.html</link>
			<description>Brown rice and white rice are two different types of rice that undergo varying levels of processing.  Here are some key differences between brown rice and white rice:   Processing: Brown rice is the whole grain rice that retains its bran, germ and endosperm layers, while white rice has had its bran and germ removed, leaving only the endosperm. Nutritional Content: Brown rice is considered more nut</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/brown-rice-vs-white-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to make a compost without worm/kitchen composting/organic composting</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</link>
			<description>Composting is a great way to reduce waste and create nutrient-rich soil for your garden. While worm composting and kitchen composting are popular methods, there are other ways to make compost without using worms or organic kitchen waste. Here are some options:   Leaf Composting: Fallen leaves are an excellent source of carbon and can be used to create a nutrient-rich compost. Simply pile up the le</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Eight vegetables that can be grown at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see eight vegetables that you can grow at your home easily. Chili pepper, Tomato, Garlic, Peas, Raddish, Cabbage, Cauliflower and Carrot are the few vegetables that you can grow at home with less effort.  1. Chili pepper  Chili pepper can be easily grown from seeds, so we need to buy good seeds for better results. Sprinkle seeds over the soil surface, then cover with a</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Onions to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Onions are easy to grow, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. They need less attention during the growth when compared to other plants.  Onions will be having flavonoids, which have both an antioxidant and anti-inflammatory effect. By eating them regularly in sufficient quantities, these components will help people to protect themselves from chronic conditions such as ca</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Complete Guide to Setup and Usage Solar Panels at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Going green is the best of the environment and if you are planning to go green, then we all know Sun is the non-renewable energy and we could use this energy for people&amp;#39;s survival. We have a few articles at PeoplesBLOG related to the Environment and going green, have a check of them.  Using the Electricity from Solar energy is one of the best combinations, because there is not much waste out o</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Tomatoes to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see how they can grow tomatoes at their home and with the help of just other tomatoes at home. We have a few other articles which help to grow vegetables at home, you can read them from here.  Generally tomatoes are used in the kitchen for almost all the curries in South Indian dishes.  Tomatoes are rich in Vitamin B9, Vitamin C and Potassium and these Antioxidants pro</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Pudina to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Pudina is easy to grow and hard to kill, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. It&amp;#39;s especially known for its soothing effect on the stomach.  Pudina is a fast growing plant, it&amp;#39;s good to keep it in a pot or a container with some boundary, so that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take up all your garden or yard.  If people buy Pudina from a market or get Punida from a neighbor&amp;#39</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Broccoli to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Broccoli is worth growing for its nutritional content value. This is rich in Vitamins and Minerals and is a good source of Vitamin A, Potassium, Folic acid, Iron and Fiber.  Broccoli is a cool seasonal crop, so it should be started in early winters. September and October are the best months for seed germination.  Germination Process?   You can start seeds in almost any type of container as long as</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Saving Vegetable seeds for your backyard gardening</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/saving-vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</link>
			<description>To become more food self-sufficient, we should plan to collect, store and use some of the seed for your own garden. With this we can create new &amp; custom varieties of vegetables that grow best in our backyard. This can be done with small amount of effort involved. Also you will have fun in the process too.                                You can save vegetable seeds from your garden produce to plant</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/saving-vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing Enough Food to Feed a Family Year-Round by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-food-to-feed-a-family.html</link>
			<description>It&amp;#39;s a great thought of growing enough food to feed your family year round by yourself. Certain things are really important for such a though, like how much food is needed for your family, which crops to plant, how to get the most from your plot and how to preserve your extra harvest.  How much food is needed?   Let&amp;#39;s say a 200 square feet plot will harvest the feeds for a single person al</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-food-to-feed-a-family.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>