<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Family - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Family.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Growing enough Pudina to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Pudina is easy to grow and hard to kill, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. It&amp;#39;s especially known for its soothing effect on the stomach.  Pudina is a fast growing plant, it&amp;#39;s good to keep it in a pot or a container with some boundary, so that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take up all your garden or yard.  If people buy Pudina from a market or get Punida from a neighbor&amp;#39</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 11:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Broccoli to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Broccoli is worth growing for its nutritional content value. This is rich in Vitamins and Minerals and is a good source of Vitamin A, Potassium, Folic acid, Iron and Fiber.  Broccoli is a cool seasonal crop, so it should be started in early winters. September and October are the best months for seed germination.  Germination Process?   You can start seeds in almost any type of container as long as</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Saving Vegetable seeds for your backyard gardening</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Saving-Vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</link>
			<description>To become more food self-sufficient, we should plan to collect, store and use some of the seed for your own garden. With this we can create new &amp; custom varieties of vegetables that grow best in our backyard. This can be done with small amount of effort involved. Also you will have fun in the process too.
                                You can save vegetable seeds from your garden produce to plan</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Saving-Vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing Enough Food to Feed a Family Year-Round by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Growing-Enough-Food-to-Feed-a-Family.html</link>
			<description>It's a great thought of growing enough food to feed your family year round by yourself. Certain things are really important for such a though, like how much food is needed for your family, which crops to plant, how to get the most from your plot, and how to preserve your extra harvest.
                                How much food is needed?
                                Let's say a 200 square f</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 11:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Growing-Enough-Food-to-Feed-a-Family.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>