<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Food - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/food.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Samosas - Snack from the Indian subcontinent</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/samosas-snack-from-the-indian-subcontinent.html</link>
			<description>Samosas are a popular savory snack originating from the Indian subcontinent. They are triangular-shaped pastries filled with a savory mixture of spiced potatoes, peas, and sometimes other ingredients.  Here&amp;#39;s how samosas are typically cooked, along with some background information:  What Are Samosas?   	Ingredients: The outer pastry shell of samosas is typically made from all-purpose flour, wa</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/samosas-snack-from-the-indian-subcontinent.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What percentage of Indians are vegetarian?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</link>
			<description>Approximately 30-40% of the population in India is estimated to follow a vegetarian diet. However, this percentage can vary depending on the region, cultural practices, and religious beliefs.  Why Indians Follow Vegetarianism:   Religious Beliefs:   Hinduism: Many Hindus follow a vegetarian diet as part of their religious beliefs, which promote compassion and non-violence (ahimsa). They believe in</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What is the most expensive spice in the world when listed by weight?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-the-most-expensive-spice-in-the-world-when-listed-by-weight.html</link>
			<description>The most expensive spice in the world, when listed by weight, is saffron. Saffron is derived from the stigma (the female reproductive part) of the Crocus sativus flower. It is renowned for its distinct flavor, aroma, and vibrant color, which adds depth and complexity to dishes.  Saffron is used in various cuisines worldwide, particularly in dishes such as paella, risotto, and certain desserts.  Se</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-the-most-expensive-spice-in-the-world-when-listed-by-weight.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What will happen to the body if you eat dried fruits every day?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-will-happen-to-the-body-if-you-eat-dried-fruits-every-day.html</link>
			<description>Eating dried fruits every day can have both positive and potentially negative effects on the body, depending on various factors such as the type and quantity of dried fruits consumed, an individual&amp;#39;s overall diet, and their health status.  Here are some considerations:  Positive Effects:   Nutrient Intake: Dried fruits are concentrated sources of nutrients, including vitamins, minerals, and fi</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 08:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-will-happen-to-the-body-if-you-eat-dried-fruits-every-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are recommended servings of fruits and vegetables?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-recommended-servings-of-fruits-and-vegetables.html</link>
			<description>The recommended servings of fruits and vegetables can vary slightly based on factors such as age, sex, and activity level. However, general guidelines provide a useful framework for individuals to ensure they&amp;#39;re incorporating enough fruits and vegetables into their diet.  According to dietary guidelines, a common recommendation for adults is to aim for:   Fruits:   Quantity: 1.5 to 2 cups per </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-recommended-servings-of-fruits-and-vegetables.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How much fruit intake is too much for a person?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-much-fruit-intake-is-too-much-for-a-person.html</link>
			<description>The recommended intake of fruit can vary based on factors such as age, sex, activity level, and overall health. However, general dietary guidelines suggest that adults should aim for 1.5 to 2 cups of fruit per day. This can include whole fruits, such as apples, bananas, berries, etc., or 100% fruit juice.  Here are some considerations regarding fruit intake:   Balanced Diet: It&amp;#39;s important to </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-much-fruit-intake-is-too-much-for-a-person.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best food to have for better bowel movement</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-food-to-have-for-better-bowel-movement.html</link>
			<description>Maintaining good bowel movements is essential for overall digestive health.  Here are some foods that can promote healthy bowel movements:   Fiber-Rich Foods:   Whole Grains: Brown rice, quinoa, oats, and whole wheat. Legumes: Beans, lentils, and chickpeas. Fruits: Berries, apples, pears, prunes, and kiwi. Vegetables: Broccoli, carrots, sweet potatoes, and leafy greens.   Prunes (Dried Plums): Pru</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 11:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-food-to-have-for-better-bowel-movement.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Which fruits are having amazing health benefits?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/which-fruits-are-having-amazing-health-benefits.html</link>
			<description>Many fruits offer a wide range of health benefits due to their rich nutrient content, antioxidants, and other bioactive compounds.  Here are some fruits known for their amazing health benefits:  Blueberries:   Rich in antioxidants, particularly anthocyanins. May improve cognitive function and have anti-inflammatory effects.   Strawberries:   High in vitamin C, manganese, and antioxidants. May have</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/which-fruits-are-having-amazing-health-benefits.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Health benefits of bananas and why people need to consume them?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/health-benefits-of-bananas-and-why-people-need-to-consume-them.html</link>
			<description>Bananas are a popular and nutritious fruit that offer a range of health benefits.  Here are some reasons why people should consider including bananas in their diet:   Rich in Nutrients: Bananas are a good source of several essential nutrients, including potassium, vitamin C, vitamin B6, and dietary fiber. High in Potassium: Potassium is a crucial mineral for maintaining proper heart and muscle fun</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/health-benefits-of-bananas-and-why-people-need-to-consume-them.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Nutrient foods which people need to have daily</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/nutrient-foods-which-people-need-to-have-daily.html</link>
			<description>Eating a variety of nutrient-dense foods is essential for maintaining good health.  Here is a list of nutrient-rich foods that people should consider including in their daily diet:  Vegetables:   Leafy greens (spinach, kale, collard greens) Cruciferous vegetables (broccoli, Brussels sprouts, cauliflower) Carrots Bell peppers Sweet potatoes   Fruits:   Berries (blueberries, strawberries, raspberrie</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/nutrient-foods-which-people-need-to-have-daily.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cabbage fried rice recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cabbage-fried-rice-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for preparing Cabbage Fried Rice at home:  Ingredients:   2 cups cooked basmati rice (preferably leftover and cooled) 1 cup finely shredded cabbage 1/2 cup carrots, finely chopped 1/2 cup green peas 1/2 cup onions, finely chopped 2-3 green chilies, finely chopped 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 2 tablespoons soy sauce 1 tablespoon chili sauce (adjust to taste) 1/2 teasp</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cabbage-fried-rice-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Carrot Fried Rice Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/carrot-fried-rice-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for Carrot Fried Rice in Andhra style:  Ingredients:   2 cups cooked basmati rice (preferably leftover and cooled) 1 cup carrots, finely chopped 1/2 cup green peas 1/2 cup onions, finely chopped 2-3 green chilies, finely chopped 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 2 tablespoons oil 1/2 teaspoon mustard seeds     (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    1/2 teas</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/carrot-fried-rice-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is spinach called a superfood?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-spinach-called-a-superfood.html</link>
			<description>Spinach is a nutrient-rich leafy green vegetable that offers a wide range of health benefits. It&amp;#39;s a versatile and nutritious addition to various dishes and can be consumed cooked or raw.&amp;nbsp;  Here&amp;rsquo;s the nutritional composition of spinach per 100 grams of raw spinach:   Calories: 23 kcal Carbohydrates: 3.6 g  Dietary Fiber: 2.2 g Sugars: 0.4 g   Protein: 2.9 g Fat: 0.4 g  Saturated Fat</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-spinach-called-a-superfood.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg Biryani Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Egg Biryani in Andhra style:  Ingredients:  For the rice:   2 cups basmati rice 4 cups water 1 bay leaf 2 green cardamom pods 2 cloves Salt to taste   For the egg marinade:   6 boiled eggs, peeled and pricked with a fork 1/2 cup yogurt 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder 1/2 teaspoon garam masala powder Salt to taste    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What happens if people are having milk everyday?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happens-if-people-are-having-milk-everyday.html</link>
			<description>Consuming milk every day can have both positive and potential negative effects on health, depending on various factors such as individual tolerance, health conditions, and the quantity consumed.  Here&amp;#39;s a balanced overview of what can happen if people have milk every day:  Positive Effects:   Nutrient Intake: Milk is a rich source of essential nutrients such as calcium, vitamin D, vitamin B12,</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 09:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happens-if-people-are-having-milk-everyday.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vegetable Biryani Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vegetable-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Vegetable Biryani in Andhra style:  Ingredients:  For the rice:   2 cups basmati rice 4 cups water 1 bay leaf 2 green cardamom pods 2 cloves Salt to taste   For the vegetable mixture:   2 tablespoons oil or ghee 1 large onion, thinly sliced 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 1 cup mixed vegetables (such as carrots, peas, beans, cauliflower), c</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vegetable-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Jonna roti with chili chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jonna-roti-with-chili-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Jonna Roti (Sorghum Roti) with Chilli Chutney in Andhra style:  For Jonna Roti:  Ingredients:   2 cups jowar flour (sorghum flour) Water as needed Salt to taste Oil or ghee for cooking   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the jowar flour and salt. Gradually add water and knead the flour to form a soft and pliable dough. Add water as needed to achieve the right consis</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 09:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jonna-roti-with-chili-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ragi roti with tomato chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ragi-roti-with-tomato-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Ragi Roti with Tomato Chutney in Andhra style:  For Ragi Roti:  Ingredients:   1 cup ragi flour (finger millet flour) 1/4 cup finely chopped onions 1/4 cup grated carrots 2 green chilies, finely chopped 2 tablespoons chopped coriander leaves Salt to taste Water as needed Oil for cooking      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    Instructions:   In a mixing b</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ragi-roti-with-tomato-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Gongura Pappu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gongura-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Gongura Pappu, a popular Andhra-style lentil curry made with Gongura leaves (sorrel leaves):  Ingredients:   1 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 cups Gongura leaves, washed and chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 08:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gongura-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vankaya Pappu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vankaya-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Vankaya Pappu, an Andhra-style lentil and eggplant curry:  Ingredients:   1 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 small eggplants (brinjals), chopped into cubes 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon coriander powder </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vankaya-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pasta at home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pasta-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for making pasta at home:  Ingredients:   8 ounces (225 grams) dried pasta (such as spaghetti, penne, or fettuccine) Water for boiling Salt for seasoning Olive oil (optional)   Instructions:   Fill a large pot with water and bring it to a boil over high heat. Add a generous amount of salt to the boiling water. Once the water is boiling, add the pasta to the pot. Stir gen</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pasta-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pizza at home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pizza-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for homemade pizza:  For the Pizza Dough:  Ingredients:   2 &amp;frac12; cups all-purpose flour 2 &amp;frac14; teaspoons instant yeast 1 teaspoon sugar 1 teaspoon salt 1 cup warm water 2 tablespoons olive oil   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the flour, instant yeast, sugar, and salt. Gradually add the warm water while stirring the mixture. Knead the dough for about 5-7 minut</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pizza-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare paneer kulcha at home - Paneer Kulcha Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-paneer-kulcha-at-home-paneer-kulcha-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Paneer Kulcha, a popular Indian bread stuffed with paneer (Indian cottage cheese):  For the Kulcha Dough:  Ingredients:   2 cups all-purpose flour (maida) 1/2 teaspoon baking powder 1/2 teaspoon baking soda 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/2 cup plain yogurt 2 tablespoons oil Water as needed   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine all-purpose flour, baking powder, baking soda, and s</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-paneer-kulcha-at-home-paneer-kulcha-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare gobi manchurian at home - Gobi Manchurian Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-gobi-manchurian-at-home-gobi-manchurian-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Gobi Manchurian, a popular Indo-Chinese dish made with cauliflower:  Ingredients:  For the batter:   1 medium-sized cauliflower, cut into florets 1/2 cup all-purpose flour (maida) 1/4 cup cornstarch 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder 1/2 teaspoon soy sauce 1/2 teaspoon vinegar Salt to taste Water as needed Oil for deep frying   For the sauce:   1 t</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 10:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-gobi-manchurian-at-home-gobi-manchurian-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cook Onion Rava Dosa at home - Onion Rava Dosa Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-onion-rava-dosa-at-home-onion-rava-dosa-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Onion Rava Dosa, a popular South Indian crepe made with semolina (rava) and onions:  Ingredients:   1 cup semolina (rava) 1/2 cup rice flour 1/4 cup all-purpose flour (maida) 1 onion, finely chopped 2 green chilies, finely chopped 1/4 cup chopped coriander leaves 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon black pepper, coarsely crushed 1/2 teaspoon grated ginger Salt to taste Water </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-onion-rava-dosa-at-home-onion-rava-dosa-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cook Lemon Rice at home - Lemon Rice Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-lemon-rice-at-home-lemon-rice-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Lemon Rice, a tangy and flavorful rice dish:  Ingredients:   1 cup basmati rice (or any long-grain rice) 2 tablespoons oil 1 teaspoon mustard seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/4 cup peanuts 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 curry leaves 1/4 teaspoon turmeric powder Juice of 1 lemon Salt to taste Fresh coriander leaves for garnishing           </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-lemon-rice-at-home-lemon-rice-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Veg Kurma at Home - Veg Kurma Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-veg-kurma-at-home-veg-kurma-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Veg Kurma, a creamy and flavorful Indian dish made with mixed vegetables:  Ingredients:   2 cups mixed vegetables (carrots, beans, potatoes, peas, cauliflower, etc.), chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 cup grated coconut 1/4 cup cashew nuts 1 teaspoon fennel seeds 1 teaspoon cumin </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-veg-kurma-at-home-veg-kurma-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Bisi bele bhath at Home - Bisi bele bhath Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-bisi-bele-bhath-at-home-bisi-bele-bhath-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Bisi Bele Bhath, a flavorful and traditional dish from Karnataka, India:  Ingredients:  For the spice paste:   2 tablespoons chana dal (Bengal gram) 1 tablespoon urad dal (split black gram) 1 tablespoon coriander seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon fenugreek seeds 6-8 dried red chilies 1/2 teaspoon peppercorns 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder                      (adsbygoog</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-bisi-bele-bhath-at-home-bisi-bele-bhath-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cook Pongal at Home - Pongal Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Pongal, a popular South Indian dish made with rice and lentils:  Ingredients:   1 cup raw rice 1/4 cup split yellow moong dal (split yellow lentils) 4 cups water 2 tablespoons ghee (clarified butter) 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon whole black peppercorns 1 tablespoon grated ginger A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 cashew nuts 10-12 curry leaves Salt to taste            </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Cauliflower Peas Masala at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Cauliflower Peas Masala:  Ingredients:   1 small cauliflower, cut into florets 1 cup green peas 2 onions, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon coriander powder 1/2 teaspoon garam masala Salt to tast</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Sambar at Home - Sambar recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sambar-at-home-sambar-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Andhra-style vegetable sambar, a delicious South Indian dish made with lentils and mixed vegetables, Here&amp;#39;s the recipe:  Ingredients:   1/2 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 cups mixed vegetables (such as drumsticks, carrots, beans, brinjal, pumpkin, etc.), chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, chopped 2 tablespoons tamarind pulp 2 tablespoons sambar powder 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sambar-at-home-sambar-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Brown rice vs White rice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/brown-rice-vs-white-rice.html</link>
			<description>Brown rice and white rice are two different types of rice that undergo varying levels of processing.  Here are some key differences between brown rice and white rice:   Processing: Brown rice is the whole grain rice that retains its bran, germ, and endosperm layers, while white rice has had its bran and germ removed, leaving only the endosperm. Nutritional Content: Brown rice is considered more nu</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/brown-rice-vs-white-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Palak Paneer at Home - Palak Paneer Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Palak paneer is a popular North Indian dish made with spinach and paneer (Indian cheese).  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing palak paneer at home for serving four people:  Ingredients:   2 cups chopped spinach (palak) 200g paneer, cut into small cubes 1 medium-sized onion, chopped 2 medium-sized tomatoes, chopped 1 tbsp ginger-garlic paste 1 green chili, chopped                                    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Mango Pickle at Home - Mango Pickle Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Mango pickle is a popular Indian condiment made with raw mangoes and spices.  Mango pickle is a variety of pickles prepared using mango. It is very popular in South and Southeast Asia. The pickling process in India differs from other regions mainly due to an additional spice mixture added to them after anaerobic fermentation.  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing mango pickle at home:  Ingredients:  </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to make a compost without worm/kitchen composting/organic composting</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</link>
			<description>Composting is a great way to reduce waste and create nutrient-rich soil for your garden. While worm composting and kitchen composting are popular methods, there are other ways to make compost without using worms or organic kitchen waste. Here are some options:   Leaf Composting: Fallen leaves are an excellent source of carbon and can be used to create a nutrient-rich compost. Simply pile up the le</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian style Spanish omelette, Egg + Potato + Onion</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</link>
			<description>Egg with Potato plus Onion will make a delicious and healthy breakfast, You have have it as a Breakfast or you can have it as a Snack in the day, will also be a great starter in the barbecue. This combination of dish is called Spanish omelette, but lets make it in Indian Style.  Ingredients Needed?  3 Eggs, 4 medium sized Potato (chopped in small) &amp;amp; 4 medium sized Onion (chopped in small), 4-5</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg Stuffed Paratha Home made Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Egg Stuffed Paratha is a delicious and healthy Paratha dish, filled with egg mixture. Both the eggs and whole wheat are healthy as it provides the right amount of proteins and carbs. The egg mixture has finely chopped onions, green chili and coriander leaves. This is then slided into the half cooked paratha pockets and cooked further. The Egg Stuffed Parathas are quite filling in itself.  Ingredie</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Eight vegetables that can be grown at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see eight vegetables that you can grow at your home easily. Chili pepper, Tomato, Garlic, Peas, Raddish, Cabbage, Cauliflower and Carrot are the few vegetables that you can grow at home with less effort.  1. Chili pepper  Chili pepper can be easily grown from seeds, so we need to buy good seeds for better results. Sprinkle seeds over the soil surface, then cover with a</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Onions to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Onions are easy to grow, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. They need less attention during the growth when compared to other plants.  Onions will be having flavonoids, which have both an antioxidant and anti-inflammatory effect. By eating them regularly in sufficient quantities, these components will help people to protect themselves from chronic conditions such as ca</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Tomatoes to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see how they can grow tomatoes at their home and with the help of just other tomatoes at home. We have a few other articles which help to grow vegetables at home, you can read them from here.  Generally tomatoes are used in the kitchen for almost all the curries in South Indian dishes.  Tomatoes are rich in Vitamin B9, Vitamin C and Potassium and these Antioxidants pro</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cooking Food with Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
			<description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Pudina to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Pudina is easy to grow and hard to kill, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. It&amp;#39;s especially known for its soothing effect on the stomach.  Pudina is a fast growing plant, it&amp;#39;s good to keep it in a pot or a container with some boundary, so that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take up all your garden or yard.  If people buy Pudina from a market or get Punida from a neighbor&amp;#39</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Broccoli to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Broccoli is worth growing for its nutritional content value. This is rich in Vitamins and Minerals and is a good source of Vitamin A, Potassium, Folic acid, Iron and Fiber.  Broccoli is a cool seasonal crop, so it should be started in early winters. September and October are the best months for seed germination.  Germination Process?   You can start seeds in almost any type of container as long as</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pudina chutney Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Pudina Chutney is a flavorful condiment and aromatic chutney to serve with rice, mudde, idli, dosa. Pudina Chutney can also be served with snacks like bonda, bajji too.  People sometimes are confused pudina chutney with mint chutney or green chutney that is served along with chats and tandoori platter, but it&amp;#39;s not the same which we serve with rice or mudde or idle, and this chutney is more au</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
			<description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Chintakaya Pachadi Recipe, Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi chintakaya pachadi (Green raw tamarind pickle) is an age-old dish, which is generally eaten with Rice &amp; some also eaten with Ghee for even better taste. As we Indians love the tangy &amp; sweetish taste of pickle, this delicious Pachi chintakaya pachadi is enjoyed by all age groups and in fact, the recipe is one among the famous Indian dishes. This dish also has many health benefits</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Pulusu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi Pulusu Recipe is a thin rasam made with freshly extracted tamarind water and mixed with sliced onions and freshly cut coriander leaves. Comfort food at its best when served with some steamed rice for a simple meal.                                It is a different way of creating a rasam that has been followed by the people from Andhra Pradesh and Telangana. This rasam is not hea</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Raw Mango Chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Raw mango chutney is a flavorful condiment made with raw mangos, coriander leaves, onions and some spices. Raw Mango Chutney is a must-try recipe when raw mangoes are in season. Raw mangoes are packed with minerals and vitamins and are good to beat the summer heat.                                This raw mango chutney aids digestion and enhances the taste, aroma, and nutrition of any dish. We usua</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Oranges - Let us know how to peel off &amp; eat; along with its benefits</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/oranges-let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</link>
			<description>Ever heard of that name, it’s a fruit which helps us to boost our immunity levels and lowers the risk of diseases.                                In this lockdown time, one day I felt very tired, couldn’t continue my routine life, and coincidently, all my family members were affected with some or other illness like headache, cough, cold, backache and tiredness to do mundane things.            </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/oranges-let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Researchers solve riddle of plant immune system</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</link>
			<description>How do plants build resilience? An international research team led by the University of Gottingen studied the molecular mechanisms of the plant immune system. They were able to show a connection between a relatively unknown gene and resistance to pathogens. The results of the study were published in the journal The Plant Cell.                                Scientists from "PRoTECT" -- Plant Respo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>