<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Food - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Food.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Growing enough Pudina to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Pudina is easy to grow and hard to kill, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. It&amp;#39;s especially known for its soothing effect on the stomach.  Pudina is a fast growing plant, it&amp;#39;s good to keep it in a pot or a container with some boundary, so that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take up all your garden or yard.  If people buy Pudina from a market or get Punida from a neighbor&amp;#39</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 11:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Broccoli to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Broccoli is worth growing for its nutritional content value. This is rich in Vitamins and Minerals and is a good source of Vitamin A, Potassium, Folic acid, Iron and Fiber.  Broccoli is a cool seasonal crop, so it should be started in early winters. September and October are the best months for seed germination.  Germination Process?   You can start seeds in almost any type of container as long as</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pudina chutney Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Pudina Chutney is a flavorful condiment and aromatic chutney to serve with rice, mudde, idli, dosa. Pudina Chutney can also be served with snacks like bonda, bajji too.  People sometimes are confused pudina chutney with mint chutney or green chutney that is served along with chats and tandoori platter, but it&amp;#39;s not the same which we serve with rice or mudde or idle, and this chutney is more au</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 19:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
			<description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Chintakaya Pachadi Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Pachi-Chintakaya-Pachadi-Recipe-Andhra-Style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi chintakaya pachadi (Green raw tamarind pickle) is an age-old dish, which is generally eaten with Rice &amp; some also eaten with Ghee for even better taste. As we Indians love the tangy &amp; sweetish taste of pickle, this delicious Pachi chintakaya pachadi is enjoyed by all age groups and in fact, the recipe is one among the famous Indian dishes. This dish also has many health benefits</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jan 2022 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Pachi-Chintakaya-Pachadi-Recipe-Andhra-Style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Pulusu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Pachi-Pulusu-Recipe-Andhra-Style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi Pulusu Recipe is a thin rasam made with freshly extracted tamarind water and mixed with sliced onions and freshly cut coriander leaves. Comfort food at its best when served with some steamed rice for a simple meal.
                                It is a different way of creating a rasam that has been followed by the people from Andhra Pradesh and Telangana. This rasam is not he</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 13 Jun 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Pachi-Pulusu-Recipe-Andhra-Style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Raw Mango Chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Raw-Mango-Chutney-Andhra-Style.html</link>
			<description>Raw mango chutney is a flavorful condiment made with raw mangos, coriander leaves, onions and some spices. Raw Mango Chutney is a must-try recipe when raw mangoes are in season. Raw mangoes are packed with minerals and vitamins and are good to beat the summer heat.
                                This raw mango chutney aids digestion and enhances the taste, aroma, and nutrition of any dish. We usu</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Raw-Mango-Chutney-Andhra-Style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Oranges - Let us know how to peel off &amp; eat; along with its benefits</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Oranges-Let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</link>
			<description>Ever heard of that name, it’s a fruit which helps us to boost our immunity levels and lowers the risk of diseases.
                                In this lockdown time, one day I felt very tired, couldn’t continue my routine life, and coincidently, all my family members were affected with some or other illness like headache, cough, cold, backache and tiredness to do mundane things.
          </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 May 2021 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Oranges-Let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Researchers solve riddle of plant immune system</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</link>
			<description>How do plants build resilience? An international research team led by the University of Gottingen studied the molecular mechanisms of the plant immune system. They were able to show a connection between a relatively unknown gene and resistance to pathogens. The results of the study were published in the journal The Plant Cell.
                                Scientists from "PRoTECT" -- Plant Resp</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What to Eat &amp; What to Avoid, after a Tooth Extraction</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/What-to-Eat-and-What-to-Avoid-after-a-Tooth-Extraction.html</link>
			<description>Tooth extraction is a long chain of steps where you have to take care of the area of the extraction for weeks of extration steps. Means you need to take care of brushing and cleaning the area properly &amp; avoiding too much activity right after the extraction.
                                Since you have to consume food everyday, you can do by taking certain restrictions like what you can eat and w</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/What-to-Eat-and-What-to-Avoid-after-a-Tooth-Extraction.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Saving Vegetable seeds for your backyard gardening</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Saving-Vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</link>
			<description>To become more food self-sufficient, we should plan to collect, store and use some of the seed for your own garden. With this we can create new &amp; custom varieties of vegetables that grow best in our backyard. This can be done with small amount of effort involved. Also you will have fun in the process too.
                                You can save vegetable seeds from your garden produce to plan</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Saving-Vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Your Oral Health is Your Total Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Your-Oral-Health-is-Your-Total-Health.html</link>
			<description>We human beings, to live and survive consume food as a basic need. How many of us have thought that food we consume orally is keeping one's dental health in good condition.
                                Studies and researchers have proven that.. plaque and calculus in dental terminology which contains aerobic and anaerobic bacteria which accumulated and attached to teeth slowly discharge and goe</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Jan 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Your-Oral-Health-is-Your-Total-Health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing Enough Food to Feed a Family Year-Round by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Growing-Enough-Food-to-Feed-a-Family.html</link>
			<description>It's a great thought of growing enough food to feed your family year round by yourself. Certain things are really important for such a though, like how much food is needed for your family, which crops to plant, how to get the most from your plot, and how to preserve your extra harvest.
                                How much food is needed?
                                Let's say a 200 square f</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2022 11:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Growing-Enough-Food-to-Feed-a-Family.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian style Spanish omelette, Egg + Potato + Onion</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</link>
			<description>Egg with Potato plus Onion will make a delicious and healthy breakfast, You have have it as a Breakfast or you can have it as a Snack in the day, will also be a great starter in the barbecue. This combination of dish is called Spanish omelette, but lets make it in Indian Style.
                                Ingredients Needed?
                                3 Eggs, 4 medium sized Potato (choppe</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 07 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg Stuffed Paratha Recipe - Home made</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Egg-Stuffed-Paratha-Home-made-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Egg Stuffed Paratha is a delicious and healthy Paratha dish, filled with egg mixture. Both the eggs and whole wheat are healthy as it provides the right amount of proteins and carbs. The egg mixture has finely chopped onions, green chili and coriander leaves. This is then slided into the half cooked paratha pockets and cooked further. The Egg Stuffed Parathas are quite filling in itself.Ingredient</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Egg-Stuffed-Paratha-Home-made-recipe.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>