<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Food - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/food.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Cook Pongal at Home - Pongal Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Pongal, a popular South Indian dish made with rice and lentils:  Ingredients:   1 cup raw rice 1/4 cup split yellow moong dal (split yellow lentils) 4 cups water 2 tablespoons ghee (clarified butter) 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon whole black peppercorns 1 tablespoon grated ginger A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 cashew nuts 10-12 curry leaves Salt to taste            </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Cauliflower Peas Masala at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Cauliflower Peas Masala:  Ingredients:   1 small cauliflower, cut into florets 1 cup green peas 2 onions, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon coriander powder 1/2 teaspoon garam masala Salt to tast</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Sambar at Home - Sambar recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sambar-at-home-sambar-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Andhra-style vegetable sambar, a delicious South Indian dish made with lentils and mixed vegetables, Here&amp;#39;s the recipe:  Ingredients:   1/2 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 cups mixed vegetables (such as drumsticks, carrots, beans, brinjal, pumpkin, etc.), chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, chopped 2 tablespoons tamarind pulp 2 tablespoons sambar powder 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sambar-at-home-sambar-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Brown rice vs White rice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/brown-rice-vs-white-rice.html</link>
			<description>Brown rice and white rice are two different types of rice that undergo varying levels of processing.  Here are some key differences between brown rice and white rice:   Processing: Brown rice is the whole grain rice that retains its bran, germ, and endosperm layers, while white rice has had its bran and germ removed, leaving only the endosperm. Nutritional Content: Brown rice is considered more nu</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/brown-rice-vs-white-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Palak Paneer at Home - Palak Paneer Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Palak paneer is a popular North Indian dish made with spinach and paneer (Indian cheese).  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing palak paneer at home for serving four people:  Ingredients:   2 cups chopped spinach (palak) 200g paneer, cut into small cubes 1 medium-sized onion, chopped 2 medium-sized tomatoes, chopped 1 tbsp ginger-garlic paste 1 green chili, chopped                                    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Mango Pickle at Home - Mango Pickle Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Mango pickle is a popular Indian condiment made with raw mangoes and spices.  Mango pickle is a variety of pickles prepared using mango. It is very popular in South and Southeast Asia. The pickling process in India differs from other regions mainly due to an additional spice mixture added to them after anaerobic fermentation.  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing mango pickle at home:  Ingredients:  </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to make a compost without worm/kitchen composting/organic composting</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</link>
			<description>Composting is a great way to reduce waste and create nutrient-rich soil for your garden. While worm composting and kitchen composting are popular methods, there are other ways to make compost without using worms or organic kitchen waste. Here are some options:   Leaf Composting: Fallen leaves are an excellent source of carbon and can be used to create a nutrient-rich compost. Simply pile up the le</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian style Spanish omelette, Egg + Potato + Onion</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</link>
			<description>Egg with Potato plus Onion will make a delicious and healthy breakfast, You have have it as a Breakfast or you can have it as a Snack in the day, will also be a great starter in the barbecue. This combination of dish is called Spanish omelette, but lets make it in Indian Style.  Ingredients Needed?  3 Eggs, 4 medium sized Potato (chopped in small) &amp;amp; 4 medium sized Onion (chopped in small), 4-5</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg Stuffed Paratha Home made Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Egg Stuffed Paratha is a delicious and healthy Paratha dish, filled with egg mixture. Both the eggs and whole wheat are healthy as it provides the right amount of proteins and carbs. The egg mixture has finely chopped onions, green chili and coriander leaves. This is then slided into the half cooked paratha pockets and cooked further. The Egg Stuffed Parathas are quite filling in itself.  Ingredie</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Eight vegetables that can be grown at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see eight vegetables that you can grow at your home easily. Chili pepper, Tomato, Garlic, Peas, Raddish, Cabbage, Cauliflower and Carrot are the few vegetables that you can grow at home with less effort.  1. Chili pepper  Chili pepper can be easily grown from seeds, so we need to buy good seeds for better results. Sprinkle seeds over the soil surface, then cover with a</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Onions to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Onions are easy to grow, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. They need less attention during the growth when compared to other plants.  Onions will be having flavonoids, which have both an antioxidant and anti-inflammatory effect. By eating them regularly in sufficient quantities, these components will help people to protect themselves from chronic conditions such as ca</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Tomatoes to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see how they can grow tomatoes at their home and with the help of just other tomatoes at home. We have a few other articles which help to grow vegetables at home, you can read them from here.  Generally tomatoes are used in the kitchen for almost all the curries in South Indian dishes.  Tomatoes are rich in Vitamin B9, Vitamin C and Potassium and these Antioxidants pro</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cooking Food with Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
			<description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Pudina to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Pudina is easy to grow and hard to kill, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. It&amp;#39;s especially known for its soothing effect on the stomach.  Pudina is a fast growing plant, it&amp;#39;s good to keep it in a pot or a container with some boundary, so that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take up all your garden or yard.  If people buy Pudina from a market or get Punida from a neighbor&amp;#39</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Broccoli to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Broccoli is worth growing for its nutritional content value. This is rich in Vitamins and Minerals and is a good source of Vitamin A, Potassium, Folic acid, Iron and Fiber.  Broccoli is a cool seasonal crop, so it should be started in early winters. September and October are the best months for seed germination.  Germination Process?   You can start seeds in almost any type of container as long as</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pudina chutney Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Pudina Chutney is a flavorful condiment and aromatic chutney to serve with rice, mudde, idli, dosa. Pudina Chutney can also be served with snacks like bonda, bajji too.  People sometimes are confused pudina chutney with mint chutney or green chutney that is served along with chats and tandoori platter, but it&amp;#39;s not the same which we serve with rice or mudde or idle, and this chutney is more au</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
			<description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Chintakaya Pachadi Recipe, Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi chintakaya pachadi (Green raw tamarind pickle) is an age-old dish, which is generally eaten with Rice &amp; some also eaten with Ghee for even better taste. As we Indians love the tangy &amp; sweetish taste of pickle, this delicious Pachi chintakaya pachadi is enjoyed by all age groups and in fact, the recipe is one among the famous Indian dishes. This dish also has many health benefits</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Pulusu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi Pulusu Recipe is a thin rasam made with freshly extracted tamarind water and mixed with sliced onions and freshly cut coriander leaves. Comfort food at its best when served with some steamed rice for a simple meal.
                                It is a different way of creating a rasam that has been followed by the people from Andhra Pradesh and Telangana. This rasam is not he</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Raw Mango Chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Raw mango chutney is a flavorful condiment made with raw mangos, coriander leaves, onions and some spices. Raw Mango Chutney is a must-try recipe when raw mangoes are in season. Raw mangoes are packed with minerals and vitamins and are good to beat the summer heat.
                                This raw mango chutney aids digestion and enhances the taste, aroma, and nutrition of any dish. We usu</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Oranges - Let us know how to peel off &amp; eat; along with its benefits</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/oranges-let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</link>
			<description>Ever heard of that name, it’s a fruit which helps us to boost our immunity levels and lowers the risk of diseases.
                                In this lockdown time, one day I felt very tired, couldn’t continue my routine life, and coincidently, all my family members were affected with some or other illness like headache, cough, cold, backache and tiredness to do mundane things.
          </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/oranges-let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Researchers solve riddle of plant immune system</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</link>
			<description>How do plants build resilience? An international research team led by the University of Gottingen studied the molecular mechanisms of the plant immune system. They were able to show a connection between a relatively unknown gene and resistance to pathogens. The results of the study were published in the journal The Plant Cell.
                                Scientists from "PRoTECT" -- Plant Resp</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Saving Vegetable seeds for your backyard gardening</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/saving-vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</link>
			<description>To become more food self-sufficient, we should plan to collect, store and use some of the seed for your own garden. With this we can create new &amp; custom varieties of vegetables that grow best in our backyard. This can be done with small amount of effort involved. Also you will have fun in the process too.
                                You can save vegetable seeds from your garden produce to plan</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/saving-vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing Enough Food to Feed a Family Year-Round by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-food-to-feed-a-family.html</link>
			<description>It's a great thought of growing enough food to feed your family year round by yourself. Certain things are really important for such a though, like how much food is needed for your family, which crops to plant, how to get the most from your plot, and how to preserve your extra harvest.
                                How much food is needed?
                                Let's say a 200 square f</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-food-to-feed-a-family.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>