<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Fruits - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fruits.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>What will happen to the body if you eat dried fruits every day?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-will-happen-to-the-body-if-you-eat-dried-fruits-every-day.html</link>
			<description>Eating dried fruits every day can have both positive and potentially negative effects on the body, depending on various factors such as the type and quantity of dried fruits consumed, an individual&amp;#39;s overall diet and their health status.  Here are some considerations:  Positive Effects:   Nutrient Intake: Dried fruits are concentrated sources of nutrients, including vitamins, minerals and fibe</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 08:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-will-happen-to-the-body-if-you-eat-dried-fruits-every-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are recommended servings of fruits and vegetables?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-recommended-servings-of-fruits-and-vegetables.html</link>
			<description>The recommended servings of fruits and vegetables can vary slightly based on factors such as age, sex and activity level. However, general guidelines provide a useful framework for individuals to ensure they&amp;#39;re incorporating enough fruits and vegetables into their diet.  According to dietary guidelines, a common recommendation for adults is to aim for:   Fruits:   Quantity: 1.5 to 2 cups per d</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-recommended-servings-of-fruits-and-vegetables.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How much fruit intake is too much for a person?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-much-fruit-intake-is-too-much-for-a-person.html</link>
			<description>The recommended intake of fruit can vary based on factors such as age, sex, activity level and overall health. However, general dietary guidelines suggest that adults should aim for 1.5 to 2 cups of fruit per day. This can include whole fruits, such as apples, bananas, berries, etc., or 100% fruit juice.  Here are some considerations regarding fruit intake:   Balanced Diet: It&amp;#39;s important to c</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-much-fruit-intake-is-too-much-for-a-person.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Which fruits are having amazing health benefits?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/which-fruits-are-having-amazing-health-benefits.html</link>
			<description>Many fruits offer a wide range of health benefits due to their rich nutrient content, antioxidants and other bioactive compounds.  Here are some fruits known for their amazing health benefits:  Blueberries:   Rich in antioxidants, particularly anthocyanins. May improve cognitive function and have anti-inflammatory effects.   Strawberries:   High in vitamin C, manganese and antioxidants. May have c</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/which-fruits-are-having-amazing-health-benefits.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Health benefits of bananas and why people need to consume them?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/health-benefits-of-bananas-and-why-people-need-to-consume-them.html</link>
			<description>Bananas are a popular and nutritious fruit that offer a range of health benefits.  Here are some reasons why people should consider including bananas in their diet:   Rich in Nutrients: Bananas are a good source of several essential nutrients, including potassium, vitamin C, vitamin B6 and dietary fiber. High in Potassium: Potassium is a crucial mineral for maintaining proper heart and muscle func</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/health-benefits-of-bananas-and-why-people-need-to-consume-them.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>