<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Government - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/government.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>RCB, Alcohol Ownership, and the Public Spectacle: A Modern-Colosseum Distraction?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rcb-alcohol-ownership-and-the-public-spectacle-a-modern-colosseum-distraction.html</link>
			<description>Every April&amp;ndash;May from past 18 years, Bengaluru transforms into a sea of red and black as fans don RCB jerseys and pour into pubs, chanting their team&amp;rsquo;s praises. For many, RCB (Royal Challengers Bengaluru) isn&amp;rsquo;t just a cricket franchise&amp;mdash;it&amp;rsquo;s Karnataka pride incarnate. 🏏 But beneath the enthusiasm lies a deeper truth: RCB is owned by United Spirits, a subsidiary of Di</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rcb-alcohol-ownership-and-the-public-spectacle-a-modern-colosseum-distraction.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Should people really vote in democracy?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</link>
			<description>Yes, voting is a crucial aspect of a democratic society and it plays a fundamental role in shaping the governance and policies of a nation.  Here are some reasons why voting is important:   Representation: Voting allows individuals to have a say in choosing representatives who will make decisions on their behalf. By participating in elections, citizens can help ensure that their interests and conc</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>INS Vikrant Delivered to Indian Navy, First Indigenous Aircraft Carrier by India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</link>
			<description>INS Vikrant which is also known as Indigenous Aircraft Carrier 1 (IAC-1). It is the first aircraft carrier to be built in India. This is an Aircraft Carrier constructed by the Cochin Shipyard Limited (CSL) for the Indian Navy.  The name Vikrant means courageous in Sanskrit. The motto of the ship is Jayema Saṁ Yudhi Sprdhah, which means I defeat those who fight against me.  Brief of the backgroun</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Droupadi Murmu, New President of India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</link>
			<description>Droupadi Murmu was nominated to President elections and on 21st of July 2022 elections counting was finished and Droupadi Murmu won the elections and will be the New President of India, Murmu is likely to take oath on July 25 as President of India.  A few highlights of 15th President of India   Droupadi Murmu will be the first person belonging to a Scheduled Tribe (ST) community to be elected as t</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>President of India nominated Veerendra Heggade, P.T. Usha, Ilaiyaraaja and V. Vijayendra Prasad to the Rajya Sabha</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</link>
			<description>According to the Fourth Schedule (Articles 4(1) and 80(2)) of the Constitution of India, The President of India can nominate 12 members to Rajya Sabha for a term of six-years for their contributions towards Arts, Literature, Sciences and Social Services.  Maybe earlier most of the South Indian peoples, for this matter all the Indian people might not be aware that The President of India can nominat</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>