<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Health - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/health.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Monkeypox Outbreak around the World in 2022</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</link>
			<description>The outbreak of monkeypox, which is a viral disease, was confirmed in May 2022, once few cases were found in the United Kingdom. The first case was detected on 6th May 2022 and confirmed this case had travel links to Nigeria (where the disease is endemic).  From 18th May 2022 onwards, there was an increase in cases in Europe, North and South America, Asia, Africa, and Australia.  As of 23rd July 2</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Stop Overthinking your Thoughts of Future</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</link>
			<description>Overthinking your thoughts will lead you to even more worry. If you are an overthinker or a person who thinks to take precautions for the future, then you will know exactly how it goes. Generally a problem comes to your mind, for example a worry or health or a problem at work or some sort of issue in a relationship, because of the thoughts you will be thinking about it a lot and you will try to ge</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Help People to recognize the Physical Signs of Stress and Manage the Stress</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/help-people-to-recognize-the-physical-signs-of-stress-and-manage-the-stress.html</link>
			<description>Actually stress symptoms may be affecting your health in one or the other way, even though you might not actually realise it. You might think, the stress you are facing is because of your Life or Work or the stuff which you are doing, but it cannot be true.  The true reason for having stress could be that you are not able to manage the stress properly. And this Stress will lead people to not be pr</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/help-people-to-recognize-the-physical-signs-of-stress-and-manage-the-stress.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Importance of Good Sleep for Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/importance-of-good-sleep-for-health.html</link>
			<description>Nowadays in this busy life, good sleep is very rare for all kinds of generations.  Late night sleep, watching phones and computers till late at night makes our sleep very difficult.  Everyone has to sleep for at least 7 to 9 hours per night. Good sleep makes the mind calm and relaxed, even a fresh day starts with good sleep.  Hormone called melatonin is produced by the brain and helps to get sleep</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/importance-of-good-sleep-for-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Benefits of Aloe vera in Oral Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/benefits-of-aloe-vera-in-oral-health.html</link>
			<description>Aloe vera or aloe barbadensis, is a medicinal plant which is a thick short stemmed plant that stores aloe vera gel in its leaves.  It is used topically in most of today&amp;#39;s skin diseases,sun burns,hair etc.  Studies have shown that aloe vera has its own benefits in oral health as well.  Aloe vera contains more vitamins and minerals.  In oral health  Aloe vera plays an important role in the numbe</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/benefits-of-aloe-vera-in-oral-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dentist Inputs on Diabetes and Oral Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-inputs-on-diabetes-and-oral-health.html</link>
			<description>In diabetes people, due to increased glycaemic state, there will be more glucose and nutrients available for bacteria to keep alive and flourish. And this results in an increase in the bacterial load, as they can live and flourish well. And diabetic people take insulin, which is a hormone that is necessary to keep the level of blood glucose under check. And Diabetes mellitus (DM), is a group of me</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-inputs-on-diabetes-and-oral-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dentist suggestions on Teeth Cleaning</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-teeth-cleaning.html</link>
			<description>As we brush our teeth twice a day in such cases as well, do we really need teeth cleaning? And why does the Dentist say to have teeth cleaning in such cases also?.
                            Let’s understand what it is actually from a Dentist.
                            In Dental terminology, teeth cleaning is referred to as "Scaling". So what is this "Scaling"? While you visit a Dentist for S</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-teeth-cleaning.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Studies estimate long COVID-19 has over two hundred Symptoms</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</link>
			<description>According to a Lancet's journal EClinicalMedicine, In the Coronavirus (Covid-19) patients who are facing prolonged symptoms have reported more than 200 symptoms across 10 organ systems.
                            They have analysed the responses of 3,762 peoples from 56 different countries with confirmed or suspected Covid-19. And the data were collected from September 6, 2020, to November 25, 20</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Precautions while travelling during Coronavirus times</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/precautions-while-travelling-during-coronavirus-times.html</link>
			<description>It is not completely safe to travel during the Coronavirus times. Although the mortality rate of the people affected with COVID appears to be quite low, there is always a chance with the data which we get in our country. I see one should avoid travelling as much as possible so that we reduce the chances of spreading the virus.
                                Following are some of the things to be </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/precautions-while-travelling-during-coronavirus-times.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why Dental Implants?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-dental-implants.html</link>
			<description>Advanced dental treatments all over the world led to new advanced solutions for dental problems, one such is Implant. An implant is a medical device manufactured to replace a missing biological structure, support a damaged biological structure, or enhance an existing biological structure.
                                In cases a like, 
                                    A person’s teeth missi</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-dental-implants.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Black Fungus - Detected in Coronavirus Patients</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</link>
			<description>Black fungus is an infection caused by a fungus named mucormycosis. This fungal infection is being reported in a few Corona-affected patients during or post-recovery.
                                People catch mucormycosis when they come in contact with the fungal spores in the environment. It can also be contacted through skin contact through a cut, burn, or any other form of skin trauma.
     </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dentist suggestions on Quit Smoking &amp; Breathe Healthy</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-quit-smoking-breathe-healthy.html</link>
			<description>We have heard many times that smoking causes cancer. Smoking kills! but how? Let's know about facts about smoking and it's harmful causes to our body.
                                Each one cigarette contains nicotine (the main ingredient) and more than 5000 chemical compounds of which many are cancerous. The nicotine gets you addicted to smoking as every time you smoke a cigarette, you get a go</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dentist-suggestions-on-quit-smoking-breathe-healthy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tooth Sensitivity? What to do &amp; What not to do?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tooth-sensitivity-what-to-do-what-not-to-do.html</link>
			<description>Are you afraid of eating any food which is hot or cold or sweet or sour? If yes, then u might be suffering from tooth sensitivity. In this article, we're gonna get dentist advice for, What causes tooth sensitivity? And What should you do if you have tooth sensitivity? And what should you not do if you have tooth sensitivity?
                                So, let's see what our dentist says..
   </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tooth-sensitivity-what-to-do-what-not-to-do.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Heat waves in India and Current Temperature Status and Warning for next five Days</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/heat-waves-in-india-and-current-temperature-status-and-warning-for-next-five-day.html</link>
			<description>In 21st century due to climate changes, global temperature can increase means heat waves would be compartively more. This might affect human health a lot and in some cases can lead to death. We should know that, these heat waves will affect many people in small amount of time.
                                In India, these Heat waves generally occur from March - June, &amp; in some cases, they might </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/heat-waves-in-india-and-current-temperature-status-and-warning-for-next-five-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to keep your Kids Teeth Healthy and Strong?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-keep-your-kids-teeth-healthy-strong.html</link>
			<description>Good smiles from kids makes us smile more and keep us happy. But how to make your kids teeth healthy from initial stages. Within this  article, I will be sharing a few basic tips to keep your kids teeth healthy &amp; strong.
                                Here are few basic measures to be taken by every parent to keep their kids teeth healthy &amp; strong.
                                - &amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp;A </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-keep-your-kids-teeth-healthy-strong.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World Cancer Day, February 4th - Early detection of Cancer can lead to Improved outcomes &amp; Cure.</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</link>
			<description>Cancer is a large group of diseases that can start in almost any organ or tissue of the body when abnormal cells grow uncontrollably, go beyond their usual boundaries to invade adjoining parts of the body and/or spread to other organs. The latter process is called metastasizing which is a major cause of death from cancer. A neoplasm and malignant tumour are other common names for cancer.
         </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Your Oral Health is Your Total Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/your-oral-health-is-your-total-health.html</link>
			<description>We human beings, to live and survive consume food as a basic need. How many of us have thought that food we consume orally is keeping one's dental health in good condition.
                                Studies and researchers have proven that.. plaque and calculus in dental terminology which contains aerobic and anaerobic bacteria which accumulated and attached to teeth slowly discharge and goe</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/your-oral-health-is-your-total-health.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>