<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Health - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/health.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Hormonal Imbalances: Common Symptoms and Treatments</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hormonal-imbalances-common-symptoms-and-treatments.html</link>
			<description>Hormones play a vital role in regulating many functions in the body, including growth, metabolism, reproduction, and mood. When these chemical messengers are too high or too low, it leads to hormonal imbalance&amp;mdash;a condition that can affect men and women at any stage of life. Recognizing the symptoms and seeking timely treatment is essential for restoring balance and maintaining overall health.</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Sep 2025 15:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hormonal-imbalances-common-symptoms-and-treatments.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How Hereditary Conditions Are Diagnosed and Managed</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-hereditary-conditions-are-diagnosed-and-managed.html</link>
			<description>Hereditary conditions, also known as genetic disorders, are health problems passed down from parents to children through genes. These conditions can range from mild issues like lactose intolerance to more serious disorders such as cystic fibrosis, sickle cell anemia, or Huntington&amp;rsquo;s disease. Understanding how these conditions are diagnosed and managed is important because early detection and</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-hereditary-conditions-are-diagnosed-and-managed.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Advances in Prosthetic Limb Technology</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advances-in-prosthetic-limb-technology.html</link>
			<description>Prosthetic limb technology has undergone remarkable transformation over the past two decades, evolving from basic mechanical replacements to highly sophisticated, sensor-integrated, and AI-assisted extensions of the human body. These innovations are not only restoring mobility for amputees but also redefining what artificial limbs can do&amp;mdash;enhancing lives with improved functionality, comfort, </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Aug 2025 09:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advances-in-prosthetic-limb-technology.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Importance of Post-Surgical Rehabilitation Programs</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-importance-of-post-surgical-rehabilitation-programs.html</link>
			<description>Undergoing surgery is often just the beginning of a patient&amp;#39;s journey to recovery. What follows&amp;mdash;post-surgical rehabilitation&amp;mdash;is equally vital to ensure full healing, restore function, and improve quality of life. Post-surgical rehabilitation programs are structured, individualized plans that guide patients through recovery, aiming to minimize complications, regain strength, and hel</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 08:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-importance-of-post-surgical-rehabilitation-programs.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How Nanotechnology is Revolutionizing Medicine</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-nanotechnology-is-revolutionizing-medicine.html</link>
			<description>Nanotechnology, the science of manipulating materials at the molecular and atomic level, is transforming modern medicine. By working at a scale of nanometers (one-billionth of a meter), researchers and doctors can develop highly precise treatments, improve diagnostics, and create innovative medical devices. From targeted drug delivery to tissue engineering, nanotechnology is revolutionizing health</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-nanotechnology-is-revolutionizing-medicine.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Exploring the Use of Artificial Organs in Healthcare</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/exploring-the-use-of-artificial-organs-in-healthcare.html</link>
			<description>Artificial organs represent one of the most groundbreaking advancements in modern medicine, offering hope to patients suffering from organ failure. With the increasing demand for organ transplants and the limited availability of donor organs, artificial organs have emerged as a life-saving alternative. These bioengineered or mechanically created organs aim to restore lost function, improve quality</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2025 13:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/exploring-the-use-of-artificial-organs-in-healthcare.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Role of Virtual Reality in Surgical Training</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-role-of-virtual-reality-in-surgical-training.html</link>
			<description>Virtual reality (VR) has revolutionized many industries, and healthcare is no exception. One of the most significant advancements in this domain is the use of VR in surgical training. By creating immersive, interactive, and realistic simulations, VR provides an innovative platform for medical professionals to develop and refine their surgical skills. This technology is transforming the way surgeon</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 07:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-role-of-virtual-reality-in-surgical-training.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How Community Health Campaigns Save Lives</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-community-health-campaigns-save-lives.html</link>
			<description>Community health campaigns play a vital role in promoting public health, preventing diseases, and saving lives. By addressing health challenges at the community level, these campaigns aim to educate, empower, and inspire individuals to adopt healthier behaviors and make informed decisions. Whether focused on disease prevention, vaccination, nutrition, or mental health, community health campaigns h</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 08:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-community-health-campaigns-save-lives.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prevent morning breath?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prevent-morning-breath.html</link>
			<description>Morning breath, also known as halitosis, is a common issue caused by the natural decrease in saliva production while you sleep. Without adequate saliva to rinse away bacteria, odor-causing microbes can flourish, leading to unpleasant breath upon waking.  While it&amp;rsquo;s a natural occurrence, there are several steps you can take to minimize or prevent morning breath.  Understanding the Causes of M</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 08:59:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prevent-morning-breath.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Reasons to Hang Eucalyptus in Your Shower</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reasons-to-hang-eucalyptus-in-your-shower.html</link>
			<description>Hanging eucalyptus in your shower has become a popular practice, not only because it adds a touch of natural beauty but because it offers a wide range of health and wellness benefits. Eucalyptus, a plant known for its distinctive aroma and healing properties, has been used for centuries in traditional medicine to relieve respiratory issues, promote relaxation, and improve overall well-being.  Here</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reasons-to-hang-eucalyptus-in-your-shower.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Working out at this time can help manage blood sugar</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/working-out-at-this-time-can-help-manage-blood-sugar.html</link>
			<description>Timing your workouts can play a significant role in blood sugar management, especially for individuals with diabetes or prediabetes. Exercise helps increase insulin sensitivity and facilitates glucose uptake by muscles, helping to maintain stable blood sugar levels.  The Best Time for Blood Sugar Control: After Meals  Studies suggest that working out after meals, particularly after lunch or dinner</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/working-out-at-this-time-can-help-manage-blood-sugar.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How long does nicotine stay in your system?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-long-does-nicotine-stay-in-your-system.html</link>
			<description>Nicotine, the addictive substance found in tobacco products like cigarettes, cigars and e-cigarettes, enters your system quickly and has various effects on the body. Understanding how long nicotine stays in your system is important for anyone looking to quit smoking, undergo testing, or better understand the health impacts of nicotine.  How Nicotine is Absorbed and Metabolized  When you smoke or u</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 12:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-long-does-nicotine-stay-in-your-system.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is living a healthy lifestyle important?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-living-a-healthy-lifestyle-important.html</link>
			<description>Living a healthy lifestyle is important for many reasons that affect both your body and mind.  Better Physical Health   Staying healthy can lower the chances of getting diseases like heart disease, diabetes and some cancers. It helps you stay fit, strengthens your immune system and can help you live longer.   Improved Mental Health   Regular exercise and eating well can boost your mood, reduce str</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 Oct 2024 11:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-living-a-healthy-lifestyle-important.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Role of Vedas in Hindu Philosophy</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-role-of-vedas-in-hindu-philosophy.html</link>
			<description>The Vedas are the oldest sacred texts in Hinduism and have greatly influenced Hindu philosophy. Written in ancient Sanskrit, these texts cover a variety of ideas about philosophy, spirituality and rituals that shape Hindu thought and practice.  This article looks at how the Vedas contribute to Hindu philosophy by examining their teachings, their impact on later philosophical schools and their last</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Sep 2024 10:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-role-of-vedas-in-hindu-philosophy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Everything you need to know about blood pressure</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everything-you-need-to-know-about-blood-pressure.html</link>
			<description>Blood pressure is the force of blood pushing against the walls of the arteries as the heart pumps it around the body.  It is an important indicator of cardiovascular health.  Key Components:   Systolic Pressure: The higher number in a blood pressure reading, indicating the pressure in the arteries when the heart beats. Diastolic Pressure: The lower number, indicating the pressure in the arteries w</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 21:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everything-you-need-to-know-about-blood-pressure.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to increase breast size naturally</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-increase-breast-size-naturally.html</link>
			<description>Increasing breast size naturally is a common concern, but it&amp;#39;s important to note that there are no guaranteed methods to significantly increase breast size without surgery.  However, some natural methods may help enhance breast appearance or promote overall breast health:  Exercises:   Push-Ups:   Strengthen the chest muscles (pectorals) which can make breasts appear firmer. Lie face down with</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-increase-breast-size-naturally.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Natural home remedies for Constipation</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/natural-home-remedies-for-constipation.html</link>
			<description>Constipation is a common digestive condition characterized by infrequent, difficult, or painful bowel movements. It typically involves having fewer than three bowel movements per week, with stools that are often hard, dry and difficult to pass. Symptoms may include abdominal discomfort, bloating and a feeling of incomplete evacuation after a bowel movement.  Constipation can often be managed with </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 20:47:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/natural-home-remedies-for-constipation.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>PCOS - Symptoms, Causes, Diagnosis, Treatment, Recovery</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pcos-symptoms-causes-diagnosis-treatment-recovery.html</link>
			<description>PCOS is recognized as a common endocrine disorder affecting women of reproductive age, with significant advancements in its diagnosis, treatment and management aimed at improving quality of life and long-term health outcomes.  PCOS is a hormonal disorder characterized by a combination of symptoms including irregular periods, elevated androgen levels and the presence of multiple small ovarian cysts</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 07:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pcos-symptoms-causes-diagnosis-treatment-recovery.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Five exercises to naturally increase penis size</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/five-exercises-to-naturally-increase-penis-size.html</link>
			<description>There is no scientific evidence to support that exercises can significantly increase penis size. However, certain exercises can improve erectile function and overall penile health by increasing blood flow and strengthening the pelvic floor muscles.  Here are five exercises that may help:  Kegel Exercises:   Purpose: Strengthen the pelvic floor muscles, which support erectile function. How to Perfo</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/five-exercises-to-naturally-increase-penis-size.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rheumatoid Arthritis - Symptoms, Causes, Diagnosis, Treatment, Recovery</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rheumatoid-arthritis-symptoms-causes-diagnosis-treatment-recovery.html</link>
			<description>Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is a chronic inflammatory disorder that primarily affects the joints. It is an autoimmune condition, meaning the immune system mistakenly attacks the body&amp;#39;s own tissues.  Symptoms:   Joint pain and swelling: Commonly affects small joints in the hands, wrists and feet. Stiffness: Particularly pronounced in the morning or after periods of inactivity. Fatigue: Persistent</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rheumatoid-arthritis-symptoms-causes-diagnosis-treatment-recovery.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lifestyle changes to enhance your mood and mental health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lifestyle-changes-to-enhance-your-mood-and-mental-health.html</link>
			<description>Enhancing your mood and mental health often requires a holistic approach that includes various lifestyle changes.  Here are several effective strategies:  1. Regular Exercise   Why: Physical activity releases endorphins and other chemicals that improve mood and reduce anxiety. How: Aim for at least 30 minutes of moderate exercise, such as walking, running, or cycling, most days of the week.   2. B</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 13:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lifestyle-changes-to-enhance-your-mood-and-mental-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Importance of Holistic Wellness at Workplace</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/importance-of-holistic-wellness-at-workplace.html</link>
			<description>Holistic wellness at the workplace is crucial for fostering a healthy, productive and engaged workforce. Holistic wellness addresses the overall well-being of employees, encompassing physical, mental, emotional and social aspects.  Here are several reasons why holistic wellness is important in the workplace:   Increased Productivity:   Why: Healthy employees are more productive, engaged and motiva</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jun 2024 18:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/importance-of-holistic-wellness-at-workplace.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Average yearly consumption of Rice for the typical Indian</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/average-yearly-consumption-of-rice-for-the-typical-indian.html</link>
			<description>Average yearly consumption of rice for a typical Indian varies based on factors such as region, cultural practices, dietary preferences and socioeconomic status.  However, rice is a staple food in India and is consumed in significant quantities across the country.  Why Rice is Consumed:   Cultural Significance:   Rice holds immense cultural significance in India and is deeply ingrained in traditio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 08:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/average-yearly-consumption-of-rice-for-the-typical-indian.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cure PCOD or PCOS to have better Lifestyle</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cure-pcod-pcos-to-have-better-lifestyle.html</link>
			<description>Polycystic ovary syndrome (PCOS) and polycystic ovary disorder (PCOD) are chronic conditions that do not have a cure. However, lifestyle changes and medical interventions can help manage symptoms and improve overall quality of life.  Here are some strategies to promote a better lifestyle with PCOS/PCOD:   Dietary Modifications:   Balanced Diet: Adopt a balanced diet rich in fruits, vegetables, who</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 10:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cure-pcod-pcos-to-have-better-lifestyle.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What percentage of Indians are vegetarian?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</link>
			<description>Approximately 30-40% of the population in India is estimated to follow a vegetarian diet. However, this percentage can vary depending on the region, cultural practices and religious beliefs.  Why Indians Follow Vegetarianism:   Religious Beliefs:   Hinduism: Many Hindus follow a vegetarian diet as part of their religious beliefs, which promote compassion and non-violence (ahimsa). They believe in </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What will happen to the body if you eat dried fruits every day?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-will-happen-to-the-body-if-you-eat-dried-fruits-every-day.html</link>
			<description>Eating dried fruits every day can have both positive and potentially negative effects on the body, depending on various factors such as the type and quantity of dried fruits consumed, an individual&amp;#39;s overall diet and their health status.  Here are some considerations:  Positive Effects:   Nutrient Intake: Dried fruits are concentrated sources of nutrients, including vitamins, minerals and fibe</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 08:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-will-happen-to-the-body-if-you-eat-dried-fruits-every-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are recommended servings of fruits and vegetables?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-recommended-servings-of-fruits-and-vegetables.html</link>
			<description>The recommended servings of fruits and vegetables can vary slightly based on factors such as age, sex and activity level. However, general guidelines provide a useful framework for individuals to ensure they&amp;#39;re incorporating enough fruits and vegetables into their diet.  According to dietary guidelines, a common recommendation for adults is to aim for:   Fruits:   Quantity: 1.5 to 2 cups per d</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-recommended-servings-of-fruits-and-vegetables.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How much fruit intake is too much for a person?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-much-fruit-intake-is-too-much-for-a-person.html</link>
			<description>The recommended intake of fruit can vary based on factors such as age, sex, activity level and overall health. However, general dietary guidelines suggest that adults should aim for 1.5 to 2 cups of fruit per day. This can include whole fruits, such as apples, bananas, berries, etc., or 100% fruit juice.  Here are some considerations regarding fruit intake:   Balanced Diet: It&amp;#39;s important to c</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-much-fruit-intake-is-too-much-for-a-person.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best food to have for better bowel movement</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-food-to-have-for-better-bowel-movement.html</link>
			<description>Maintaining good bowel movements is essential for overall digestive health.  Here are some foods that can promote healthy bowel movements:   Fiber-Rich Foods:   Whole Grains: Brown rice, quinoa, oats and whole wheat. Legumes: Beans, lentils and chickpeas. Fruits: Berries, apples, pears, prunes and kiwi. Vegetables: Broccoli, carrots, sweet potatoes and leafy greens.   Prunes (Dried Plums): Prunes </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Mar 2024 11:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-food-to-have-for-better-bowel-movement.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Which fruits are having amazing health benefits?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/which-fruits-are-having-amazing-health-benefits.html</link>
			<description>Many fruits offer a wide range of health benefits due to their rich nutrient content, antioxidants and other bioactive compounds.  Here are some fruits known for their amazing health benefits:  Blueberries:   Rich in antioxidants, particularly anthocyanins. May improve cognitive function and have anti-inflammatory effects.   Strawberries:   High in vitamin C, manganese and antioxidants. May have c</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Dec 2023 14:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/which-fruits-are-having-amazing-health-benefits.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Health benefits of bananas and why people need to consume them?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/health-benefits-of-bananas-and-why-people-need-to-consume-them.html</link>
			<description>Bananas are a popular and nutritious fruit that offer a range of health benefits.  Here are some reasons why people should consider including bananas in their diet:   Rich in Nutrients: Bananas are a good source of several essential nutrients, including potassium, vitamin C, vitamin B6 and dietary fiber. High in Potassium: Potassium is a crucial mineral for maintaining proper heart and muscle func</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Dec 2023 20:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/health-benefits-of-bananas-and-why-people-need-to-consume-them.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Importance of good sleep for health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/importance-of-good-sleep-for-health.html</link>
			<description>Nowadays in this busy life, good sleep is very rare for all kinds of generations.  Late night sleep, watching phones and computers till late at night makes our sleep very difficult.  Everyone has to sleep for at least 7 to 9 hours per night. Good sleep makes the mind calm and relaxed, even a fresh day starts with good sleep.  Hormone called melatonin is produced by the brain and helps to get sleep</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/importance-of-good-sleep-for-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Nutrient foods which people need to have daily</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/nutrient-foods-which-people-need-to-have-daily.html</link>
			<description>Eating a variety of nutrient-dense foods is essential for maintaining good health.  Here is a list of nutrient-rich foods that people should consider including in their daily diet:  Vegetables:   Leafy greens (spinach, kale, collard greens) Cruciferous vegetables (broccoli, Brussels sprouts, cauliflower) Carrots Bell peppers Sweet potatoes   Fruits:   Berries (blueberries, strawberries, raspberrie</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/nutrient-foods-which-people-need-to-have-daily.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Possible reasons you feel tired all the time</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/possible-reasons-you-feel-tired-all-the-time.html</link>
			<description>Feeling tired all the time, or experiencing chronic fatigue, can be attributed to various factors and often, it&amp;#39;s a combination of several reasons.  Here are some possible reasons why you might feel tired frequently:   Lack of Sleep: Not getting enough sleep or experiencing poor sleep quality can leave you feeling tired and lethargic. Sleep Disorders: Conditions like sleep apnea, insomnia, or </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/possible-reasons-you-feel-tired-all-the-time.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is spinach called a superfood?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-spinach-called-a-superfood.html</link>
			<description>Spinach is a nutrient-rich leafy green vegetable that offers a wide range of health benefits. It&amp;#39;s a versatile and nutritious addition to various dishes and can be consumed cooked or raw.&amp;nbsp;  Here&amp;rsquo;s the nutritional composition of spinach per 100 grams of raw spinach:   Calories: 23 kcal Carbohydrates: 3.6 g  Dietary Fiber: 2.2 g Sugars: 0.4 g   Protein: 2.9 g Fat: 0.4 g  Saturated Fat</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 21 Oct 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-spinach-called-a-superfood.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What happens if people are having milk everyday?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happens-if-people-are-having-milk-everyday.html</link>
			<description>Consuming milk every day can have both positive and potential negative effects on health, depending on various factors such as individual tolerance, health conditions and the quantity consumed.  Here&amp;#39;s a balanced overview of what can happen if people have milk every day:  Positive Effects:   Nutrient Intake: Milk is a rich source of essential nutrients such as calcium, vitamin D, vitamin B12, </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Sep 2023 09:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happens-if-people-are-having-milk-everyday.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mental &amp; Physical Wellbeing Connection</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mental-and-physical-wellbeing-connection.html</link>
			<description>The connection between mental and physical well-being is significant. The state of our mind and emotions can have a direct impact on our physical health and likewise, our physical health can influence our mental well-being.  Here are some key aspects of the mental and physical well-being connection:   Psychological impact on physical health: Mental health conditions such as stress, anxiety and dep</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mental-and-physical-wellbeing-connection.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Checklist for building an Eco-Friendly Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</link>
			<description>To build a home, which makes low-impact environmentally. And built using materials &amp;amp; technology that lowers its energy needs in future. And also make sure built home is reliable for few decades with minimal energy spent on it.  To do this, you have to consider Energy? what Sustainable materials to be used? how it impacts on our health? And what is costs  Before getting into the details of each</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Eight vegetables that can be grown at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see eight vegetables that you can grow at your home easily. Chili pepper, Tomato, Garlic, Peas, Raddish, Cabbage, Cauliflower and Carrot are the few vegetables that you can grow at home with less effort.  1. Chili pepper  Chili pepper can be easily grown from seeds, so we need to buy good seeds for better results. Sprinkle seeds over the soil surface, then cover with a</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Monkeypox Outbreak around the World in 2022</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</link>
			<description>The outbreak of monkeypox, which is a viral disease, was confirmed in May 2022, once few cases were found in the United Kingdom. The first case was detected on 6th May 2022 and confirmed this case had travel links to Nigeria (where the disease is endemic).  From 18th May 2022 onwards, there was an increase in cases in Europe, North and South America, Asia, Africa and Australia.  As of 23rd July 20</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Stop Overthinking your Thoughts of Future</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</link>
			<description>Overthinking your thoughts will lead you to even more worry. If you are an overthinker or a person who thinks to take precautions for the future, then you will know exactly how it goes. Generally a problem comes to your mind, for example a worry or health or a problem at work or some sort of issue in a relationship, because of the thoughts you will be thinking about it a lot and you will try to ge</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Help People to recognize the Physical Signs of Stress and Manage the Stress</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/help-people-to-recognize-the-physical-signs-of-stress-and-manage-the-stress.html</link>
			<description>Actually stress symptoms may be affecting your health in one or the other way, even though you might not actually realise it. You might think, the stress you are facing is because of your Life or Work or the stuff which you are doing, but it cannot be true.  The true reason for having stress could be that you are not able to manage the stress properly. And this Stress will lead people to not be pr</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/help-people-to-recognize-the-physical-signs-of-stress-and-manage-the-stress.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Studies estimate long COVID-19 has over two hundred Symptoms</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</link>
			<description>According to a Lancet's journal EClinicalMedicine, In the Coronavirus (Covid-19) patients who are facing prolonged symptoms have reported more than 200 symptoms across 10 organ systems.                            They have analysed the responses of 3,762 peoples from 56 different countries with confirmed or suspected Covid-19. And the data were collected from September 6, 2020, to November 25, 202</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Precautions while travelling during Coronavirus times</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/precautions-while-travelling-during-coronavirus-times.html</link>
			<description>It is not completely safe to travel during the Coronavirus times. Although the mortality rate of the people affected with COVID appears to be quite low, there is always a chance with the data which we get in our country. I see one should avoid travelling as much as possible so that we reduce the chances of spreading the virus.                                Following are some of the things to be c</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/precautions-while-travelling-during-coronavirus-times.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Black Fungus - Detected in Coronavirus Patients</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</link>
			<description>Black fungus is an infection caused by a fungus named mucormycosis. This fungal infection is being reported in a few Corona-affected patients during or post-recovery.                                People catch mucormycosis when they come in contact with the fungal spores in the environment. It can also be contacted through skin contact through a cut, burn, or any other form of skin trauma.       </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Oranges - Let us know how to peel off &amp; eat; along with its benefits</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/oranges-let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</link>
			<description>Ever heard of that name, it&amp;rsquo;s a fruit which helps us to boost our immunity levels and lowers the risk of diseases.  In this lockdown time, one day I felt very tired, couldn&amp;rsquo;t continue my routine life and coincidently, all my family members were affected with some or other illness like headache, cough, cold, backache and tiredness to do mundane things.  When we all went to the doctor, h</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 19:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/oranges-let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Heat waves in India and Current Temperature Status and Warning for next five Days</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/heat-waves-in-india-and-current-temperature-status-and-warning-for-next-five-day.html</link>
			<description>In 21st century due to climate changes, global temperature can increase means heat waves would be compartively more. This might affect human health a lot and in some cases can lead to death. We should know that, these heat waves will affect many people in small amount of time.                                In India, these Heat waves generally occur from March - June, &amp; in some cases, they might e</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/heat-waves-in-india-and-current-temperature-status-and-warning-for-next-five-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Researchers solve riddle of plant immune system</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</link>
			<description>How do plants build resilience?  An international research team led by the University of Gottingen studied the molecular mechanisms of the plant immune system. They were able to show a connection between a relatively unknown gene and resistance to pathogens. The results of the study were published in the journal The Plant Cell.  Scientists from &amp;quot;PRoTECT&amp;quot; -- Plant Responses To Eliminate C</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 20 Aug 2024 09:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World Cancer Day, February 4th - Early detection of Cancer can lead to Improved outcomes &amp; Cure.</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</link>
			<description>Cancer is a large group of diseases that can start in almost any organ or tissue of the body when abnormal cells grow uncontrollably, go beyond their usual boundaries to invade adjoining parts of the body and/or spread to other organs. The latter process is called metastasizing which is a major cause of death from cancer. A neoplasm and malignant tumour are other common names for cancer.          </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>It is OK.. to not be ok !!! - Hanukkah John</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/it-is-ok-to-not-be-ok-hanukkah-john.html</link>
			<description>Ever felt that you are worthless or a burden to others? Ever felt so exhausted mentally? Ever felt sad not for a day or two but for weeks continuously? I'm not talking about grieving over a loss but feeling sad for something which you could have let go easily at least after a day or two.                                Have you ever found yourself lying in bed all day continuously for days doing no</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Hanukkah John</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/it-is-ok-to-not-be-ok-hanukkah-john.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>