<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
<title>Feeds - Peoples BLOG</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/feeds/index.html</link>
  <description/>
  <language>en</language>
  <item>
    <title>Discovering Wellness Through Work - Life Integration</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/discovering-wellness-through-work-life-integration.html</link>
    <description>Work-life integration is an approach that emphasizes finding a healthy and sustainable balance between work and personal life. It recognizes that work and personal life are interconnected and seeks to create harmony between the two rather than viewing them as separate entities in constant conflict.  Here are some ways to discover wellness through work-life integration:   Define your values and pri</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/discovering-wellness-through-work-life-integration.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Should people really vote in democracy?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</link>
    <description>Yes, voting is a crucial aspect of a democratic society, and it plays a fundamental role in shaping the governance and policies of a nation.  Here are some reasons why voting is important:   Representation: Voting allows individuals to have a say in choosing representatives who will make decisions on their behalf. By participating in elections, citizens can help ensure that their interests and con</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Why do people use shortcut words like AFK etc?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-use-shortcut-words-like-afk-etc.html</link>
    <description>People use shortcut words like AFK (Away From Keyboard), BRB (Be Right Back), LOL (Laughing Out Loud), and others for several reasons:   Convenience: Using shorthand or abbreviations can be faster and more convenient than typing out the full phrase or sentence. This is particularly true in online communication, where speed and brevity are often valued. Community and culture: Many shorthand words a</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-use-shortcut-words-like-afk-etc.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>node_get_recent() is deprecated in Drupal 10.1.x</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/node-get-recent-is-deprecated-in-drupal-ten.html</link>
    <description>node_get_recent() is unused in core and is now deprecated, developers can use views or EntityQuery to get the nodes which are recently modified or added.  Earlier drupal developers used to use the function&amp;nbsp;node_get_recent() to get the recently changed nodes like seen in below example  $latest_updated_nodes = node_get_recent(10);  Now from Drupal 10.1.x onwards, developers need to use entity q</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/node-get-recent-is-deprecated-in-drupal-ten.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Best way to add additional estimates upon the original estimate for a Story in a Sprint?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-way-to-add-additional-estimates-upon-the-original-estimate-for-a-story-in-a-sprint.html</link>
    <description>When additional work or requirements are identified for a Story during a Sprint, it is important to ensure that the impact on the Sprint&amp;#39;s scope and timeline is understood and communicated to the team and stakeholders. Here are some steps that can be followed to add additional estimates to a Story in a Sprint:   Review the original estimate: First, review the original estimate for the Story an</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-way-to-add-additional-estimates-upon-the-original-estimate-for-a-story-in-a-sprint.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to generate good revenue from blogging websites?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-generate-good-revenue-from-blogging-websites.html</link>
    <description>To maximize revenue from your blog, it&amp;#39;s important to focus on creating high-quality content, engaging with your audience, and promoting your blog through social media and other marketing channels.  There are several ways to generate revenue from a blogging website:   Advertising: Displaying ads on your blog is one of the most common ways to generate revenue. You can use ad networks like Googl</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-generate-good-revenue-from-blogging-websites.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to improve a website's SEO score and make it searchable on Search Engines like Google?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-websites-seo-score-and-make-it-searchable-on-search-engines-like-google.html</link>
    <description>It is very important for the business to have their web sites to be popular on the search engines and the process of improving the quality and quantity of website traffic to a website or a web page from search engines is search engine optimization.  In this article, we are going to see how one can improve their website&amp;rsquo;s SEO score and make the website popular on search engines.  Improving yo</description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-websites-seo-score-and-make-it-searchable-on-search-engines-like-google.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to prepare Palak Paneer at Home - Palak Paneer Recipe</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</link>
    <description>Palak paneer is a popular North Indian dish made with spinach and paneer (Indian cheese).  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing palak paneer at home for serving four people:  Ingredients:   2 cups chopped spinach (palak) 200g paneer, cut into small cubes 1 medium-sized onion, chopped 2 medium-sized tomatoes, chopped 1 tbsp ginger-garlic paste 1 green chili, chopped                                    </description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to prepare Mango Pickle at Home - Mango Pickle Recipe</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</link>
    <description>Mango pickle is a popular Indian condiment made with raw mangoes and spices.  Mango pickle is a variety of pickles prepared using mango. It is very popular in South and Southeast Asia. The pickling process in India differs from other regions mainly due to an additional spice mixture added to them after anaerobic fermentation.  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing mango pickle at home:  Ingredients:  </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Why should we chant Hare Rama Hare Krishna Mahamantra?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-should-we-chant-hare-rama-hare-krishna-mahamantra.html</link>
    <description>The Hare Krishna Mahamantra, also known as the Maha Mantra, is a powerful mantra that is chanted by devotees of the Krishna Consciousness movement.  The Hare Krishna Maha Mantra is a chant that is believed to have spiritual and transformative effects. It is chanted by devotees of the Hare Krishna movement and those who follow the Vaishnavite tradition of Hinduism.  The Hare Krishna Maha Mantra is </description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-should-we-chant-hare-rama-hare-krishna-mahamantra.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How Do I Deal with Anxiety During Sex?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-i-deal-with-anxiety-during-sex.html</link>
    <description>Experiencing anxiety during sex can be a common issue, and it is important to address the root cause of the anxiety and find ways to manage it.  Here are some tips for dealing with anxiety during sex:   Communicate with your partner: Let your partner know how you&amp;#39;re feeling and what you need to feel comfortable. Communication is key to a healthy and satisfying sexual experience.               </description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-i-deal-with-anxiety-during-sex.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to secure the Passwords of Users in Web Applications?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-secure-the-passwords-of-users-in-web-applications.html</link>
    <description>Generally while working with Web applications, one of the important data related to Users is their passwords, and keeping them secured is one of the important jobs of the Web application.  In this article we gonna see a brief how a developer or admin can make sure the passwords are secure on the web application.  Here are some best practices to secure passwords in web applications:   Use Strong Pa</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-secure-the-passwords-of-users-in-web-applications.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Fix Colima connection refused error: failed to get Info from .lima/colima/ha.sock on Mac</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-colima-connection-refused-error-failed-to-get-info-from-lima-colima-ha-sock-on-mac.html</link>
    <description>This article is about fixing only a single error which you see with Colima on Mac machines. This might be a simple &amp;amp; specific issue, but people who are facing this issue will really feel grateful with the solution provided.  While you are running Colima on your mac machines, generally you get into such issue, when you power off or shut down your mac, without stopping the colima service (and de</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-colima-connection-refused-error-failed-to-get-info-from-lima-colima-ha-sock-on-mac.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Everest Base Camp Trek - What should you know before you start?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-what-should-you-know-before-you-start.html</link>
    <description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of what to know before you proceed further.  The Everest Base Camp Trek is a challenging and rewarding adventure that takes you to the base of the highest mountain in the world.  Here are some things you should know before you start:   Physical Fitness: The Everest Base Camp Trek</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-what-should-you-know-before-you-start.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to make a compost without worm/kitchen composting/organic composting</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</link>
    <description>Composting is a great way to reduce waste and create nutrient-rich soil for your garden. While worm composting and kitchen composting are popular methods, there are other ways to make compost without using worms or organic kitchen waste. Here are some options:   Leaf Composting: Fallen leaves are an excellent source of carbon and can be used to create a nutrient-rich compost. Simply pile up the le</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>BDSM Role Play: How Does It Work?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bdsm-role-play-how-does-it-work.html</link>
    <description>BDSM (bondage and discipline, dominance and submission, sadism and masochism) role play is a consensual sexual activity that involves one partner taking on a dominant role and the other partner taking on a submissive role. This can include activities such as power exchange, restraint, and impact play.                     (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});        In BDSM role play, </description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bdsm-role-play-how-does-it-work.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Different ways to get more out of 69 position</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-ways-to-get-more-out-of-six-nine-position.html</link>
    <description>The 69 position is a popular sexual position that involves mutual oral sex. Here are some tips to get more out of the 69 position:  1. Change positions: Try changing positions to mix things up. You can start with one person on top, then switch to the other person on top, or try a side-by-side position.  2. Use your hands: Incorporate your hands into the mix by touching your partner&amp;#39;s erogenous</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-ways-to-get-more-out-of-six-nine-position.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Curiosity, how will this change people's Life?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/curiosity-how-will-this-change-peoples-life.html</link>
    <description>Curiosity can have a significant impact on a person&amp;#39;s life, both personally and professionally. Here are a few ways that curiosity can change a person&amp;#39;s life:   Learning and growth: Curiosity leads people to explore new ideas and concepts, and to seek out new experiences. This can lead to personal growth and learning, which can broaden their perspective and help them understand the world a</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/curiosity-how-will-this-change-peoples-life.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How can I evaluate whether counseling is working?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-evaluate-whether-counseling-is-working.html</link>
    <description>Evaluating whether counseling is working can be a challenging task because it is a personal and subjective experience. However, there are some indicators that can help you determine whether counseling is helping you to achieve your goals and make progress.  Here are some ways to evaluate whether counseling is working:   Reflection: Take some time to reflect on how you feel before and after each se</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-evaluate-whether-counseling-is-working.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How does confidentiality work?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-confidentiality-work.html</link>
    <description>Confidentiality is a fundamental aspect of the counseling process, and it ensures that any information shared between a client and counselor is kept private and secure. Confidentiality is crucial for building trust between the client and counselor and creating a safe, non-judgmental environment for the client to explore their thoughts and feelings.  In general, confidentiality works as follows:   </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-confidentiality-work.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bengaluru to BR Hills and KGudi Solo Trip plan</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bengaluru-to-br-hills-and-kgudi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
    <description>One day trip or Two day trip from Bengaluru to BR Hills and KGudi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in BR Hills and KGudi.  BR Hills is a Hill range, also a tiger reserve, also a temple of Lord Ranganathaswamy which attracts people to visit BR Hills. Once in two years, the Soliga Tribals pre</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bengaluru-to-br-hills-and-kgudi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Indian style Spanish omelette, Egg + Potato + Onion</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</link>
    <description>Egg with Potato plus Onion will make a delicious and healthy breakfast, You have have it as a Breakfast or you can have it as a Snack in the day, will also be a great starter in the barbecue. This combination of dish is called Spanish omelette, but lets make it in Indian Style.  Ingredients Needed?  3 Eggs, 4 medium sized Potato (chopped in small) &amp;amp; 4 medium sized Onion (chopped in small), 4-5</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Ghati Subramanya (Solo Morning Ride Plan)</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/short-trip-from-bangalore-to-ghati.html</link>
    <description>One day trip from Bengaluru to Ghati Subramanya, If you are&amp;nbsp;Solo&amp;nbsp;riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this plan works very well to cover places in Ghati Subramanya.  Ghati Subramanya&amp;nbsp;is an ancient Hindu temple, 50 kms away from Bangalore towards Doddaballapur situated on the outskirts of Bangalore. Ghati Subramanya has a recorded&amp;nbsp;history of more than</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 12 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/short-trip-from-bangalore-to-ghati.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>What happens in counseling sessions?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happens-in-counseling-sessions.html</link>
    <description>In a counseling session, a trained professional known as a counselor or therapist works with an individual or group to help them explore and address personal, social, or psychological issues.  The specific activities and techniques used in a counseling session can vary depending on the client&amp;#39;s needs and the counselor&amp;#39;s approach, but in general, a counseling session may involve the followi</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happens-in-counseling-sessions.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>When should one seek counseling?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-should-one-seek-counseling.html</link>
    <description>There are several situations in which seeking counseling may be helpful. Here are some common reasons why people seek counseling:   Mental health concerns: If you are experiencing symptoms of a mental health condition, such as depression, anxiety, or post-traumatic stress disorder, counseling can help you to manage these symptoms and develop coping strategies. Relationship issues: Counseling can b</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-should-one-seek-counseling.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Checklist for building an Eco-Friendly Home</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</link>
    <description>To build a home, which makes low-impact environmentally. And built using materials &amp;amp; technology that lowers its energy needs in future. And also make sure built home is reliable for few decades with minimal energy spent on it.  To do this, you have to consider Energy? what Sustainable materials to be used? how it impacts on our health? And what is costs  Before getting into the details of each</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>UnConditional Love in a Couples Relationship</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</link>
    <description>It is commonly said that Women are complex in mental nature while Men remain easy to understand and simple. Whatever be the reasons that backup this comment,&amp;nbsp;in relationships both Men and Women follow slightly diverted paths.&amp;nbsp;What Men look for in a relationship is not what motivates Women to fall in relationships. The differences in desires, mentalities, passion, expression levels etc., </description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Multisite Local environment setup with DDEV and Drupal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-ddev-and-drupal.html</link>
    <description>In this article we are going to see how we can set up a multisite environment with ddev on the local machine. Assuming people are aware of configuring the drupal multiple site from the drupal side of configurations.  As we all know ddev is an open source tool for running local PHP development environments in minutes, which makes developer life easier during the local environment setup process, her</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-ddev-and-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Mysore Solo Trip plan (2 Days + 1 Night)</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</link>
    <description>Two days Ride from&amp;nbsp;Bangalore to Mysore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for two days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Chamundeshwari</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Egg Stuffed Paratha Home made Recipe</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</link>
    <description>Egg Stuffed Paratha is a delicious and healthy Paratha dish, filled with egg mixture. Both the eggs and whole wheat are healthy as it provides the right amount of proteins and carbs. The egg mixture has finely chopped onions, green chili and coriander leaves. This is then slided into the half cooked paratha pockets and cooked further. The Egg Stuffed Parathas are quite filling in itself.  Ingredie</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Courtship time, Make it memorable, ways to add some spice</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/courtship-time-make-it-memorable-ways-to-add-some-spice.html</link>
    <description>Finally you found a guy or girl with whom you can&amp;#39;t wait to start most excitement time of your life. But you see lot of time for wedding and So you got lot of time to know each other even more better. The Best you can do is make this time memorable.  1. Wedding planning, will be best time pass for each of you.  Hmm, Obviously meeting in person in this courtship period would happen with this we</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/courtship-time-make-it-memorable-ways-to-add-some-spice.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Secure your Web Application's Reset Password flow</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-your-applications-reset-password-flow.html</link>
    <description>Generally any application framework provides users to have a flow to reset the passwords by default, It is more like, use clicking on the Reset Password link and redirects to a page where he will asked for email, and reset link sent to users email, so that user can reset the password on their own.  This is a default or general flow that any application framework provides, but developers or archite</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-your-applications-reset-password-flow.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Kochi Solo Trip plan</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
    <description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Kochi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Kochi and one couple more quick visits in Mysore, Ooty and Coimbatore on the way.  Kochi, called as Queen of the Arabian Sea, is one of the major port cities in the coast of India and also has trading from 14th century</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 20 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Expectations and Freedom in a Relationship</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</link>
    <description>People having expectations in a relationship and willing to have freedom in relationships are few of the main reasons for not having a peaceful and healthy relationship with each other.  Having or Setting some unrealistic expectations to have in a relationship can contribute to ending their marriage.  Honestly both the people should be open in communication to each other in terms of the expectatio</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How does Captcha know that I'm not a Robot?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-captcha-know-that-iam-not-robot.html</link>
    <description>Almost all the developers working on web applications would have come across captcha or re-captcha.  And developers might have also used them on the web pages before authentication of users on web applications or before showing specific content to users.  As developers, we might have got a thought like how will this work behind the scenes, but in most of the cases, we developers would have ignored</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-captcha-know-that-iam-not-robot.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Colima, similar tool like Docker Desktop, for Drupal Development</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</link>
    <description>Colima is a project that is easy to use and fully open source, and it helps in running docker containers on Linux OS and MacOs machines.  We know Docker Desktop is no more a complete open source, if you are not using it personally. So now Colima is a tool which does work similar to Docker Desktop and In this article we are going to see how it works alone or along with Docker Desktop on your Linux </description>
    <pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Eight vegetables that can be grown at Home</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</link>
    <description>In this article we are gonna see eight vegetables that you can grow at your home easily. Chili pepper, Tomato, Garlic, Peas, Raddish, Cabbage, Cauliflower and Carrot are the few vegetables that you can grow at home with less effort.  1. Chili pepper  Chili pepper can be easily grown from seeds, so we need to buy good seeds for better results. Sprinkle seeds over the soil surface, then cover with a</description>
    <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal 10</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal-ten.html</link>
    <description>We developers always choose to have some tools or setup, which makes our lives easier during the development process whether it might be a local environment or higher environments. Not only will lives be easier with such a setup, even the productivity of the individual or team will be increased. And today we are gonna see how Lando will help the drupal developer or drupal development much quicker </description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 12:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal-ten.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Srisailam Solo Trip plan</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
    <description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Srisailam, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Srisailam and one more Shakti Peethas on the way.  Srisailam is one of the places where people get to visit Lord Mallikarjuna (one of the Jyotirlinga) and Goddess Bhramaramba (one of the Ashtadasa Shakti Peetha) in</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Get more Pleasure from Lotus position!</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-more-pleasure-from-lotus-position.html</link>
    <description>People have sexual intercourse in different positions, generally what they most like. And Lotus position is one of the such positions where you get to see and talk to your partner in a relaxed manner during your intimate intercourse.  So what is the Lotus position? - having an&amp;nbsp;intimate&amp;nbsp;intercourse by facing the partner by sitting as close as you both can, wrap your legs around their body</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-more-pleasure-from-lotus-position.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to Have a Better Sex?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-have-a-better-sex.html</link>
    <description>For all people to have a healthy relationship, people need to have healthy communication. Many of us might have ended up with an unsatisfied sex, but did you really communicate this with your partner?  Actually one should not be silent though, ideally should speak about it, but how and when, I would leave it to the people, anyways they have their own ways of presentations and explanations.  Genera</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-have-a-better-sex.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tips to Trust Yourself more!</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-trust-yourself-more.html</link>
    <description>If you are finding the tips to trust yourself more, generally at first it is better to know yourself and what you need will be a great start. Also spending some quality time alone will help you to achieve this.  You might have come across stuff where you lose trust in yourself or sometimes stop yourself to build the trust. Because of this you may make wrong decisions or not be able to make decisio</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 10:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-trust-yourself-more.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal 10 is coming in a few days!</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-ten-is-coming-in-a-few-days.html</link>
    <description>Drupal 10 is planned to be released in December 2022. Drupal 10 will be straightforward upgrades like Drupal 8 to 9. Upgrade processes used are more or less similar. Mostly you need to keep your current site up to date with the latest drupal core and contributed projects.  What is new in Drupal 10?  Drupal 10 is a refined version of Drupal 9 with the certain features   Claro administration theme i</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-ten-is-coming-in-a-few-days.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>People still say yes to Condoms, instead of Birth Control</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-still-say-yes-to-condoms-instead-of-birth-control.html</link>
    <description>Generally when you don&amp;rsquo;t want to get any&amp;nbsp;byproduct out of your pleasure, then you tend to have birth control or an IUD, Intrauterine device or an Implant. But many people will still prefer to&amp;nbsp;use condoms instead&amp;nbsp;of other stuff. I think there are many good reasons behind that, let&amp;#39;s see what are those.   Easy available method to avoid Pregnancy or any STIs No need of a Pres</description>
    <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-still-say-yes-to-condoms-instead-of-birth-control.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Pondicherry Solo Trip plan</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-pondicherry-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
    <description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Pondicherry, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well.  Among the touristers Pondicherry is famous for its rich French essence of architecture of buildings in the White town area. Also it&amp;#39;s famous for beaches and it&amp;#39;s one of the good places for Solo travelers. Let&amp;#3</description>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 16:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-pondicherry-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Project vs Product - Plan and Delivery, Agile Characteristics</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/project-vs-product-plan-and-delivery-agile-characteristics.html</link>
    <description>In the Service Industry, a Technical Lead or Technical Architect or Delivery Manager, one is always looking at the work, either as a Project or a Product, but I say, one should look at it as both, because work would be a Project for us but work would be a Product for the clients.  While working on Agile basis, being at the leading positions one will be seeing the scope of work, then prepare the ba</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/project-vs-product-plan-and-delivery-agile-characteristics.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Lepakshi Solo Trip Plan</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
    <description>One day trip from Bangalore to Lepakshi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this one day plan works very well.  Lepakshi is a small village located in Anantapur district, Andhra Pradesh. It is around 120 KM from Bangalore. It is famous for Veerabhadra temple, one of the oldest temples in India. The temple has Ganesha, Nandi, Veerabhadra, Shiva, Bhadrak</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Everest Base Camp Trek, Start Trekking from Salleri and back to Salleri</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</link>
    <description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of where you can start your trek. I have read through many articles &amp;amp; videos and found the best route for trekking.  Generally people all over the world will reach Kathmandu and then take a flight to Lukla and start the trek to Everest base camp from Lukla.  In case you are n</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
    <description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Usage of Constraints (Validations) on Media Entities in Drupal Application</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-constraints-validations-on-media-entities-in-drupal-application.html</link>
    <description>In this article we are going to see how drupal developers can use the Drupal Constraints to Validate the Media entities.  Basically Drupal provides Constraints to do the Validations on the Entities, where Drupal uses the Symfony&amp;rsquo;s validator and extends with Symfony&amp;rsquo;s Typed Data API for validating specific Entity field definitions.  These constraint validators can be used in different w</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-constraints-validations-on-media-entities-in-drupal-application.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>INS Vikrant Delivered to Indian Navy, First Indigenous Aircraft Carrier by India</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</link>
    <description>INS Vikrant which is also known as Indigenous Aircraft Carrier 1 (IAC-1). It is the first aircraft carrier to be built in India. This is an Aircraft Carrier constructed by the Cochin Shipyard Limited (CSL) for the Indian Navy.  The name Vikrant means courageous in Sanskrit. The motto of the ship is Jayema Saṁ Yudhi Sprdhah, which means I defeat those who fight against me.  Brief of the backgroun</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, Bangalore to Kathmandu then to Salleri</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</link>
    <description>If you are planning to trek Solo to Everest Base Camp by yourself from Bangalore, then this article will help you to get a picture of how to reach Salleri from Bangalore, where Salleri will be the starting point of Trek to Everest Base Camp.  There are many possible routes to reach Kathmandu from Bangalore.   Flight  There are direct flights from Bangalore to Kathmandu and vice versa. You also hav</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tips to Overcome Suicidal Thoughts</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-overcome-suicidal-thoughts.html</link>
    <description>When you are having suicidal thoughts, first thing you need to tell your mind is you can overcome this, whatever the problem or situation is, you can overcome.  Suicidal thoughts are very difficult to handle or they are difficult to understand or explain. Sometimes they can be just going around your mind or sometimes they can become a thing, which you wish to do right away. In either case you have</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-overcome-suicidal-thoughts.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Growing enough Onions to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
    <description>Onions are easy to grow, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. They need less attention during the growth when compared to other plants.  Onions will be having flavonoids, which have both an antioxidant and anti-inflammatory effect. By eating them regularly in sufficient quantities, these components will help people to protect themselves from chronic conditions such as ca</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Monkeypox Outbreak around the World in 2022</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</link>
    <description>The outbreak of monkeypox, which is a viral disease, was confirmed in May 2022, once few cases were found in the United Kingdom. The first case was detected on 6th May 2022 and confirmed this case had travel links to Nigeria (where the disease is endemic).  From 18th May 2022 onwards, there was an increase in cases in Europe, North and South America, Asia, Africa, and Australia.  As of 23rd July 2</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Stop Overthinking your Thoughts of Future</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</link>
    <description>Overthinking your thoughts will lead you to even more worry. If you are an overthinker or a person who thinks to take precautions for the future, then you will know exactly how it goes. Generally a problem comes to your mind, for example a worry or health or a problem at work or some sort of issue in a relationship, because of the thoughts you will be thinking about it a lot and you will try to ge</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Usage of Local Php Security Checker for Drupal Applications</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to see how the Local PHP Security Checker library will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated security review. Here comes the Local PHP Security Checker library, which checks for any known vulnerabilities in the package dependencies.  Th</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Droupadi Murmu, New President of India</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</link>
    <description>Droupadi Murmu was nominated to President elections and on 21st of July 2022 elections counting was finished and Droupadi Murmu won the elections and will be the New President of India, Murmu is likely to take oath on July 25 as President of India.  A few highlights of 15th President of India   Droupadi Murmu will be the first person belonging to a Scheduled Tribe (ST) community to be elected as t</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Solo Travel to Gokarna for Three Nights and Four Days</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</link>
    <description>You are planning to visit Gokarna solo then here is the article which will help you to plan your trip. And this plan in this article is for three days and four nights and for a person who wants to travel solo.  If you are traveling from Bangalore, overnight bus or a train will be the best option for travel to Gokarna. And if you wish to travel via flight, the nearest airport for people will be eit</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Complete Guide to Setup and Usage Solar Panels at Home</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</link>
    <description>Going green is the best of the environment and if you are planning to go green, then we all know Sun is the non-renewable energy and we could use this energy for people&amp;#39;s survival. We have a few articles at PeoplesBLOG related to the Environment and going green, have a check of them.  Using the Electricity from Solar energy is one of the best combinations, because there is not much waste out o</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Growing enough Tomatoes to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
    <description>In this article we are gonna see how they can grow tomatoes at their home and with the help of just other tomatoes at home. We have a few other articles which help to grow vegetables at home, you can read them from here.  Generally tomatoes are used in the kitchen for almost all the curries in South Indian dishes.  Tomatoes are rich in Vitamin B9, Vitamin C and Potassium and these Antioxidants pro</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Cooking Food with Solar Power at Home</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
    <description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Read Data to Paragraph Template in Drupal Application</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/read-data-to-paragraph-template-in-drupal-application.html</link>
    <description>In this article we are going to see how to read the dynamic data of the node or entity or field values to the template file, which are specific to the paragraph template.  Generally while the Paragraph module is used, default template suggestions given by the paragraph module or the template suggestions provided by the hooks are used and further template design is done. Here&amp;rsquo;s the article wh</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/read-data-to-paragraph-template-in-drupal-application.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tips for Night Driving on Motorcycle on Roads and Highways</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-for-night-driving-on-motorcycle-on-roads-and-highways.html</link>
    <description>Driving during night will have few advantages and yes it comes with being very careful and prepared as well. And sharing this article particularly for the Motorcycle riders.  Night driving will have few advantages for people, like no need to worry about the huge traffic because most of the people will be sleeping, And you will not get tired like you get tired in the daytime, And most of the night </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-for-night-driving-on-motorcycle-on-roads-and-highways.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Growing enough Pudina to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
    <description>Pudina is easy to grow and hard to kill, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. It&amp;#39;s especially known for its soothing effect on the stomach.  Pudina is a fast growing plant, it&amp;#39;s good to keep it in a pot or a container with some boundary, so that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take up all your garden or yard.  If people buy Pudina from a market or get Punida from a neighbor&amp;#39</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to work with Drupal Paragraphs?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</link>
    <description>Paragraphs can be used as a way for Content Creation in Drupal. It actually allows the site builders to do their stuff a bit cleanly and for the end users this will be pretty easy to manage the content, meaning people get more control on the Editing side.  Paragraphs is one of the&amp;nbsp; popular modules in Drupal, for handling content. It is more or less very similar to the fields and will provide </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Growing enough Broccoli to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
    <description>Broccoli is worth growing for its nutritional content value. This is rich in Vitamins and Minerals and is a good source of Vitamin A, Potassium, Folic acid, Iron and Fiber.  Broccoli is a cool seasonal crop, so it should be started in early winters. September and October are the best months for seed germination.  Germination Process?   You can start seeds in almost any type of container as long as</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Help People to recognize the Physical Signs of Stress and Manage the Stress</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/help-people-to-recognize-the-physical-signs-of-stress-and-manage-the-stress.html</link>
    <description>Actually stress symptoms may be affecting your health in one or the other way, even though you might not actually realise it. You might think, the stress you are facing is because of your Life or Work or the stuff which you are doing, but it cannot be true.  The true reason for having stress could be that you are not able to manage the stress properly. And this Stress will lead people to not be pr</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/help-people-to-recognize-the-physical-signs-of-stress-and-manage-the-stress.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>President of India nominated Veerendra Heggade, P.T. Usha, Ilaiyaraaja and V. Vijayendra Prasad to the Rajya Sabha</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</link>
    <description>According to the Fourth Schedule (Articles 4(1) and 80(2)) of the Constitution of India, The President of India can nominate 12 members to Rajya Sabha for a term of six-years for their contributions towards Arts, Literature, Sciences, and Social Services.  Maybe earlier most of the South Indian peoples, for this matter all the Indian people might not be aware that The President of India can nomina</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, What to pack?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</link>
    <description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of what you might need to pack in your backpack. Packing proper equipment, clothing &amp;amp; quick energy foods will help you to do your trek bit smoothly.  One more important thing, is this plan would fit for the people who are willing to trek solo (without a porter), so what you a</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Usage of PhpStan on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development and code review process. We have a similar helpful article related to Phpcs, have a check of this.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here come</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Pudina chutney Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
    <description>Pudina Chutney is a flavorful condiment and aromatic chutney to serve with rice, mudde, idli, dosa. Pudina Chutney can also be served with snacks like bonda, bajji too.  People sometimes are confused pudina chutney with mint chutney or green chutney that is served along with chats and tandoori platter, but it&amp;#39;s not the same which we serve with rice or mudde or idle, and this chutney is more au</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to charge a Mobile phone with Solar power?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to see what all options we have to charge a mobile phone with Solar power.  If you are going on treks which are primarily overnight or a few days of trek in some isolated place. In such cases obviously we won&amp;rsquo;t get any electrical power, In such cases for people Solar energy would be an alternative option to keep your device charged.  And let&amp;rsquo;s see what all</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
    <description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>How to work with Twig Templates in Drupal?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to see how a developer can work with Twig templates, and how to override templates (if needed) and create template suggestions with hooks, so that templates could be easily managed.  Basically drupal allows people to override the existing twig templates, so that people can fully have control on the html generated via the custom theme.  First thing, we need to make sur</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Quick reference of Code Reviews for Drupal Application</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</link>
    <description>In this article we are going to see how your Drupal team can do code reviews and available tools or libraries which help people in the team to do the code reviews seamlessly.  It&amp;rsquo;s pretty important to follow a few guidelines as well, so that all people or developers in the team are on the same page.  Firstly, for the code reviews to be at their best, the committed code should be more organis</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Usage of PHPCS on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  And to make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here comes the PHP codesniffer and Drupal coder module.  If you are maintaini</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Why do people Worship?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-worship.html</link>
    <description>Based on the history and the observation, I can say everyone or every individual would or will look up for someone or something. And the society will revolve around what or who look for and what or who don&amp;rsquo;t look for.  I see this as people searching for the meaning of the purpose of their existence.  We (people) will compare each other&amp;#39;s likes or dislikes, love or hate, and it&amp;#39;s a no</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-worship.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Store Secrets Securely on Pantheon for Drupal Application</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-secrets-securely-on-pantheon-for-drupal-application.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to see how people can store access keys and tokens securely, in the case of your drupal application that is managed on pantheon.  Generally, all the Access keys or Tokens or any Secret third party auth information should not be stored in the database or within the project web root, Its safe to store it encrypted and within a file, and keep the file outside of the proj</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-secrets-securely-on-pantheon-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Configuration management via Quicksilver on Pantheon</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuration-management-via-quicksilver-on-pantheon.html</link>
    <description>As we saw in the earlier article, like how we manage the configuration across the environments.  In this article we are going to see how Drupal configurations can be deployed or imported across the environments with the help of Quicksilver which hooks into platform workflows to automate your Pantheon WebOps workflow across the environments.  In the pantheon environment&amp;rsquo;s drupal code base, yo</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuration-management-via-quicksilver-on-pantheon.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal Configuration management (Local, Dev, Test and Live)</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-configuration-management-local-dev-test-and-live.html</link>
    <description>In this article we are going to see how Drupal serves configurations across the environments, which can be well maintained with help of some contributed modules and version control.  Drupal 8 onwards configuration has been saved in the yml files in a consistent manner, which includes all the enabled modules, all the content types, vocabularies, fields &amp;amp; views.  Making the configurations direct</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-configuration-management-local-dev-test-and-live.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Unconditional love...</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unconditional-love.html</link>
    <description>To say, it is a love without any strings attached and selfless.  It is about acceptance. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t associate with outward appearance, supports the other person by always being there and doesn&amp;rsquo;t go away even when circumstances are bad or difficult.  It can be understood as without any reservations, without judgements, caring about the happiness of the other person without expecting any</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unconditional-love.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Friend, What comes to your mind, When you hear this word?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/friend-what-comes-to-your-mind-when-you-hear-this-word.html</link>
    <description>One line would be someone whom we are fond of talking to or spending time with.  Usually, he/she is someone apart from a family member, with whom you share a good bond, which might be fun, compassion, empathy, or maybe a few common interests with them.  Seldom, friendships are formed among unexpected people and in uncertain circumstances.&amp;nbsp; Whatever it may be, there is a belief that we meet pe</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/friend-what-comes-to-your-mind-when-you-hear-this-word.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Dream, Small Information on it…</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dream-small-info-on-it.html</link>
    <description>Have you ever dreamed about something like people you have known in life, a place you are very familiar with, some incident that disturbs your mental peace, meeting an unknown person, or exploring a far distant place?  Of course, all of us dream, that’s a natural phenomenon that happens with everyone. Sometimes dreams give us a good feeling which refreshes our life or a bad feeling which keeps u</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dream-small-info-on-it.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Migrate your site from Drupal 7 To Drupal 9?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate-your-site-from-drupal-seven-to-drupal-nine.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to see what are the important things you need to understand for the migration of your Drupal 7 site to the Drupal 9 site. And if you see from your Business perspective, Drupal 7 was launched nine years ago, and this is the perfect time for some reassessment of the needs of site users &amp; content managers. And if you see from Drupal’s end, Initially, Drupal 7 end of li</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate-your-site-from-drupal-seven-to-drupal-nine.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Get to know one's Personality Type</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-to-know-ones-personality-type.html</link>
    <description>Myers-Briggs Personality Type Way to identify the personality type of the person, his/her strengths, and preferences in life. Based on the set of questions and answers to it, one’s personality type can be assessed. So, here we go, choose your response, and pick the letter corresponding to that set of questions if you agree. The questions fall under four categories which are described below. 1. A</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-to-know-ones-personality-type.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Do you know? Your Brain is the biggest Sex organ!</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-you-know-your-brain-is-the-biggest-sex-organ.html</link>
    <description>Experiencing our sexuality has a lot to do with bodies, like how we like to touch and be touched by our partner. And when we think of the sex organs,&amp;nbsp;our minds think toward&amp;nbsp;the naughty parts between our legs, but our minds should be doing this right.  The&amp;nbsp;real catalyst for sexual activity&amp;nbsp;is the brain, actually not entirty brain, but specific parts of the brain, and it&amp;rsquo;s </description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-you-know-your-brain-is-the-biggest-sex-organ.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Having Good Sex at any Age! Is it Really Possible?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/having-good-sex-at-any-age-is-it-really-possible.html</link>
    <description>No matter what is your gender, you can always enjoy sex for as long as you wish. And naturally sex at age of 70 or 80&amp;nbsp;may not be same&amp;nbsp;like it is at would be at 20 or 30, but It would be better in some ways.  Sex can be one of the powerful emotional experience and one of the great tool for protecting or improving your health, And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean, you can have it only at young age. Y</description>
    <pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/having-good-sex-at-any-age-is-it-really-possible.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Improve Drupal Search with Solr, Locally configured via Lando</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/improve-drupal-search-with-solr-locally-configured-via-lando.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to learn how Drupal search can be improved with Solr which provides great performance, and is suitable even for use on large commercial websites. And along with this using the search_api &amp; search_api_solr modules, helps to configure the Facets &amp; Multilingual content can be handled in an improved manner. And let's see how we can configure this locally with the help of </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/improve-drupal-search-with-solr-locally-configured-via-lando.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>When to use hook_update_N &amp; hook_post_update_NAME?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-to-use-hook_update_n-and-hook_post_update_name.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to learn when to use hook_update_N and hook_post_update_NAME. In general, I was using hook_update_N for any database-related changes or with any configuration additions or updates. And I was using hook_post_update_NAME for any content creation or updating or for the creation or updating any taxonomy terms etc, sometimes for clearing site caches as well. But, let’s h</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-to-use-hook_update_n-and-hook_post_update_name.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Why Madanapalle should be headquarters of proposed Annamayya District?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-madanapalle-should-be-the-headquarters-of-the-proposed-annamayya-district.html</link>
    <description>There are many reasons for Madanapalle to be the headquarters of the proposed Annamayya district in almost all aspects. Madanapalle is a city in the Chittoor district of the Indian state of Andhra Pradesh. Madanapalli was founded by Sri Maadanna in 1618 AD. One of the oldest towns. In 1850, Madanapalle was developed as Sub Division and had the First Sub Collector. Rabindranath Tagore translated Ja</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-madanapalle-should-be-the-headquarters-of-the-proposed-annamayya-district.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Pachi Chintakaya Pachadi Recipe, Andhra Style</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
    <description>Andhra Style Pachi chintakaya pachadi (Green raw tamarind pickle) is an age-old dish, which is generally eaten with Rice &amp; some also eaten with Ghee for even better taste. As we Indians love the tangy &amp; sweetish taste of pickle, this delicious Pachi chintakaya pachadi is enjoyed by all age groups and in fact, the recipe is one among the famous Indian dishes. This dish also has many health benefits</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Improvements for Editor Experience in Drupal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/improvements-for-editor-experience-in-drupal.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we are going to learn what Drupal offers for text editors or content managers as a content management framework within Drupal Core &amp; Contributed modules. Earlier versions of Drupal have several useful features to help content editors to manage their content on a daily basis. And in the newer versions of Drupal (from when Symfony was introduced), there are a few more improvements i</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/improvements-for-editor-experience-in-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Makalidurga - Trekking</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</link>
    <description>One-day trek from Bangalore to Makalidurga to Bangalore. If you are a couple riding on a Bike or you are a Family driving in a Car, then this trek plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. Makalidurga is a hill fort situated 60 km north of Bangalore. The fort at the summit has an old temple of Shiva with Nandi and in legend, Markandeya Rishi performed penan</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Core</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-drupal-offers-as-responsive-web-design-within-core.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we gonna see What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Drupal Core for developers. While Drupal 8 was out and it had a buzz of being responsive, mobile friendly. And yes, the Internet is on the verge of being dominated by smartphones &amp; Drupal needs to be prepared.Mobile friendly will also mean the content is first. From a big screen to a little screen, elements would look</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-drupal-offers-as-responsive-web-design-within-core.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Know why Symfony framework was picked by Drupal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/know-why-symfony-framework-was-picked-by-drupal.html</link>
    <description>In this article, we gonna see why Symfony was picked for Drupal and what it changes for developers. As we all know PHP evolved rapidly in the past years, and unfortunately, Drupal adjustment to this development was not satisfying, especially in the case of software engineering patterns adoption. And that is one of the reasons why Drupal Developers had to come up with creative ways to deal with suc</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/know-why-symfony-framework-was-picked-by-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Understand why Twig is replacing PHP Template in Drupal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understand-why-twig-is-replacing-php-template-in-drupal.html</link>
    <description>A completely new template engine is introduced in Drupal. The templating system in all previous versions of Drupal is using theme_* functions and PHP-based *.tpl.php files. Now, this has been completely replaced in Drupal 8. Instead of using theme functions and theme template files, Drupal is now using the Twig templating system.
                            Twig is a PHP-based compiled templating </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understand-why-twig-is-replacing-php-template-in-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Gandikota (Two Days and One Night, Trip Plan)</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-gandikota-two-days-one-night-trip-plan.html</link>
    <description>Two Days Trip from Bangalore to Gandikota to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on a Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly.
                            A couple of the best places you can visit on the way or around are Lakshmi Narasimha Swamy temple in Kadiri &amp; Belum Caves in Kolimigundla.
  </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-gandikota-two-days-one-night-trip-plan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>In layman's terms, Services &amp; Dependency Injection in Drupal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/in-laymans-terms-services-and-dependency-injection-in-drupal.html</link>
    <description>If we look into the basis of Software engineering, Dependency Injection is an approach in which one object get another object that it depends on. And these other objects are called dependencies. And Injection refers to the passing of a dependency (as a service) into the client object that would use it.
                            With Dependency Injection, the class is no longer responsible for in</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/in-laymans-terms-services-and-dependency-injection-in-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal Cache Clear &amp; Cache Rebuild</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-cache-clear-and-cache-rebuild.html</link>
    <description>In order to render a page via Drupal, Drupal will need to make several database queries and get the data to render. This process of making queries can be reduced by storing the web pages in a cache, which is what Drupal does.
                            And developers during developments may use this cache clear or cache rebuild quite often, like after installing a new module or theme. The site wo</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-cache-clear-and-cache-rebuild.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Multisite Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</link>
    <description>As we have seen in the earlier article to setup the Local environment with Lando &amp; Drupal, Now let's see how we set up the multisite with the lando.
                            And hope you are already aware of Drupal Multisite. If not, It is a feature of Drupal that allows you to run multiple Drupal installs off of a common codebase. This allows you to share themes and modules between a collectio</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>What to Know for Estimating Projects</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-for-estimating-projects.html</link>
    <description>Estimating projects is part of project management. And we can’t always estimate a project with 100% accuracy. There will be learning from the failed attempts at estimating projects, maybe with running overtime, or with budget, or with resources etc.
                            If one needs to deliver a project successfully then one must estimate the project as better as possible.
               </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-for-estimating-projects.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Studies estimate long COVID-19 has over two hundred Symptoms</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</link>
    <description>According to a Lancet's journal EClinicalMedicine, In the Coronavirus (Covid-19) patients who are facing prolonged symptoms have reported more than 200 symptoms across 10 organ systems.
                            They have analysed the responses of 3,762 peoples from 56 different countries with confirmed or suspected Covid-19. And the data were collected from September 6, 2020, to November 25, 20</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</link>
    <description>We developers always choose to have some tools or setup, which makes our lives easier during the development process whether it might be a local environment or higher environments. Not only will lives be easier with such a setup, even the productivity of the individual or team will be increased. And today we are gonna see how Lando will help the drupal developer or drupal development much more qui</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Fix SSL error 61 in Citrix Web Receiver on Ubuntu</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-ssl-error-in-citrix-web-receiver-on-ubuntu.html</link>
    <description>This article is about fixing only a single error which you see with Citrix Web Receiver on the Ubuntu machines. This might be a simple &amp; specific issue, but people who are facing this issue will really feel grateful with the solution provided.
                                After you install the Citrix web receiver on Ubuntu machine &amp; while you try to connect, in some cases no connection to syste</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-ssl-error-in-citrix-web-receiver-on-ubuntu.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>South Indian Hindu Marriage - Andhra Style</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</link>
    <description>South Indian weddings are traditionally going to be planned or happen for one or more than a day, which involve having mehndi for the bride particularly, in some cases times groom as well have mehndi. Few of the south Indians have Haldi ceremonies as well. Groom's arrival itself is celebrated. And the wedding ceremony begins with a few pooja’s &amp; traditions. And at the end, the couple will be sen</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Precautions while travelling during Coronavirus times</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/precautions-while-travelling-during-coronavirus-times.html</link>
    <description>It is not completely safe to travel during the Coronavirus times. Although the mortality rate of the people affected with COVID appears to be quite low, there is always a chance with the data which we get in our country. I see one should avoid travelling as much as possible so that we reduce the chances of spreading the virus.
                                Following are some of the things to be </description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/precautions-while-travelling-during-coronavirus-times.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Why to have a Green Roof or Eco Friendly Roof on a Building</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-to-have-a-green-roof-or-eco-friendly-roof-on-a-building.html</link>
    <description>A roof of a building that is partially or completely covered with vegetation, that is planted over a waterproofing membrane. It may also include additional layers such as a root barrier and drainage and irrigation systems. Rooftop ponds are another form of green roofs which are used to treat greywater.
                                Vegetation, soil, drainage layer, roof barrier and irrigation sy</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-to-have-a-green-roof-or-eco-friendly-roof-on-a-building.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Security Hardening - Nginx Response Headers</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-hardening-nginx-response-headers.html</link>
    <description>Now-a-days, web based attacks are one of the most common types of cybercrime, and in most cases, the attacked protocol is the HTTP, while the component that receives the attacks is the web server. Hardening Nginx HTTP headers becomes necessary for reducing any attacks to the web server.
                                And how to harden Nginx response HTTP headers? - HTTP headers are pieces of info</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-hardening-nginx-response-headers.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Pachi Pulusu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
    <description>Andhra Style Pachi Pulusu Recipe is a thin rasam made with freshly extracted tamarind water and mixed with sliced onions and freshly cut coriander leaves. Comfort food at its best when served with some steamed rice for a simple meal.
                                It is a different way of creating a rasam that has been followed by the people from Andhra Pradesh and Telangana. This rasam is not he</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Black Fungus - Detected in Coronavirus Patients</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</link>
    <description>Black fungus is an infection caused by a fungus named mucormycosis. This fungal infection is being reported in a few Corona-affected patients during or post-recovery.
                                People catch mucormycosis when they come in contact with the fungal spores in the environment. It can also be contacted through skin contact through a cut, burn, or any other form of skin trauma.
     </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Coping up with Life in an Effective Way</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coping-up-with-life-in-an-effective-way.html</link>
    <description>Life tends to go on as we go on with our daily routine works. Whatever stage of life you are in now, one has things to do, atleast to take care of family by providing what they need by doing what one can do.
                                You can play a major role in that process of fulfilling your responsibilities or a minor role, but your contribution is what makes a difference, if one apprecia</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coping-up-with-life-in-an-effective-way.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Dealing with Uncertainty, To Be Happier and Less Anxious</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dealing-with-uncertainty-to-be-happier-and-less-anxious.html</link>
    <description>Uncertainty is everywhere. It might be a pandemic like Covid, Health, Finances, Relationships etc at most everywhere we see uncertainty. We human beings always want to feel safe &amp; want to have control over our life. Uncertainity and Fear along with uncertainity will make us feeling stressed, anxious &amp; we feel like, we are missing the direction of our life. It can also put us into that thought of "</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Hanukkah John</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dealing-with-uncertainty-to-be-happier-and-less-anxious.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Raw Mango Chutney - Andhra Style</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
    <description>Raw mango chutney is a flavorful condiment made with raw mangos, coriander leaves, onions and some spices. Raw Mango Chutney is a must-try recipe when raw mangoes are in season. Raw mangoes are packed with minerals and vitamins and are good to beat the summer heat.
                                This raw mango chutney aids digestion and enhances the taste, aroma, and nutrition of any dish. We usu</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Oranges - Let us know how to peel off &amp; eat; along with its benefits</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/oranges-let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</link>
    <description>Ever heard of that name, it’s a fruit which helps us to boost our immunity levels and lowers the risk of diseases.
                                In this lockdown time, one day I felt very tired, couldn’t continue my routine life, and coincidently, all my family members were affected with some or other illness like headache, cough, cold, backache and tiredness to do mundane things.
          </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/oranges-let-us-know-how-to-peel-off-eat-along-with-its-benefits.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Is Feedback really necessary in Person's Life?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-feedback-really-necessary-in-persons-life.html</link>
    <description>Is feedback really necessary? Do people really care about the given feedback? Do people really care to give feedback? It all depends on the situation and people, whether to give or take the given feedback. And honestly everyone has their own views to consider or not to consider the feedback.
                                Every individual might have come across many people giving/taking the feedb</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-feedback-really-necessary-in-persons-life.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal 7 to Drupal 8/9 Audits</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal--to-drupalaudits.html</link>
    <description>Migration from Drupal 7 to Drupal 8/9 is more of a re-build than a simple upgrade. We can move the content. users and other configuration with the help of core system, But still their will be a need to re-write custom modules or themes and some times contrib ones as well. By having a list which helps us to Audit any D7 Project to Drupal 8/9 migration would help start quick.
                       </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal--to-drupalaudits.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Tirumala (2 Days + 1 Night)</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tirumala-two-days-trip.html</link>
    <description>Two days Trip from Bangalore to Tirumala to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on bike or you are a family driving in car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. You can book the Dharshna Tickets &amp; Stay via Online Booking or you can get it once you reach their based on the Crowd on Tirumala.
                                Tirumala </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tirumala-two-days-trip.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Technical Writing Vs Content Writing</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/technical-writing-vs-content-writing.html</link>
    <description>While we see at the first time, we might see Technical Writing and Content Writing career paths to be similar. But in reality these two are differnt in concepts.
                                Technical writer would have an excellent grip on the technical abilities which would help to work in various domains. While Content writer would a precise attention grabbing writing style which makes the re</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/technical-writing-vs-content-writing.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>For Indian Youth..! What should you know about Nambi Narayanan?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-indian-youth-what-should-you-know-about-nambi-narayanan.html</link>
    <description>Lets see the background,
                                In 1992, India signed an agreement with Russia..
                                
                                    Aggrement was for transfer of technology to develop cryogenic fuel-based engines and procurement of two such engines for ₹ 235 crore.
                                    However, Russia did not materialize after the US pres</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-indian-youth-what-should-you-know-about-nambi-narayanan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title> The Shawshank Redemption Movie about Life, Hope, and Freedom</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-shawshank-redemption-movie-about-life-hope-and-freedom.html</link>
    <description>Shawshank Redemption is one of the best movies ever made. Even today its stands above The Godfather movie on the IMDb top rated 250 movies. A must watch movie.
                                Their are many lines in the movie by the characters, which tells about Life, Hope and Freedom. In this article, I'm gona list of few of them.
                                 Thats The Beauty Of Music. They C</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-shawshank-redemption-movie-about-life-hope-and-freedom.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>The Confident You, Taking Charge of Your Life</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-confident-you-taking-charge-of-your-life.html</link>
    <description>Recently I had to attend a virtual session by Transformation Coach and a Psychologist. Where in the session, she was saying about how one can take charge of their own life.. by being confident! It was a great session.. started with, Do you often feel that you have no control over your life? Do you feel that you are just drifting day after day, without any goal and direction?. It was really nice to</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-confident-you-taking-charge-of-your-life.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Heat waves in India and Current Temperature Status and Warning for next five Days</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/heat-waves-in-india-and-current-temperature-status-and-warning-for-next-five-day.html</link>
    <description>In 21st century due to climate changes, global temperature can increase means heat waves would be compartively more. This might affect human health a lot and in some cases can lead to death. We should know that, these heat waves will affect many people in small amount of time.
                                In India, these Heat waves generally occur from March - June, &amp; in some cases, they might </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/heat-waves-in-india-and-current-temperature-status-and-warning-for-next-five-day.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal JSON API, Deep Dive - Part 2</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-deep-dive-part-two.html</link>
    <description>In Part 2, Let's see about the Core concepts like Types, URL structure, HTTP methods, Request headers, Response codes and Document structure i.e Data in the request body. JSON:API module will provide the APIs for Drupal entity types and bundles, where every bundle will have its own unique url path, which will have a shared pattern.
                                Types
                            </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-deep-dive-part-two.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Locally Setup and Scan your Docker images via Clair</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/locally-setup-and-scan-your-docker-images-via-clair.html</link>
    <description>Docker Images contain not only application code, but a OS and additional utilities to make application run as expected. Images can also be vulnerable its better not have any CVE's in image. Running scans are one of the way to protect from CVE's. These container scanning tools scan for known vulnerabilities in the image.
                                In this article, We use Clair to scan a Docker</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/locally-setup-and-scan-your-docker-images-via-clair.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Things to Know before you go for Registration of a Plot or Property in Bangalore</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-before-you-go-for-registration-of-a-plot-in-bangalore.html</link>
    <description>When you decide to buy a property or land than a normal business deal where you get a plot of land in exchange of money. Before going into details of plot registration, there are a few terms you must know.
                                Registration fee - It's a small percentage of total cost of plot paid by buyer to state government for registering property on his name.
                         </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-before-you-go-for-registration-of-a-plot-in-bangalore.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>When Police doesnot register your FIR? Contact Judge!</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-police-doesnot-register-your-fir-contact-judge.html</link>
    <description>If you are reporting a cognisable crime and Police refuse to register your FIR, you can make a complaint to a higher ranking officer such as the Superintendent of Police (SP), the Deputy Inspector General (DIG) or the Inspector General of Police (IGP). You can also complain to the nearest Judicial Magistrate, who will order the police to register the FIR if deemed necessary.
                      </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-police-doesnot-register-your-fir-contact-judge.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Monitoring Web Application with ELK Stack</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monitoring-web-application-with-elk-stack.html</link>
    <description>For Auditing &amp; Troubleshooting issues in an application, log data is very useful. And to make it easy to read the log data via some kind of tool will make developers &amp; maintainers happy. However, not all the log data for any event is not needed to be stored in the log record. Means, Each log record should have only the information needed for further notice or further debugging. Strictly all sensit</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monitoring-web-application-with-elk-stack.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal JSON API, Deep Dive - Part 1</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-deep-dive-part-one.html</link>
    <description>JSON:API module is implemented based on JSON:API Specification. Means, a specification that says how client should request the resources to be fetched or modified, &amp; also how server should respond to such requests. This JSON:API is designed to minimize the number of requests and also minimize the amount of data transmitted between clients &amp; servers. And such efficiency is achieved without compromi</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-deep-dive-part-one.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Privatisation of Public Sector Banks &amp; Banks Strike in March 2021</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/privatisation-of-public-sector-banks-banks-strike-march-.html</link>
    <description>The Finance Minister has announced in Union Budget of India for 2021-22, that two Public Sector Banks (PSBs) will be Privatised. The policy of government in last three decades of economic reforms was to sell a part of shares in Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) including PSBs to public while retaining the controlling share in its own hands.
                                Privatisation of PSBs is </description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/privatisation-of-public-sector-banks-banks-strike-march-.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Lines worth reading, How do we identify ourselves?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lines-worth-reading.html</link>
    <description>Here we go,
                                How do we identify ourselves?
                                By our name, origin, work we do, good or wrong deeds, likes, dislikes etc. the list goes on...
                                Whatever we may choose according to one's mindset about life, anything chosen becomes just a part of us and doesn't stand out alone.
                                We</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lines-worth-reading.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>COVID-19 Vaccination in India, Covishield and Covaxin</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/covid--vaccination-in-india.html</link>
    <description>In January 2021 India started National Vaccination programme against the SARS-CoV-2 virus which has caused the COVID-19 pandemic. The drive prioritises healthcare and frontline workers, and then those over the age of 60, and then those over the age of 45 and suffering from certain comorbidities.
                                In January 2021 Secretary-General of the United Nations Antonio Guterre</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/covid--vaccination-in-india.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>UNSAID CONFESSIONS - Some insights that one can take</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unsaid-confessions.html</link>
    <description>What does confessing something, which concerns you, to one who cares about you, does to your life? Confession means when you admit that you have done something wrong. Here, we have our fellow being Anand, who had an argument with his brother over property issues and ended up not interacting with his brother for years.
                                After 10 years, when he had gone for a health ch</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unsaid-confessions.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Be Aware of Chain Snatchers &amp; Tips to Prevent Chain Snatching</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/be-aware-of-chain-snatchers-tips-to-prevent-chain-snatching.html</link>
    <description>Chain Snatching is one of the crime happening across India by different individuals or gangs. One should be aware while being in public places and should be cautious always. Chain snatching an easy job unlike burglaries, robberies or dacoities. These chain snatchers mostly will be from different places, They will often go to a new places and do their job and leave within hours.
                   </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/be-aware-of-chain-snatchers-tips-to-prevent-chain-snatching.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>World Wildlife Day</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-wildlife-day.html</link>
    <description>On 20 December 2013, United Nations General Assembly (UNGA), in its resolution UN 68/205, decided to proclaim 3 March, the international day of the adoption of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Wild Fauna and Flora (CITES) on the planet raise awareness and benefits fauna and flora in 1973, as World Wildlife Day, which was proposed by Thailand, to celebrate and raise aw</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-wildlife-day.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Things to know about Proofreading</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-about-proofreading.html</link>
    <description>Proofreading is the process of looking for and correcting errors in your work i.e. finding and correcting spelling, grammar, punctuation, consistency and errors.
                            Proofreading is the last step in your writing and editing process.
                            You should have written and edited your work for general coherence and flow before proofreading.
                  </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-about-proofreading.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Reduce the Risk of Becoming a Sexual Assault Victim!</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</link>
    <description>To Reduce the risk for you to becoming a sexual victim, you have to take some preventative measures, which will help you to avoid a risky situations from escalating. Anyone can be the target of sexual assault, regardless of age, gender, race, ethnicity, sexual orientation, sexual history, or social class. There is no stereotypical victim or rapist.
                                What's bad? - Nea</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Lessons Learnt from three years of Relationship</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-learnt-from-three-years-of-relationship.html</link>
    <description>Living together for almost three years is a good amount of journey in your life. For me atleast like, part of me feels like time is absolutely flying and the other half feels like we have been married for three years. We have certainly not been perfect, but I'm gonna share fews lessons which I learnt out of these three years which I spent in my relationship.
                            1. Importan</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-learnt-from-three-years-of-relationship.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Researchers solve riddle of plant immune system</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</link>
    <description>How do plants build resilience? An international research team led by the University of Gottingen studied the molecular mechanisms of the plant immune system. They were able to show a connection between a relatively unknown gene and resistance to pathogens. The results of the study were published in the journal The Plant Cell.
                                Scientists from "PRoTECT" -- Plant Resp</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/researchers-solve-riddle-of-plant-immune-system.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Prime accused in gang-rape case nabbed after two decades</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prime-accused-in-gang-rape-case-nabbed-after-two-decades.html</link>
    <description>Prime accused Bibekananda Biswal in a sensational gangrape that shook Odisha in its aftermath in 1999 is now caught by Police from Aamby Valley in Lonavala in Maharashtra.
                                The incident, that occurred in 1999, had created a state-wide outrage. A total of three persons were accused in the case. Two of them - Pradeep Sahi and Dhirendra Mohanty, were arrested and convic</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prime-accused-in-gang-rape-case-nabbed-after-two-decades.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Coronavirus, Discovered in the 1960s, Serious Respiratory Tract Infections</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coronavirus-discovered-in-the-s-serious-respiratory-tract-infections.html</link>
    <description>Coronaviruses are a group of viruses that cause diseases in mammals and birds that include diarrhea in cows and pigs, and upper respiratory disease in chickens. In humans, the virus causes respiratory infections, which are often mild, but in rare cases are potentially lethal.
                                There are no vaccines or antiviral drugs that are approved for prevention or treatment.
   </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coronavirus-discovered-in-the-s-serious-respiratory-tract-infections.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>International Mother Language Day</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/international-mother-language-day.html</link>
    <description>International Mother Language Day is a worldwide annual observance held on 21st February to promote awareness of linguistic and cultural diversity and to promote multilingualism. First announced by UNESCO on 17 November 1999, it was formally recognized by the United Nations General Assembly with the adoption of UN resolution 56/262 in 2002.
                                Mother Language Day is pa</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/international-mother-language-day.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Tips to Live a Happy Life, How to be Happy?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-live-a-happy-life-how-to-be-happy.html</link>
    <description>What Is Happiness? Happiness is an emotional state characterized by feelings of joy, satisfaction, contentment, and fulfillment. While happiness has many different definitions, it is often described as involving positive emotions and life satisfaction. And Why Happiness is needed in Life? in simple, We become more creative, witty, energetic and fun to be around and it can also lead us to become mo</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-live-a-happy-life-how-to-be-happy.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Rameswaram (3 Days + 2 Nights, Trip Plan)</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</link>
    <description>Three days Trip from Bangalore to Rameswaram to Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Rameshwaram is a small Hindu pilgrimage town a</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>If farmers have greater choice to sell to whoever &amp; wherever! Why still Farmers are protesting?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/if-farmers-have-greater-choice-to-sell-to-whoever-and-wherever.html</link>
    <description>The Rajya Sabha passed two out of the three Bills being referred to as the Farm Bills. These two Bills are the Farmers Produce Trade and Commerce (Promotion and Facilitation) Bill, 2020, and the Farmers (Empowerment and Protection) Agreement on Price Assurance and Farm Services Bill, 2020. The Lok Sabha had already passed these Bills. There was some ruckus in the Rajya Sabha where the Bill was pas</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/if-farmers-have-greater-choice-to-sell-to-whoever-and-wherever.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>World Cancer Day, February 4th - Early detection of Cancer can lead to Improved outcomes &amp; Cure.</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</link>
    <description>Cancer is a large group of diseases that can start in almost any organ or tissue of the body when abnormal cells grow uncontrollably, go beyond their usual boundaries to invade adjoining parts of the body and/or spread to other organs. The latter process is called metastasizing which is a major cause of death from cancer. A neoplasm and malignant tumour are other common names for cancer.
         </description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Benefits of Reading - Why You Should Read?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/benefits-of-reading-why-you-should-read.html</link>
    <description>By the way, when was the last time you read a book, or read an article on internet? Or you generally tend to look across tweets, facebook updates etc. If you are one of them who is not having an habit of reading regularly, you are missing out few things. Actually reading has few benefits, and i'm gona share few of the benefits of reading, so that you start reading!
                                </description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/benefits-of-reading-why-you-should-read.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Send Mail with Custom Email Template &amp; with Dynamic values via Drupal Mail Service</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/send-mail-with-custom-email-template-and-with-dynamic-values-via-drupal-mail-service.html</link>
    <description>Sending an email works with defining an email template (subject, text and possibly email headers) and the replacement values to use in the appropriate places in the template. Processed email templates are requested from hook_mail() from the module sending the email. Any module can modify the composed email message array using hook_mail_alter(). Finally \Drupal::service('plugin.manager.mail')->mail</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/send-mail-with-custom-email-template-and-with-dynamic-values-via-drupal-mail-service.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>API Docs Drupal Module simple way to show OAS Docs on Drupal Portal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/api-docs-drupal-module-simple-way-to-show-oas-api-docs-on-drupal-portal.html</link>
    <description>If you want to show API Documents on your Drupal Portal and you want to do it do it quickly, Here's the module API Docs which solves your purpose. API Docs is a simple module which will will provide a content type for the API Doc and User will be able to create API Documents by just uploading Open API Spec. Each API Doc is a content with this API Docs module.
                                Prereq</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/api-docs-drupal-module-simple-way-to-show-oas-api-docs-on-drupal-portal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Saving Vegetable seeds for your backyard gardening</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/saving-vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</link>
    <description>To become more food self-sufficient, we should plan to collect, store and use some of the seed for your own garden. With this we can create new &amp; custom varieties of vegetables that grow best in our backyard. This can be done with small amount of effort involved. Also you will have fun in the process too.
                                You can save vegetable seeds from your garden produce to plan</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/saving-vegetable-seeds-for-your-backyard-gardening.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Reading a book, it's not my thing; is it your instant reply?</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reading-a-book-its-not-my-thing-is-it-your-instant-reply.html</link>
    <description>Reading a book expands your thinking dimensions and gives a better perspective about things going on around you. If you agree with what you read just now, Let's have a look at two books which make significant changes to one's life.
                                Life is what you make it by Preeti Shenoy
                                This is a wonderful fictional story and it revolves around the</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reading-a-book-its-not-my-thing-is-it-your-instant-reply.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Indian Farms Reforms of 2020</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-farms-reforms-of-.html</link>
    <description>The Indian Farms Reforms of 2020 refer to the agricultural bills passed by the Lok Sabha on 17th September 2020 and by the Rajya Sabha on 20th September 2020. The bills collectively seek to provide farmers with multiple marketing channels and provide a legal framework for farmers to enter into pre-arranged contracts among other things.
                                The President of India gave hi</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-farms-reforms-of-.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>It is OK.. to not be ok !!! - Hanukkah John</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/it-is-ok-to-not-be-ok-hanukkah-john.html</link>
    <description>Ever felt that you are worthless or a burden to others? Ever felt so exhausted mentally? Ever felt sad not for a day or two but for weeks continuously? I'm not talking about grieving over a loss but feeling sad for something which you could have let go easily at least after a day or two.
                                Have you ever found yourself lying in bed all day continuously for days doing n</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Hanukkah John</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/it-is-ok-to-not-be-ok-hanukkah-john.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Rainwater Collection, Storage &amp; Purification</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rain-water-collection-storage-purification.html</link>
    <description>Rainwater Harvesting is the collection &amp; storage of rain water, rather than allowing it to run off. Rainwater is collected from a roof-like surface and redirected to a tank, cistern, deep pit (well, shaft, or borehole), aquifer, or a reservoir with percolation. We can utilize this water for many purposes like, include watering gardens, livestock, irrigation, domestic use with proper treatment, and</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rain-water-collection-storage-purification.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>National Education Policy 2020, Government of India (NEP 2020)</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/national-education-policy-nep.html</link>
    <description>National Education Policy (NEP 2020) has been approved by Union Cabinet on 29 July 2020. Its major aim is to introduce changes in the Indian Education System right from the school to the college level of education. Making India a Global Knowledge Superpower is the ultimate objective of the NEP 2020. It is the third major change in education systems in India since independence in 1947. Earlier two </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/national-education-policy-nep.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Fighting in a Couple's Relationship is Normal</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fighting-in-a-relationship-is-normal.html</link>
    <description>Every Couple will fight &amp; it's completely Normal, unless its scares both of them. No two people are exactly the same way, each of them are unique. Couples can occasionally or often might have conflicts or disagreements which might lead to an argument of fight. If that particular conflict of argument is taken as a healthy discussion, then you will be knowing more about your partner and you both wil</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fighting-in-a-relationship-is-normal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore to Ooty (3 Days + 2 Nights, Trip Plan)</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</link>
    <description>Three days Trip from Bangalore  Ooty  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Ooty known as the Queen of the hill stations in South In</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>World's Fastest Anti-Ship Cruise Missile in Operation</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/worlds-fastest-anti-ship-cruise-missile-in-operation.html</link>
    <description>BrahMos is a medium-range ramjet supersonic cruise missile that can be launched from submarine, ships, aircraft, or land. It is the fastest supersonic cruise missile in the world. It is a joint venture between the Russian Federation's NPO Mashinostroyeniya and India's Defence Research and Development Organisation (DRDO), who together have formed BrahMos Aerospace. The name BrahMos is formed from t</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/worlds-fastest-anti-ship-cruise-missile-in-operation.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Growing Enough Food to Feed a Family Year-Round by Yourself</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-food-to-feed-a-family.html</link>
    <description>It's a great thought of growing enough food to feed your family year round by yourself. Certain things are really important for such a though, like how much food is needed for your family, which crops to plant, how to get the most from your plot, and how to preserve your extra harvest.
                                How much food is needed?
                                Let's say a 200 square f</description>
    <pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-food-to-feed-a-family.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Bangalore -> Murdeshwar -> Gokarna -> Goa -> Dandeli -> Bangalore</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-murdeshwar-gokarna-goa-dandeli.html</link>
    <description>Ten days Ride from Bangalore  Murdeshwar  Gokarna  Goa  Dandeli  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for ten days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.
       </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-murdeshwar-gokarna-goa-dandeli.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Construction materials for Thermal Resistance Walls, Earth Bricks</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/construction-materials-for-thermal-resistant-walls.html</link>
    <description>Construction process can be tedious, time consuming, and expensive. To overcome this during construction, varied methods of construction is being considered and developed. Also, materials and equipment used for construction are also being fabricated to enhance the quality of construction and furthermore minimize the time and cost. Interlocking bricks are one such advancement in construction indust</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/construction-materials-for-thermal-resistant-walls.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Openness in a Couples Relationships can be Secret/Private</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/openness-in-relationships-secret-or-private.html</link>
    <description>In a healthy romantic relationship, as time goes on trust is earned, and we eventually open up more &amp; more. Based on each others mutual respect &amp; valuing, couples are sometimes unclear in how much they should or want to share within each other. Each of them have right to privacy and each decide, how much to share or how much to open up.
                                Few are too open or soon offe</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/openness-in-relationships-secret-or-private.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Scientists Have Created Hexagonal Salt, For First Time Ever</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/scientists-have-created-hexagonal-salt.html</link>
    <description>While it probably won't make it to your dining table, a new scientific achievement might be able to help in everything from radar equipment to electric cars: scientists have been able to form salt, aka sodium chloride (NaCl), in a hexagonal shapeThis is work done at the smallest of scales, with researchers able to get a thin film of hexagonal salt to form on top of a layer of diamond, due to the c</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/scientists-have-created-hexagonal-salt.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>'PigeonBot' is the first robot that can bend its wings like a real bird</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pigeonbot-is-the-first-robot-that-can-bend-its-wings.html</link>
    <description>Pigeons may be considered rats of the sky, but some scientists have found greater value in these urban birds: the blueprint for a new generation of flying machines.Birds can modify the shape of their wings by fanning out their feathers or shuffling them closer together. Those adjustments allow birds to cut through the sky more nimbly than rigid drones. Now, using new insights into exactly how pige</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pigeonbot-is-the-first-robot-that-can-bend-its-wings.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal JSON:API GET, POST, PATCH and DELETE Samples</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-get-post-patch-and-delete-samples.html</link>
    <description>The API that the JSON:API module makes available is centered on Drupal's entity types and bundles. Every bundle receives its own, unique URL path, which all follow a shared pattern
                                HTTP Methods
                                JSON:API specifies what HTTP Methods to accept. Those are: GET, POST, PATCH, and DELETE. Notably, PUT is not included.
                       </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-jsonapi-get-post-patch-and-delete-samples.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Cache Set, Get and Invalidate per User in Drupal 7</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cache-set-get-and-invalidate-user-drupal-.html</link>
    <description>How to Set, Get and Invalidate the caches per user in Drupal 7, this blog article will explain a brief of how to do such implementation on Drupal using the default drupal cache functions.
                                Here, we go with the steps
                                
                                    Initially, create the custom functions for Get, Set and Invalidate the caches per us</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cache-set-get-and-invalidate-user-drupal-.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Store Drupal logs on Amazon S3</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-drupal-logs-amazon-s.html</link>
    <description>Store Drupal logs on Amazon S3 via hook_watchdog, so that you can get rid of heavy logs on your drupal database and can later read from the S3.
                                For this todo on Drupal
                                
                                    You should use the "hook_watchdog" hook, where this hook allows modules to route log events to custom destinations.
               </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-drupal-logs-amazon-s.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>AES Encrypt &amp; Decrypt</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aes-encrypt-decrypt.html</link>
    <description>Advanced Encryption Standard, where we use AES-256 to encrypt the data with Cipher. Encrypt &amp;amp; Decrypt approach taken is 'Cipher Block Chaining' method 'AES-256-CBC'.
                                AES Encrypt
                                
                                    We would have the 'Secret' stored in a file which is other than the web root.
                                
      </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aes-encrypt-decrypt.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Sites Still Vulnerable to Drupalgeddon 2</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sites-still-vulnerable-drupalgeddon-.html</link>
    <description>Attackers are exploiting Drupalgeddon 2 critical vulnerability in Drupal to compromise systems &amp; secretly turn them into malicious cryptocurrency mining machines like cryptojacking malware, mine for Monero.
                                The only side effects a victim might notice is that their system is running slower or doing more work than usual.
                                Still most of t</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sites-still-vulnerable-drupalgeddon-.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Secure Website running on Apache with Let's Encrypt on Linux</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-website-running-apache-lets-encrypt-linux.html</link>
    <description>Website security is generally most complicated and expensive task for every Linux admin. Let's Encrypt is a free, automated, and open certificate authority that provides free X.509 certificates for Transport Layer Security encryption via an automated process. It's very complex process to install and add SSL certificate to a web server.
                                Let's make it easier with the </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-website-running-apache-lets-encrypt-linux.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Aegir on Docker - Develop, Test, With Easier Deployment</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aegir-docker-develop-test-easier-deployment.html</link>
    <description>Aegir with Docker would be one of the brilliant option for Better Drupal Development and Faster Deployments.
                                Docker, which solves the overhead of virtualization layer. And Aegir, which gives the best possible approach for Drupal Multisite hosting.
                                Here you go???
                                Better Task Queue..! This process is usua</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aegir-docker-develop-test-easier-deployment.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Integrating Codeception with Drupal to have added support for TDD</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/integrating-codeception-drupal-have-added-support-tdd.html</link>
    <description>Getting Codeception into Drupal, will have added support for Test Driven Development.. Specifically in having the Acceptance Tests in the project.. Since Test Driven Development would be one the most integral part of the project.. And also internal team and vendor team would be having more confidence in the version releases of their project.. one can prefer TDD.
                                Tes</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/integrating-codeception-drupal-have-added-support-tdd.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Creating a Twitter Share block programmatically in Drupal 8</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/creating-twitter-share-block-programmatically-drupal-.html</link>
    <description>How to Create a Twitter Share block programmatically in Drupal 8. Which includes few minor stuff like
                                
                                    Accessing the Current Node data in Block.
                                    How do we create the link programmatically.
                                    Disable cache for particular block.
                                
  </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/creating-twitter-share-block-programmatically-drupal-.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Auto Tagging of Taxonomy terms in Drupal7</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/auto-tagging-taxonomy-terms-drupal.html</link>
    <description>This article help you to create the way to implement the autotagging of the taxonomy terms based on the other field of the node page. This can be implemented by using the hook_node_presave().
                                In our case lets consider the field_tags is the taxonomy field, and we are autotagging based on the content present in title and body fields.
                                Al</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/auto-tagging-taxonomy-terms-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Configuring &amp; Debugging Drupal 7 on PHPStorm with XDebug on Ubuntu14</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuring-debugging-drupal--phpstorm-xdebug-ubuntu.html</link>
    <description>Debugging the code is one of the important process for a developer, So now this article will help you to configure the Phpstorm for debugging the Drupal 7 application with the help of xDebug.
                                The configuration made in this article refers specifically to the Ubuntu machine, which has Apache2 webserver running and xDebug installed.
                                Init</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuring-debugging-drupal--phpstorm-xdebug-ubuntu.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Custom Batch processing in Drupal 7 to update Nodes - Batch API</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/custom-batch-processing-drupal--update-nodes-batch-api.html</link>
    <description>Drupal's batch API processing is very nice and provides few benifits, We can break long tasks into smaller batches, and by this we will be able to prevent maximum execution time errors.
This article will show how to Build a batch routine in a custom module, its more straight forward approach, you can follow up below code, which is been explained with required comments.
Create your custom module, w</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/custom-batch-processing-drupal--update-nodes-batch-api.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal7 Simple Test case in Custom Module</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-simple-test-case-custom-module.html</link>
    <description>Why to write test case? Very simple, in one word, Its waste of time and effort of checking something we changed in code and that effects other part, and to make sure every time what change we make that should not effect any other code, so this task can be done by our test cases
                                In this article, giving a simple test example to create a drupal test case
              </description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-simple-test-case-custom-module.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Filter content between Date ranges in Drupal 7</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/filter-content-between-date-ranges-drupal.html</link>
    <description>It is tempting to believe that using the is between on a date fields will work. However, this option is used only in the case of events Starting on a range of date.
                                This tutorial requires that you already have a content type with a date field . It is not necessary to have two fields to adjust an 'end date' for the event, only a date field with the 'Collect an end da</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/filter-content-between-date-ranges-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Create Related Content of Different Content Types through Taxonomy in Drupal7</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-related-content-different-content-types-through-taxonomy-drupal.html</link>
    <description>Step 1 Create a Taxonomy term field for the content type, In this article lets take example for Basic Page content type as shown in the below image. with the Autocomplete selected as settings of the term reference field.
                                
                                Step 2 And next create/resue the Taxonomy term field for the other content type, In this article lets take example</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-related-content-different-content-types-through-taxonomy-drupal.html</guid>
  </item><item>
    <title>Drupal Multisite development environment Configuration in Ubuntu14</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-multisite-development-environment-configuration-ubuntu.html</link>
    <description>Prerequisite Requires a working drupal installation
                                Set up your hosts file Add the following lines to /etc/hosts:
                                127.0.0.1    testsite.localhost
127.0.0.1    testsite2.localhost
Set up Virtual Hosts
                                Add the following code to /etc/apache2/sites-available:
                                Goto to the fold</description>
    <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
    <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-multisite-development-environment-configuration-ubuntu.html</guid>
  </item><item>
  <title>The wolf and the shepherds</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wolf-and-the-shepherds.html</link>
  <description>This is one of the many Aesop&amp;rsquo;s fables that one can relate to in any day and age.  One day a wolf was chased away from a farm for trying to steal some of the sheep for food. Later that week, the wolf came back to the farm hoping to find some food. He peeped inside the house and found the farmer and his family feasting on lamb roast.  &amp;ldquo;Aha!&amp;rdquo;, he thought. &amp;ldquo;If I were to do the</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wolf-and-the-shepherds.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The young crab and his mother.</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-young-crab-and-his-mother.html</link>
  <description>One day, a young crab and his mother were on the beach, spending some time together. The young crab gets up to move, but it can only walk sideways. His mother scolds him for walking sideways and asks him to walk forward by pointing his toes out front. The young crab responds, &amp;ldquo;I would like to walk forward mom, but I do not know how to&amp;rdquo;.  Hearing this, his mom gets up to show him how, b</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-young-crab-and-his-mother.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The other side of the wall</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-other-side-of-the-wall.html</link>
  <description>A young woman inherited a beautiful garden from her grandmother. She loved gardening too and was very proud of her garden. One day, she saw a very beautiful plant in a catalog and wanted that for her garden. She ordered it and planted it at the base of the stonewall in her backyard. She took great care of the plant, which grew quickly and had beautiful green leaves on it.  Months passed, but not a</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-other-side-of-the-wall.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The dog at the well</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-dog-at-the-well.html</link>
  <description>A dog and her pups lived on a farm, where there was a well. The mother dog told the pups, do not go near the well or play around it. One of the pups wondered why they shouldn&amp;rsquo;t go to the well and decided to explore it. He went to the well. Climbed up the wall and peeked inside.  In there, he saw his reflection and thought it was another dog. The pup saw that the other dog in the well (his re</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-dog-at-the-well.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Controlling anger</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/controlling-anger.html</link>
  <description>There was once a young boy who had problem controlling his temper. When he became angry, he would just say anything that came to his mind and hurt people. So his father gave him a bag of nails and a hammer and said, &amp;ldquo;Every time you get angry, hammer one nail into the fence in our backyard&amp;rdquo;.  The first few days the boy hammered so many nails that he emptied half the bag. Over the weeks,</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/controlling-anger.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Wet Pants</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wet-pants.html</link>
  <description>A nine-year-old boy was sitting at his desk in class, when suddenly, his pants felt wet, and there was a puddle at his feet. His heart almost skipped a beat, as he got worried that his classmates would see that and make fun of him.  He quickly wanted to do something, and saw the teacher and his classmate Susie walking towards him. Susie was carrying a bowl of goldfish. As they came closer, the boy</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wet-pants.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Bad Habits</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/bad-habits.html</link>
  <description>A wealthy businessman was worried about his son&amp;rsquo;s bad habits. He sought counsel from a wise, old man. The old man met the man&amp;rsquo;s son and took him out for a stroll. They walked into the woods, and the old man showed the boy a small sapling and asked him to pull it out. The boy did so with ease, and they walked on.  The old man then asked the boy to pull out a small plant. The boy did tha</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/bad-habits.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>How to Think Positive and Best out of a Situation? with King's Painting</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/how-to-think-positive-and-best-out-of-a-situation-with-kings-painting.html</link>
  <description>We people might have heard a saying to think positive, many times. In this quick read we are gonna see how a painter thinks positively with a situation to draw a King&amp;rsquo;s painting.  Once upon a time, there was a Kingdom. The king there only had one leg and one eye, but he was very intelligent and kind. Everyone in his kingdom lived a happy and healthy life because of their king. One day the ki</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/how-to-think-positive-and-best-out-of-a-situation-with-kings-painting.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Keep good company if you want to be a good person</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/keep-good-company-if-you-want-to-be-a-good-person.html</link>
  <description>Two parrots built a nest in a banyan tree. They lived with their two young ones, which they took good care of. The mother and the father parrot went out to gather food in the morning and came back home by evening. One day, when their parents were away, the young parrots were taken by a cruel hunter.  One of the birds managed to escape and flew away from the hunter. He ended up at a hermitage and g</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/keep-good-company-if-you-want-to-be-a-good-person.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Dara Singh Randhawa (Dara Singh)</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/dara-singh-randhawa.html</link>
  <description>Dara Singh was an Indian Professional Wrestler, Actor, Director and Politician.  He was born on 19th November 1928 in a Jat Sikh family, to Surat Singh Randhawa and Balwant Kaur.  He is known for his undefeated worldwide streak in wrestling. His flooring of King Kong is still remembered. According to Thesz, Dara Sing was an authentic wrestler, he was superbly conditioned and had no problem losing </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/dara-singh-randhawa.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>ISRO launched three Singapore Satellites with PSLV</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-launched-three-singapore-satellites-with-pslv.html</link>
  <description>On Thursday 30th Jun 2022 at 18:02 hours IST, India successfully placed into orbit three Singaporean satellites exactly as planned, which will make it the second successful rocket and satellite launch mission in 2022.  It was the PSLV-C53 rocket which took up the Satellites into space from the Satish Dhawan Space Centre, Sriharikota. And with this successful mission, the PSLV rocket has launched 3</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-launched-three-singapore-satellites-with-pslv.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Legislative Assistants for Members of Parliament (LAMP) Fellowship</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/legislative-assistants-for-members-of-parliament-lamp-fellowship.html</link>
  <description>LAMP Fellowship is an opportunity for young people in India, provided by the Indian Government, to be mentored by a Member of Parliament, during this course of the Fellowship, people will get the opportunity to engage with experts from diverse sectors and understand important policy and development issues of the country.   Primary role is to provide research support to the Member of Parliament (wh</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Hanukkah John</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/legislative-assistants-for-members-of-parliament-lamp-fellowship.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>A Comet which is twice the Everest's size is heading toward Earth</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-comet-which-is-twice-the-everest-size-is-heading-toward-earth.html</link>
  <description>A massive comet named C/2017 K2 (PanSTARRS) is heading toward the Earth. It is twice the size of Mount Everest and will make its closest approach on July 14.  It was first spotted in 2017. It mostly consists of ice and will not pose any danger to general people, but an astronomer will be more excited.  Let&amp;#39;s see what we know about it and how can we watch it?   This C/2017 K2 has been active fo</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-comet-which-is-twice-the-everest-size-is-heading-toward-earth.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Fourth QUAD meet on 11th February 2022</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/fourth-quad-meet-on-th-february-.html</link>
  <description>A Joint statement by QUAD member countries Australia, India, Japan, and United States was released post the fourth meeting that happened on 11th Feb 2022 in Melbourne, Australia. This Fourth QUAD meeting was with Marise Payne, Minister for Foreign Affairs Australia, Subrahmanyam Jaishankar, External Affairs Minister of India, Hayashi Yoshimasa, Minister of Foreign Affairs of Japan &amp; Antony Blinken</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/fourth-quad-meet-on-th-february-.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Vikram Misri Is New Deputy National Security Advisor</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/vikram-misri-is-new-deputy-national-security-advisor.html</link>
  <description>Vikram Misri is a career diplomat from the 1989 batch of the Indian Foreign Service. He was born in Srinagar, Vikram Misri attended the Scindia School before graduating from Delhi's Hindu College. He also holds an MBA degree. And before joining the civil services, he had worked in advertising and ad film-making for three years. Earlier Vikram Misri has served at the Ministry of External Affairs of</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/vikram-misri-is-new-deputy-national-security-advisor.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Olympics and Paralympics are two different Olympic Games</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/olympics-and-paralympics-are-two-different-olympic-games.html</link>
  <description>There is a key difference between the Olympics and the Paralympics, where in the Olympics the participants will be able-bodied people and whereas in Paralympics the participants will have some form of physical or intellectual disabilities.
                            Paralympics was originally started as a way to help soldiers who had been wounded in World War II.
                            Paral</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/olympics-and-paralympics-are-two-different-olympic-games.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Indian Astrophysicists spotted rare merger of three massive black holes</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/indian-astrophysicists-spotted-rare-merger-of-three-massive-black-holes.html</link>
  <description>According to the Press Information Bureau, Astrophysicists in India have spotted a rare merging of three supermassive black holes. They were observing the merging of two galaxies named NGC7733 and NGC7734 in our celestial neighbour.
                            When they detected unusual emissions from the centre of the latter and also a curious movement of a large bright clump having a different v</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/indian-astrophysicists-spotted-rare-merger-of-three-massive-black-holes.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>India, Russia to assess Taliban actions, before taking any action on Taliban</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/india-russia-to-assess-taliban-actions-before-taking-any-action-on-taliban.html</link>
  <description>Russian President Vladimir Putin and Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi agreed on the rise of Islamic radicalization in the region and are concerned over spread of terrorism by Taliban affiliated groups in Pakistan.
                            The two countries have also decided to set up combined teams of foreign ministry and national security officials of each country to conduct a detailed asse</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/india-russia-to-assess-taliban-actions-before-taking-any-action-on-taliban.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Virtual QUAD meet on 12th August, 2021</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/virtual-quad-meet-on-twelfth-august-twenty-twenty-one.html</link>
  <description>On August 12th, 2021 Senior Officials from four democracies - Australia, India, Japan, and the U.S. - met virtually to discuss Quad initiatives on economic recovery, maritime security, and human rights that promote a free and open IndoPacific region.
                            The four democracies acknowledged that global security and prosperity depends on the region remaining inclusive, resilien</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/virtual-quad-meet-on-twelfth-august-twenty-twenty-one.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>GSLV-F10 to launch Earth Observation Satellite</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/gslv-f-ten-to-launch-earth-observation-satellite.html</link>
  <description>GSLV-F10 is slated to launch Earth Observation Satellite, EOS-03 on August 12th, 2021 from Satish Dhawan Space Centre SHAR, Sriharikota.
                            Countdown for the launch of GSLV-F10/EOS-03 mission commenced on August 11th at 03:43 Hrs (IST) from Satish Dhawan Space Centre (SDSC) SHAR, Sriharikota
                            GSLV-F10 launch took place today (12th Aug) at 05:43 H</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/gslv-f-ten-to-launch-earth-observation-satellite.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>July 26th - Kargil Vijay Diwas</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-sixth-kargil-vijay-diwas.html</link>
  <description>In 1999, India successfully took command of high outposts on this date. The Kargil war was fought for more than 60 days &amp; ended on this date.
                            Pakistani army took advantage of the melting snow &amp; took command of high outposts of India, by betraying the bilateral agreement of both the nations that posts would remain unattended during winter season.
                        </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-sixth-kargil-vijay-diwas.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>July 23rd - National Broadcasting Day</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-third-national-broadcasting-day.html</link>
  <description>During the British Raj, Broadcasting began in June 1923 with the programs by the Bombay Presidency Radio Club and other radio clubs.
                            
                                The private Indian Broadcasting Company Ltd (IBC) was authorized to operate two radio stations in an agreement on 23 July 1927.
                                IBC started with two stations, one in Bombay (</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-third-national-broadcasting-day.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>ISRO successfully conducted the Third Test on Vikas Engine for Gaganyaan</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-successfully-conducted-the-third-test-on-vikas-engine-for-gaganyaan.html</link>
  <description>On July 14, 2021, ISRO has successfully conducted the third long-duration hot test of the liquid propellant Vikas Engine for the core L110 liquid stage of the human-rated GSLV MkIII vehicle, as part of the engine qualification requirements for the Gaganyaan Programme.
                            The engine was fired for a duration of 240 seconds at the engine test facility of ISRO Propulsion Compl</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-successfully-conducted-the-third-test-on-vikas-engine-for-gaganyaan.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Heat on Earth’s Atmosphere is Heating much as it did fifteen years ago</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/heat-on-earths-atmosphere-is-heating-much-as-it-did-fifteen-years-ago.html</link>
  <description>Earth's energy imbalance doubled between 2005 - 2019, this was identified by a team from NASA &amp; NOAA. Energy Im-balance is the difference between the amount of energy absorbed by Earth and the amount of energy emitted by Earth.
                            Means, if there is any energy imbalance on earth, Earth will be gaining energy which will lead to heat up more.
                            So t</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/heat-on-earths-atmosphere-is-heating-much-as-it-did-fifteen-years-ago.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Device with Two Atoms thick, World’s thinnest device</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/device-with-two-atoms-thick-worlds-thinnest-device.html</link>
  <description>World’s thinnest piece of technology has been developed by the Scientists, which is a device with only two Atoms thick, very tiny. It can be used to store electronic information.
                            This device consists of 2 layers one with Boron &amp; other with Nitrogen, which are arranged in a repeating hexagonal structure.
                            Electrons from Boron &amp; Nitrogen atoms</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/device-with-two-atoms-thick-worlds-thinnest-device.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Powerful Solar Storm approaching Earth</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/powerful-solar-storm-approaching-earth.html</link>
  <description>According to website spaceweather.com, a powerful solar storm is approaching the Earth at a speed of 1.6 million kilometers and this storm will hit the Earth someday on 11th July - 13th July 2021. As per the website spaceweather.com, the storm that originated from the Sun's atmosphere can have a significant impact on a region of space dominated by Earth's magnetic field.
                          </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/powerful-solar-storm-approaching-earth.html</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>