<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>India - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/india.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>UFO Sighting Over Kanchenjunga – Mystery Above the Himalayas</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ufo-sighting-over-kanchenjunga-mystery-above-the-himalayas.html</link>
			<description>The towering Kanchenjunga, the world&amp;rsquo;s third-highest mountain, has long been surrounded by myths, spirituality, and intrigue. Rising over 8,500 meters across the borders of India and Nepal, it&amp;rsquo;s revered as a sacred peak by the people of Sikkim. But beyond its breathtaking beauty and religious significance, Kanchenjunga has also become the site of one of India&amp;rsquo;s most puzzling UFO </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ufo-sighting-over-kanchenjunga-mystery-above-the-himalayas.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>RCB, Alcohol Ownership, and the Public Spectacle: A Modern-Colosseum Distraction?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rcb-alcohol-ownership-and-the-public-spectacle-a-modern-colosseum-distraction.html</link>
			<description>Every April&amp;ndash;May from past 18 years, Bengaluru transforms into a sea of red and black as fans don RCB jerseys and pour into pubs, chanting their team&amp;rsquo;s praises. For many, RCB (Royal Challengers Bengaluru) isn&amp;rsquo;t just a cricket franchise&amp;mdash;it&amp;rsquo;s Karnataka pride incarnate. 🏏 But beneath the enthusiasm lies a deeper truth: RCB is owned by United Spirits, a subsidiary of Di</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rcb-alcohol-ownership-and-the-public-spectacle-a-modern-colosseum-distraction.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Water for Pakistan: Lifeline, Dependency, and the Shifting Control</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/water-for-pakistan-lifeline-dependency-and-the-shifting-control.html</link>
			<description>Water is not just a natural resource for Pakistan&amp;mdash;it is its lifeline. With over 90% of its water supply coming from a single river system, Pakistan is critically dependent on external sources. Agriculture, power generation, and daily life across the country rely on uninterrupted water flow, primarily from rivers originating in Indian-administered territory. In recent developments, however, t</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 10:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/water-for-pakistan-lifeline-dependency-and-the-shifting-control.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vimanas in Ancient India – Were They Real Flying Machines?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vimanas-in-ancient-india-were-they-real-flying-machines.html</link>
			<description>The idea of Vimanas, ancient flying machines mentioned in Indian scriptures, has fascinated historians, scientists, and enthusiasts alike. Some believe these texts describe advanced aerial technology far ahead of their time, while others argue that Vimanas are purely mythological. But could ancient India have actually possessed flying technology, or are these references symbolic? Let&amp;rsquo;s explo</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 10:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vimanas-in-ancient-india-were-they-real-flying-machines.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Different spices are used to make a garam masala mix?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-spices-are-used-to-make-a-garam-masala-mix.html</link>
			<description>Garam masala is a quintessential spice blend used in Indian cuisine. It adds warmth, depth and complexity to dishes and its composition can vary widely based on regional preferences and personal taste.  Here&amp;#39;s a breakdown of the different spices commonly used to make garam masala, along with why, how and when it&amp;#39;s used:  What is Garam Masala?   Garam masala is a blend of ground spices comm</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 14:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-spices-are-used-to-make-a-garam-masala-mix.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Average yearly consumption of Rice for the typical Indian</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/average-yearly-consumption-of-rice-for-the-typical-indian.html</link>
			<description>Average yearly consumption of rice for a typical Indian varies based on factors such as region, cultural practices, dietary preferences and socioeconomic status.  However, rice is a staple food in India and is consumed in significant quantities across the country.  Why Rice is Consumed:   Cultural Significance:   Rice holds immense cultural significance in India and is deeply ingrained in traditio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 Apr 2024 08:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/average-yearly-consumption-of-rice-for-the-typical-indian.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Samosas - Snack from the Indian subcontinent</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/samosas-snack-from-the-indian-subcontinent.html</link>
			<description>Samosas are a popular savory snack originating from the Indian subcontinent. They are triangular-shaped pastries filled with a savory mixture of spiced potatoes, peas and sometimes other ingredients.  Here&amp;#39;s how samosas are typically cooked, along with some background information:  What Are Samosas?   	Ingredients: The outer pastry shell of samosas is typically made from all-purpose flour, wat</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/samosas-snack-from-the-indian-subcontinent.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What percentage of Indians are vegetarian?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</link>
			<description>Approximately 30-40% of the population in India is estimated to follow a vegetarian diet. However, this percentage can vary depending on the region, cultural practices and religious beliefs.  Why Indians Follow Vegetarianism:   Religious Beliefs:   Hinduism: Many Hindus follow a vegetarian diet as part of their religious beliefs, which promote compassion and non-violence (ahimsa). They believe in </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in South India to travel in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>South India offers several destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers due to their cooler climates, hill stations and coastal areas.  Here are some of the best places to visit in South India during the hot summer months, along with reasons, ways to travel and the best time to visit:    Ooty, Tamil Nadu:   Why: Ooty, also known as the &amp;quot;Queen of Hill Stations,&amp;quot; offers c</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 08:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten hill stations to travel solo in south of India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-of-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in South India can be a delightful experience, offering scenic beauty, tranquility and a chance for self-reflection.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in South India for solo travel:   Ooty, Tamil Nadu: Known as the &amp;quot;Queen of Hill Stations,&amp;quot; Ooty is famous for its lush tea gardens, serene lakes and pleasant weather. The Nilgiri Mountain Railway adds </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-of-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten best places to Travel Solo in South India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-places-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo in South India can be a remarkable experience, offering a diverse range of landscapes, cultures and experiences.  Here are ten of the best places to explore, along with reasons why they are great for solo travelers and the best times to visit:   Pondicherry, Tamil Nadu:  Why: Pondicherry offers a unique blend of French and Indian cultures, serene beaches and a peaceful ambiance. It&amp;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 09:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-places-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Should people really vote in democracy?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</link>
			<description>Yes, voting is a crucial aspect of a democratic society and it plays a fundamental role in shaping the governance and policies of a nation.  Here are some reasons why voting is important:   Representation: Voting allows individuals to have a say in choosing representatives who will make decisions on their behalf. By participating in elections, citizens can help ensure that their interests and conc</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>INS Vikrant Delivered to Indian Navy, First Indigenous Aircraft Carrier by India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</link>
			<description>INS Vikrant which is also known as Indigenous Aircraft Carrier 1 (IAC-1). It is the first aircraft carrier to be built in India. This is an Aircraft Carrier constructed by the Cochin Shipyard Limited (CSL) for the Indian Navy.  The name Vikrant means courageous in Sanskrit. The motto of the ship is Jayema Saṁ Yudhi Sprdhah, which means I defeat those who fight against me.  Brief of the backgroun</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Monkeypox Outbreak around the World in 2022</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</link>
			<description>The outbreak of monkeypox, which is a viral disease, was confirmed in May 2022, once few cases were found in the United Kingdom. The first case was detected on 6th May 2022 and confirmed this case had travel links to Nigeria (where the disease is endemic).  From 18th May 2022 onwards, there was an increase in cases in Europe, North and South America, Asia, Africa and Australia.  As of 23rd July 20</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Droupadi Murmu, New President of India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</link>
			<description>Droupadi Murmu was nominated to President elections and on 21st of July 2022 elections counting was finished and Droupadi Murmu won the elections and will be the New President of India, Murmu is likely to take oath on July 25 as President of India.  A few highlights of 15th President of India   Droupadi Murmu will be the first person belonging to a Scheduled Tribe (ST) community to be elected as t</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>President of India nominated Veerendra Heggade, P.T. Usha, Ilaiyaraaja and V. Vijayendra Prasad to the Rajya Sabha</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</link>
			<description>According to the Fourth Schedule (Articles 4(1) and 80(2)) of the Constitution of India, The President of India can nominate 12 members to Rajya Sabha for a term of six-years for their contributions towards Arts, Literature, Sciences and Social Services.  Maybe earlier most of the South Indian peoples, for this matter all the Indian people might not be aware that The President of India can nominat</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>For Indian Youth..! What should you know about Nambi Narayanan?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-indian-youth-what-should-you-know-about-nambi-narayanan.html</link>
			<description>Lets see the background,                                In 1992, India signed an agreement with Russia..                                                                    Aggrement was for transfer of technology to develop cryogenic fuel-based engines and procurement of two such engines for ₹ 235 crore.                                    However, Russia did not materialize after the US presiden</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-indian-youth-what-should-you-know-about-nambi-narayanan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Privatisation of Public Sector Banks &amp; Banks Strike in March 2021</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/privatisation-of-public-sector-banks-banks-strike-march-.html</link>
			<description>The Finance Minister has announced in Union Budget of India for 2021-22, that two Public Sector Banks (PSBs) will be Privatised. The policy of government in last three decades of economic reforms was to sell a part of shares in Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) including PSBs to public while retaining the controlling share in its own hands.                                Privatisation of PSBs is i</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/privatisation-of-public-sector-banks-banks-strike-march-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>COVID-19 Vaccination in India, Covishield and Covaxin</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/covid--vaccination-in-india.html</link>
			<description>In January 2021 India started National Vaccination programme against the SARS-CoV-2 virus which has caused the COVID-19 pandemic. The drive prioritises healthcare and frontline workers and then those over the age of 60 and then those over the age of 45 and suffering from certain comorbidities.                                In January 2021 Secretary-General of the United Nations Antonio Guterres s</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/covid--vaccination-in-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Be Aware of Chain Snatchers &amp; Tips to Prevent Chain Snatching</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/be-aware-of-chain-snatchers-tips-to-prevent-chain-snatching.html</link>
			<description>Chain Snatching is one of the crime happening across India by different individuals or gangs. One should be aware while being in public places and should be cautious always. Chain snatching an easy job unlike burglaries, robberies or dacoities. These chain snatchers mostly will be from different places, They will often go to a new places and do their job and leave within hours.                    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/be-aware-of-chain-snatchers-tips-to-prevent-chain-snatching.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Reduce the Risk of Becoming a Sexual Assault Victim!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</link>
			<description>To Reduce the risk for you to becoming a sexual victim, you have to take some preventative measures, which will help you to avoid a risky situations from escalating. Anyone can be the target of sexual assault, regardless of age, gender, race, ethnicity, sexual orientation, sexual history, or social class. There is no stereotypical victim or rapist.                                What's bad? - Near</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prime accused in gang-rape case nabbed after two decades</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prime-accused-in-gang-rape-case-nabbed-after-two-decades.html</link>
			<description>Prime accused Bibekananda Biswal in a sensational gangrape that shook Odisha in its aftermath in 1999 is now caught by Police from Aamby Valley in Lonavala in Maharashtra.                                The incident, that occurred in 1999, had created a state-wide outrage. A total of three persons were accused in the case. Two of them - Pradeep Sahi and Dhirendra Mohanty, were arrested and convict</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prime-accused-in-gang-rape-case-nabbed-after-two-decades.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>International Mother Language Day</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/international-mother-language-day.html</link>
			<description>International Mother Language Day is a worldwide annual observance held on 21st February to promote awareness of linguistic and cultural diversity and to promote multilingualism. First announced by UNESCO on 17 November 1999, it was formally recognized by the United Nations General Assembly with the adoption of UN resolution 56/262 in 2002.                                Mother Language Day is par</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/international-mother-language-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>National Education Policy 2020, Government of India (NEP 2020)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/national-education-policy-nep.html</link>
			<description>National Education Policy (NEP 2020) has been approved by Union Cabinet on 29 July 2020. Its major aim is to introduce changes in the Indian Education System right from the school to the college level of education. Making India a Global Knowledge Superpower is the ultimate objective of the NEP 2020. It is the third major change in education systems in India since independence in 1947. Earlier two </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/national-education-policy-nep.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>