<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Lifestyle - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lifestyle.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Things to keep always as a Secret</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-keep-always-as-a-secret.html</link>
			<description>Keeping secrets is a personal and ethical decision that depends on various factors, including the nature of the secret, the impact it may have on others, and legal obligations. However, here are some examples of things that are commonly considered appropriate to keep confidential:   Personal confidences: Respect the privacy of individuals who confide in you about personal matters, such as their st</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 07:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-keep-always-as-a-secret.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best Heartwarming Gestures that People would like to receive?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-heartwarming-gestures-that-people-would-like-to-receive.html</link>
			<description>A heartwarming gesture that people would likely appreciate can vary depending on individual preferences and relationships.  However, here are some generally well-received gestures:   A handwritten letter or personalized note: In today&amp;#39;s digital age, receiving a heartfelt, handwritten message can be incredibly meaningful. Express your appreciation, admiration, or love for someone in a sincere a</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jun 2023 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-heartwarming-gestures-that-people-would-like-to-receive.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Is Life worth Living without Marriage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-life-worth-living-without-marriage.html</link>
			<description>Yes, life is worth living without marriage. Marriage is a personal choice, and not being married does not diminish the value or worth of an individual&amp;#39;s life. There are many fulfilling and meaningful experiences, relationships, and accomplishments that can be pursued outside of marriage.  The worth and fulfillment of life come from various sources, such as personal growth, meaningful connectio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-life-worth-living-without-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Five most common mind games People play on you</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/five-most-common-mind-games-people-play-on-you.html</link>
			<description>While the specific mind games people play can vary, here are five examples of common mind games that individuals may employ:   Gaslighting: Gaslighting is a manipulative tactic in which someone attempts to make you doubt your perception of reality or your own sanity. They may deny or distort events, minimize your feelings, or question your memory, causing you to question your own experiences and j</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/five-most-common-mind-games-people-play-on-you.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>People who cares the least has the most power in a Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-who-cares-the-least-has-the-most-power-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>The statement &amp;quot;People who care the least have the most power in a relationship&amp;quot; is a common belief, but it is not necessarily true or healthy for a relationship. Here&amp;#39;s why:   Power dynamics: Viewing relationships as power struggles can create an imbalance and undermine the foundation of trust, mutual respect, and equality. A healthy relationship is built on mutual care, understandin</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-who-cares-the-least-has-the-most-power-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Increase your Self Respect with these Ten things</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/increase-your-self-respect-with-these-ten-things.html</link>
			<description>Increasing self-respect is an important aspect of personal growth and well-being. Here are some steps you can take to enhance your self-respect:   Practice self-care: Take care of your physical, emotional, and mental well-being. Prioritize activities that make you feel good and promote self-nurturing. This can include exercise, getting enough rest, eating nutritious meals, practicing mindfulness o</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/increase-your-self-respect-with-these-ten-things.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Psychological facts about Attracting People</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/psychological-facts-about-attracting-people.html</link>
			<description>Psychological attraction is a complex and multifaceted topic influenced by various factors. Here are some psychological facts that may play a role in attracting people:   Physical appearance matters: Physical attractiveness can have an initial impact on attracting others. Studies have shown that certain features, such as symmetry, averageness, and healthy appearance, are generally perceived as mor</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/psychological-facts-about-attracting-people.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How do you take space in a Relationship without breaking up?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-you-take-space-in-a-relationship-without-breaking-up.html</link>
			<description>Taking space in a relationship can be healthy and necessary for both individuals to maintain their well-being and strengthen the relationship.  Here are some suggestions for taking space without breaking up:   Communicate openly: Talk to your partner about the need for space and the reasons behind it. Express your feelings, desires, and concerns in a calm and honest manner. Explain that taking spa</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-you-take-space-in-a-relationship-without-breaking-up.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to express thoughts without hurting other people?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-express-thoughts-without-hurting-other-people.html</link>
			<description>Expressing thoughts without hurting other people requires a combination of empathy, tact, and effective communication skills. Here are some tips to help you express your thoughts in a considerate manner:   Practice empathy: Put yourself in the other person&amp;#39;s shoes and try to understand their perspective. Consider how your words might impact them emotionally and be mindful of their feelings. Ch</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-express-thoughts-without-hurting-other-people.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mental &amp; Physical Wellbeing Connection</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mental-and-physical-wellbeing-connection.html</link>
			<description>The connection between mental and physical well-being is significant. The state of our mind and emotions can have a direct impact on our physical health, and likewise, our physical health can influence our mental well-being.  Here are some key aspects of the mental and physical well-being connection:   Psychological impact on physical health: Mental health conditions such as stress, anxiety, and d</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 May 2023 10:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mental-and-physical-wellbeing-connection.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Some unwritten social rules everyone should know</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/some-unwritten-social-rules-everyone-should-know.html</link>
			<description>While social rules can vary depending on cultural norms and contexts, here are some unwritten social rules that are generally valued and can help guide interactions with others:   Respect personal space: Be mindful of people&amp;#39;s personal boundaries and avoid invading their personal space without consent. Maintain an appropriate physical distance in different situations. Practice good hygiene: Ma</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 29 May 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/some-unwritten-social-rules-everyone-should-know.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lessons to be learnt from Marriage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-to-be-learnt-from-marriage.html</link>
			<description>Marriage is a complex and deeply personal experience, and the lessons one can learn from it can vary based on individual circumstances. However, here are some common lessons that people often learn from their marriages:   Communication is key: Effective communication is crucial for a healthy and thriving marriage. Learning to express your thoughts, emotions, and needs openly and honestly, while al</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-to-be-learnt-from-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Eight things should Never be Rushed?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-things-should-never-be-rushed.html</link>
			<description>Certain things in life should never be rushed, as they require time, careful consideration, and attention to detail. Here are some examples:   Relationships: Building deep and meaningful relationships takes time. Rushing into a romantic partnership or friendship without truly knowing and understanding the other person can lead to disappointment or incompatible connections. Take the necessary time </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-things-should-never-be-rushed.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Communication and Self Reflection Strategies</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/communication-and-self-reflection-strategies.html</link>
			<description>Communication and self-reflection are essential skills that can help enhance personal growth, improve relationships, and promote effective communication with others.  Here are some strategies for both  Communication Strategies:   Active listening: Engaging in active listening techniques to fully understand and respond effectively to others. Clear and concise expression: Articulating thoughts and i</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/communication-and-self-reflection-strategies.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to be Approachable and Friendly</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-be-approachable-and-friendly.html</link>
			<description>Being approachable and friendly can help you create a welcoming environment that encourages others to engage with you.  Here are some tips to cultivate an approachable and friendly demeanor:   Smile: A genuine smile can instantly make you appear more approachable and friendly. It conveys warmth and openness, inviting others to feel comfortable approaching you. Maintain open body language: Ensure y</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 May 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-be-approachable-and-friendly.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How can People can build Bond with other People</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-people-can-build-bond-with-other-people.html</link>
			<description>Building bonds with others is a valuable and rewarding endeavor. Here are some practical ways people can build bonds with others:   Be approachable and friendly: Create an inviting and welcoming demeanor that encourages others to approach you. Smile, maintain open body language, and be receptive to conversations with those around you. Initiate conversations: Take the initiative to start conversati</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-people-can-build-bond-with-other-people.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bridging the Gap between Work &amp; Fitness</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bridging-the-gap-between-work-and-fitness.html</link>
			<description>Bridging the gap between work and fitness is essential for maintaining a healthy lifestyle in today&amp;#39;s fast-paced world. Balancing the demands of work with the need for physical activity can be challenging, but with proper planning and commitment, it&amp;#39;s possible to integrate fitness into your work routine.  Here are some strategies to help you bridge the gap between work and fitness:   Set f</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 19 May 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bridging-the-gap-between-work-and-fitness.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Discovering Wellness Through Work - Life Integration</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/discovering-wellness-through-work-life-integration.html</link>
			<description>Work-life integration is an approach that emphasizes finding a healthy and sustainable balance between work and personal life. It recognizes that work and personal life are interconnected and seeks to create harmony between the two rather than viewing them as separate entities in constant conflict.  Here are some ways to discover wellness through work-life integration:   Define your values and pri</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/discovering-wellness-through-work-life-integration.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why do people use shortcut words like AFK etc?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-use-shortcut-words-like-afk-etc.html</link>
			<description>People use shortcut words like AFK (Away From Keyboard), BRB (Be Right Back), LOL (Laughing Out Loud), and others for several reasons:   Convenience: Using shorthand or abbreviations can be faster and more convenient than typing out the full phrase or sentence. This is particularly true in online communication, where speed and brevity are often valued. Community and culture: Many shorthand words a</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-use-shortcut-words-like-afk-etc.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why should we chant Hare Rama Hare Krishna Mahamantra?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-should-we-chant-hare-rama-hare-krishna-mahamantra.html</link>
			<description>The Hare Krishna Mahamantra, also known as the Maha Mantra, is a powerful mantra that is chanted by devotees of the Krishna Consciousness movement.  The Hare Krishna Maha Mantra is a chant that is believed to have spiritual and transformative effects. It is chanted by devotees of the Hare Krishna movement and those who follow the Vaishnavite tradition of Hinduism.  The Hare Krishna Maha Mantra is </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-should-we-chant-hare-rama-hare-krishna-mahamantra.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How Do I Deal with Anxiety During Sex?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-i-deal-with-anxiety-during-sex.html</link>
			<description>Experiencing anxiety during sex can be a common issue, and it is important to address the root cause of the anxiety and find ways to manage it.  Here are some tips for dealing with anxiety during sex:   Communicate with your partner: Let your partner know how you&amp;#39;re feeling and what you need to feel comfortable. Communication is key to a healthy and satisfying sexual experience.               </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-i-deal-with-anxiety-during-sex.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>BDSM Role Play: How Does It Work?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bdsm-role-play-how-does-it-work.html</link>
			<description>BDSM (bondage and discipline, dominance and submission, sadism and masochism) role play is a consensual sexual activity that involves one partner taking on a dominant role and the other partner taking on a submissive role. This can include activities such as power exchange, restraint, and impact play.                     (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});        In BDSM role play, </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bdsm-role-play-how-does-it-work.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Different ways to get more out of 69 position</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-ways-to-get-more-out-of-six-nine-position.html</link>
			<description>The 69 position is a popular sexual position that involves mutual oral sex. Here are some tips to get more out of the 69 position:  1. Change positions: Try changing positions to mix things up. You can start with one person on top, then switch to the other person on top, or try a side-by-side position.  2. Use your hands: Incorporate your hands into the mix by touching your partner&amp;#39;s erogenous</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-ways-to-get-more-out-of-six-nine-position.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Curiosity, how will this change people's Life?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/curiosity-how-will-this-change-peoples-life.html</link>
			<description>Curiosity can have a significant impact on a person&amp;#39;s life, both personally and professionally. Here are a few ways that curiosity can change a person&amp;#39;s life:   Learning and growth: Curiosity leads people to explore new ideas and concepts, and to seek out new experiences. This can lead to personal growth and learning, which can broaden their perspective and help them understand the world a</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/curiosity-how-will-this-change-peoples-life.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How can I evaluate whether counseling is working?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-evaluate-whether-counseling-is-working.html</link>
			<description>Evaluating whether counseling is working can be a challenging task because it is a personal and subjective experience. However, there are some indicators that can help you determine whether counseling is helping you to achieve your goals and make progress.  Here are some ways to evaluate whether counseling is working:   Reflection: Take some time to reflect on how you feel before and after each se</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-evaluate-whether-counseling-is-working.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How does confidentiality work?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-confidentiality-work.html</link>
			<description>Confidentiality is a fundamental aspect of the counseling process, and it ensures that any information shared between a client and counselor is kept private and secure. Confidentiality is crucial for building trust between the client and counselor and creating a safe, non-judgmental environment for the client to explore their thoughts and feelings.  In general, confidentiality works as follows:   </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-confidentiality-work.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What happens in counseling sessions?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happens-in-counseling-sessions.html</link>
			<description>In a counseling session, a trained professional known as a counselor or therapist works with an individual or group to help them explore and address personal, social, or psychological issues.  The specific activities and techniques used in a counseling session can vary depending on the client&amp;#39;s needs and the counselor&amp;#39;s approach, but in general, a counseling session may involve the followi</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-happens-in-counseling-sessions.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>When should one seek counseling?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-should-one-seek-counseling.html</link>
			<description>There are several situations in which seeking counseling may be helpful. Here are some common reasons why people seek counseling:   Mental health concerns: If you are experiencing symptoms of a mental health condition, such as depression, anxiety, or post-traumatic stress disorder, counseling can help you to manage these symptoms and develop coping strategies. Relationship issues: Counseling can b</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-should-one-seek-counseling.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>UnConditional Love in a Couples Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>It is commonly said that Women are complex in mental nature while Men remain easy to understand and simple. Whatever be the reasons that backup this comment,&amp;nbsp;in relationships both Men and Women follow slightly diverted paths.&amp;nbsp;What Men look for in a relationship is not what motivates Women to fall in relationships. The differences in desires, mentalities, passion, expression levels etc., </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Courtship time, Make it memorable, ways to add some spice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/courtship-time-make-it-memorable-ways-to-add-some-spice.html</link>
			<description>Finally you found a guy or girl with whom you can&amp;#39;t wait to start most excitement time of your life. But you see lot of time for wedding and So you got lot of time to know each other even more better. The Best you can do is make this time memorable.  1. Wedding planning, will be best time pass for each of you.  Hmm, Obviously meeting in person in this courtship period would happen with this we</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/courtship-time-make-it-memorable-ways-to-add-some-spice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Expectations and Freedom in a Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>People having expectations in a relationship and willing to have freedom in relationships are few of the main reasons for not having a peaceful and healthy relationship with each other.  Having or Setting some unrealistic expectations to have in a relationship can contribute to ending their marriage.  Honestly both the people should be open in communication to each other in terms of the expectatio</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Get more Pleasure from Lotus position!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-more-pleasure-from-lotus-position.html</link>
			<description>People have sexual intercourse in different positions, generally what they most like. And Lotus position is one of the such positions where you get to see and talk to your partner in a relaxed manner during your intimate intercourse.  So what is the Lotus position? - having an&amp;nbsp;intimate&amp;nbsp;intercourse by facing the partner by sitting as close as you both can, wrap your legs around their body</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-more-pleasure-from-lotus-position.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to Have a Better Sex?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-have-a-better-sex.html</link>
			<description>For all people to have a healthy relationship, people need to have healthy communication. Many of us might have ended up with an unsatisfied sex, but did you really communicate this with your partner?  Actually one should not be silent though, ideally should speak about it, but how and when, I would leave it to the people, anyways they have their own ways of presentations and explanations.  Genera</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 12 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-have-a-better-sex.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tips to Trust Yourself more!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-trust-yourself-more.html</link>
			<description>If you are finding the tips to trust yourself more, generally at first it is better to know yourself and what you need will be a great start. Also spending some quality time alone will help you to achieve this.  You might have come across stuff where you lose trust in yourself or sometimes stop yourself to build the trust. Because of this you may make wrong decisions or not be able to make decisio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2022 10:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-trust-yourself-more.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>People still say yes to Condoms, instead of Birth Control</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-still-say-yes-to-condoms-instead-of-birth-control.html</link>
			<description>Generally when you don&amp;rsquo;t want to get any&amp;nbsp;byproduct out of your pleasure, then you tend to have birth control or an IUD, Intrauterine device or an Implant. But many people will still prefer to&amp;nbsp;use condoms instead&amp;nbsp;of other stuff. I think there are many good reasons behind that, let&amp;#39;s see what are those.   Easy available method to avoid Pregnancy or any STIs No need of a Pres</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-still-say-yes-to-condoms-instead-of-birth-control.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tips to Overcome Suicidal Thoughts</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-overcome-suicidal-thoughts.html</link>
			<description>When you are having suicidal thoughts, first thing you need to tell your mind is you can overcome this, whatever the problem or situation is, you can overcome.  Suicidal thoughts are very difficult to handle or they are difficult to understand or explain. Sometimes they can be just going around your mind or sometimes they can become a thing, which you wish to do right away. In either case you have</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-overcome-suicidal-thoughts.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Stop Overthinking your Thoughts of Future</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</link>
			<description>Overthinking your thoughts will lead you to even more worry. If you are an overthinker or a person who thinks to take precautions for the future, then you will know exactly how it goes. Generally a problem comes to your mind, for example a worry or health or a problem at work or some sort of issue in a relationship, because of the thoughts you will be thinking about it a lot and you will try to ge</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Help People to recognize the Physical Signs of Stress and Manage the Stress</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/help-people-to-recognize-the-physical-signs-of-stress-and-manage-the-stress.html</link>
			<description>Actually stress symptoms may be affecting your health in one or the other way, even though you might not actually realise it. You might think, the stress you are facing is because of your Life or Work or the stuff which you are doing, but it cannot be true.  The true reason for having stress could be that you are not able to manage the stress properly. And this Stress will lead people to not be pr</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/help-people-to-recognize-the-physical-signs-of-stress-and-manage-the-stress.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why do people Worship?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-worship.html</link>
			<description>Based on the history and the observation, I can say everyone or every individual would or will look up for someone or something. And the society will revolve around what or who look for and what or who don&amp;rsquo;t look for.  I see this as people searching for the meaning of the purpose of their existence.  We (people) will compare each other&amp;#39;s likes or dislikes, love or hate, and it&amp;#39;s a no</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-worship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Unconditional love...</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unconditional-love.html</link>
			<description>To say, it is a love without any strings attached and selfless.  It is about acceptance. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t associate with outward appearance, supports the other person by always being there and doesn&amp;rsquo;t go away even when circumstances are bad or difficult.  It can be understood as without any reservations, without judgements, caring about the happiness of the other person without expecting any</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unconditional-love.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Friend, What comes to your mind, When you hear this word?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/friend-what-comes-to-your-mind-when-you-hear-this-word.html</link>
			<description>One line would be someone whom we are fond of talking to or spending time with.  Usually, he/she is someone apart from a family member, with whom you share a good bond, which might be fun, compassion, empathy, or maybe a few common interests with them.  Seldom, friendships are formed among unexpected people and in uncertain circumstances.&amp;nbsp; Whatever it may be, there is a belief that we meet pe</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/friend-what-comes-to-your-mind-when-you-hear-this-word.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dream, Small Information on it…</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dream-small-info-on-it.html</link>
			<description>Have you ever dreamed about something like people you have known in life, a place you are very familiar with, some incident that disturbs your mental peace, meeting an unknown person, or exploring a far distant place?  Of course, all of us dream, that’s a natural phenomenon that happens with everyone. Sometimes dreams give us a good feeling which refreshes our life or a bad feeling which keeps u</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dream-small-info-on-it.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Get to know one's Personality Type</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-to-know-ones-personality-type.html</link>
			<description>Myers-Briggs Personality Type Way to identify the personality type of the person, his/her strengths, and preferences in life. Based on the set of questions and answers to it, one’s personality type can be assessed. So, here we go, choose your response, and pick the letter corresponding to that set of questions if you agree. The questions fall under four categories which are described below. 1. A</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-to-know-ones-personality-type.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Do you know? Your Brain is the biggest Sex organ!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-you-know-your-brain-is-the-biggest-sex-organ.html</link>
			<description>Experiencing our sexuality has a lot to do with bodies, like how we like to touch and be touched by our partner. And when we think of the sex organs,&amp;nbsp;our minds think toward&amp;nbsp;the naughty parts between our legs, but our minds should be doing this right.  The&amp;nbsp;real catalyst for sexual activity&amp;nbsp;is the brain, actually not entirty brain, but specific parts of the brain, and it&amp;rsquo;s </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-you-know-your-brain-is-the-biggest-sex-organ.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Having Good Sex at any Age! Is it Really Possible?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/having-good-sex-at-any-age-is-it-really-possible.html</link>
			<description>No matter what is your gender, you can always enjoy sex for as long as you wish. And naturally sex at age of 70 or 80&amp;nbsp;may not be same&amp;nbsp;like it is at would be at 20 or 30, but It would be better in some ways.  Sex can be one of the powerful emotional experience and one of the great tool for protecting or improving your health, And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean, you can have it only at young age. Y</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/having-good-sex-at-any-age-is-it-really-possible.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>South Indian Hindu Marriage - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>South Indian weddings are traditionally going to be planned or happen for one or more than a day, which involve having mehndi for the bride particularly, in some cases times groom as well have mehndi. Few of the south Indians have Haldi ceremonies as well. Groom's arrival itself is celebrated. And the wedding ceremony begins with a few pooja’s &amp; traditions. And at the end, the couple will be sen</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Coping up with Life in an Effective Way</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coping-up-with-life-in-an-effective-way.html</link>
			<description>Life tends to go on as we go on with our daily routine works. Whatever stage of life you are in now, one has things to do, atleast to take care of family by providing what they need by doing what one can do.
                                You can play a major role in that process of fulfilling your responsibilities or a minor role, but your contribution is what makes a difference, if one apprecia</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/coping-up-with-life-in-an-effective-way.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dealing with Uncertainty, To Be Happier and Less Anxious</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dealing-with-uncertainty-to-be-happier-and-less-anxious.html</link>
			<description>Uncertainty is everywhere. It might be a pandemic like Covid, Health, Finances, Relationships etc at most everywhere we see uncertainty. We human beings always want to feel safe &amp; want to have control over our life. Uncertainity and Fear along with uncertainity will make us feeling stressed, anxious &amp; we feel like, we are missing the direction of our life. It can also put us into that thought of "</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Hanukkah John</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dealing-with-uncertainty-to-be-happier-and-less-anxious.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Is Feedback really necessary in Person's Life?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-feedback-really-necessary-in-persons-life.html</link>
			<description>Is feedback really necessary? Do people really care about the given feedback? Do people really care to give feedback? It all depends on the situation and people, whether to give or take the given feedback. And honestly everyone has their own views to consider or not to consider the feedback.
                                Every individual might have come across many people giving/taking the feedb</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-feedback-really-necessary-in-persons-life.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title> The Shawshank Redemption Movie about Life, Hope, and Freedom</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-shawshank-redemption-movie-about-life-hope-and-freedom.html</link>
			<description>Shawshank Redemption is one of the best movies ever made. Even today its stands above The Godfather movie on the IMDb top rated 250 movies. A must watch movie.
                                Their are many lines in the movie by the characters, which tells about Life, Hope and Freedom. In this article, I'm gona list of few of them.
                                 Thats The Beauty Of Music. They C</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-shawshank-redemption-movie-about-life-hope-and-freedom.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>