<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Lifestyle - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Lifestyle.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Why do people Worship?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-worship.html</link>
			<description>Based on the history and the observation, I can say everyone or every individual would or will look up for someone or something. And the society will revolve around what or who look for and what or who don&amp;rsquo;t look for.  I see this as people searching for the meaning of the purpose of their existence.  We (people) will compare each other&amp;#39;s likes or dislikes, love or hate, and it&amp;#39;s a no</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 19:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-worship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Importance of Good Sleep for Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/importance-of-good-sleep-for-health.html</link>
			<description>Nowadays in this busy life, good sleep is very rare for all kinds of generations.  Late night sleep, watching phones and computers till late at night makes our sleep very difficult.  Everyone has to sleep for at least 7 to 9 hours per night. Good sleep makes the mind calm and relaxed, even a fresh day starts with good sleep.  Hormone called melatonin is produced by the brain and helps to get sleep</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/importance-of-good-sleep-for-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Benefits of Aloe vera in Oral Health</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/benefits-of-aloe-vera-in-oral-health.html</link>
			<description>Aloe vera or aloe barbadensis, is a medicinal plant which is a thick short stemmed plant that stores aloe vera gel in its leaves.  It is used topically in most of today&amp;#39;s skin diseases,sun burns,hair etc.  Studies have shown that aloe vera has its own benefits in oral health as well.  Aloe vera contains more vitamins and minerals.  In oral health  Aloe vera plays an important role in the numbe</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jun 2022 21:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/benefits-of-aloe-vera-in-oral-health.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Unconditional love...</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unconditional-love.html</link>
			<description>To say, it is a love without any strings attached and selfless.  It is about acceptance. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t associate with outward appearance, supports the other person by always being there and doesn&amp;rsquo;t go away even when circumstances are bad or difficult.  It can be understood as without any reservations, without judgements, caring about the happiness of the other person without expecting any</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 Jun 2022 21:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unconditional-love.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Friend, What comes to your mind, When you hear this word?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/friend-what-comes-to-your-mind-when-you-hear-this-word.html</link>
			<description>One line would be someone whom we are fond of talking to or spending time with.  Usually, he/she is someone apart from a family member, with whom you share a good bond, which might be fun, compassion, empathy, or maybe a few common interests with them.  Seldom, friendships are formed among unexpected people and in uncertain circumstances.&amp;nbsp; Whatever it may be, there is a belief that we meet pe</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Apr 2022 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/friend-what-comes-to-your-mind-when-you-hear-this-word.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dream, Small Information on it…</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dream-small-info-on-it.html</link>
			<description>Have you ever dreamed about something like people you have known in life, a place you are very familiar with, some incident that disturbs your mental peace, meeting an unknown person, or exploring a far distant place?  Of course, all of us dream, that’s a natural phenomenon that happens with everyone. Sometimes dreams give us a good feeling which refreshes our life or a bad feeling which keeps u</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 18 Mar 2022 17:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dream-small-info-on-it.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Get to know one's Personality Type</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-to-know-ones-personality-type.html</link>
			<description>Myers-Briggs Personality Type Way to identify the personality type of the person, his/her strengths, and preferences in life. Based on the set of questions and answers to it, one’s personality type can be assessed. So, here we go, choose your response, and pick the letter corresponding to that set of questions if you agree. The questions fall under four categories which are described below. 1. A</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 21:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-to-know-ones-personality-type.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why do Doctors suggest Meditation?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Why-do-Doctors-suggest-Meditation.html</link>
			<description>Nowadays with this busy schedule, people are busy with earning &amp; fulfilling their dreams. By this way lots of stress &amp; strain will slowly make our body weak &amp; distress which would lead to physical &amp; mental health disturbance. One of the best ways to get rid of this problem is by doing meditation. Meditation is the process of relaxation of both physical &amp; mental health of our body, mind &amp; soul. Thi</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Why-do-Doctors-suggest-Meditation.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>South Indian Hindu Marriage - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/South-Indian-Hindu-Marriage-Andhra-Style.html</link>
			<description>South Indian weddings are traditionally going to be planned or happen for one or more than a day, which involve having mehndi for the bride particularly, in some cases times groom as well have mehndi. Few of the south Indians have Haldi ceremonies as well. Groom's arrival itself is celebrated. And the wedding ceremony begins with a few pooja’s &amp; traditions. And at the end, the couple will be sen</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 16:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/South-Indian-Hindu-Marriage-Andhra-Style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Coping up with Life in an Effective Way</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Coping-up-with-Life-in-an-Effective-way.html</link>
			<description>Life tends to go on as we go on with our daily routine works. Whatever stage of life you are in now, one has things to do, atleast to take care of family by providing what they need by doing what one can do.
                                You can play a major role in that process of fulfilling your responsibilities or a minor role, but your contribution is what makes a difference, if one apprecia</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 May 2021 23:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Coping-up-with-Life-in-an-Effective-way.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>