<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Love - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/love.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Signs of someone is in Love with you</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/signs-of-someone-is-in-love-with-you.html</link>
			<description>When someone is in love with you, their feelings and emotions can manifest in various ways. While it&amp;#39;s important to remember that everyone expresses love differently, here are some common signs that someone may be in love with you:   Constantly thinking about you: They often mention or bring up thoughts about you in conversations and frequently inquire about your well-being. Prioritizing your </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 12 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/signs-of-someone-is-in-love-with-you.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>UnConditional Love in a Couples Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>It is commonly said that Women are complex in mental nature while Men remain easy to understand and simple. Whatever be the reasons that backup this comment,&amp;nbsp;in relationships both Men and Women follow slightly diverted paths.&amp;nbsp;What Men look for in a relationship is not what motivates Women to fall in relationships. The differences in desires, mentalities, passion, expression levels etc., </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 08:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Courtship time, Make it memorable, ways to add some spice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/courtship-time-make-it-memorable-ways-to-add-some-spice.html</link>
			<description>Finally you found a guy or girl with whom you can&amp;#39;t wait to start most excitement time of your life. But you see lot of time for wedding and So you got lot of time to know each other even more better. The Best you can do is make this time memorable.  1. Wedding planning, will be best time pass for each of you.  Hmm, Obviously meeting in person in this courtship period would happen with this we</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Aug 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/courtship-time-make-it-memorable-ways-to-add-some-spice.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>