<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Marriage - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marriage.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Ten Most Common Marriage Questions and Answers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-most-common-marriage-questions-and-answers.html</link>
			<description>Here are ten common marriage questions along with brief answers:  How can we improve communication in our marriage?   Answer: Prioritize active listening, express yourself honestly and respectfully, and seek to understand each other&amp;#39;s perspectives.   How do we handle conflicts and disagreements?   Answer: Approach conflicts with empathy, compromise, and a willingness to find mutually satisfact</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 07:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-most-common-marriage-questions-and-answers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Is Life worth Living without Marriage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-life-worth-living-without-marriage.html</link>
			<description>Yes, life is worth living without marriage. Marriage is a personal choice, and not being married does not diminish the value or worth of an individual&amp;#39;s life. There are many fulfilling and meaningful experiences, relationships, and accomplishments that can be pursued outside of marriage.  The worth and fulfillment of life come from various sources, such as personal growth, meaningful connectio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/is-life-worth-living-without-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lessons to be learnt from Marriage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-to-be-learnt-from-marriage.html</link>
			<description>Marriage is a complex and deeply personal experience, and the lessons one can learn from it can vary based on individual circumstances. However, here are some common lessons that people often learn from their marriages:   Communication is key: Effective communication is crucial for a healthy and thriving marriage. Learning to express your thoughts, emotions, and needs openly and honestly, while al</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-to-be-learnt-from-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Expectations and Freedom in a Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>People having expectations in a relationship and willing to have freedom in relationships are few of the main reasons for not having a peaceful and healthy relationship with each other.  Having or Setting some unrealistic expectations to have in a relationship can contribute to ending their marriage.  Honestly both the people should be open in communication to each other in terms of the expectatio</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>South Indian Hindu Marriage - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>South Indian weddings are traditionally going to be planned or happen for one or more than a day, which involve having mehndi for the bride particularly, in some cases times groom as well have mehndi. Few of the south Indians have Haldi ceremonies as well. Groom's arrival itself is celebrated. And the wedding ceremony begins with a few pooja’s &amp; traditions. And at the end, the couple will be sen</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>