<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Migrate - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Drupal 10 is coming in a few days!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-ten-is-coming-in-a-few-days.html</link>
			<description>Drupal 10 is planned to be released in December 2022. Drupal 10 will be straightforward upgrades like Drupal 8 to 9. Upgrade processes used are more or less similar. Mostly you need to keep your current site up to date with the latest drupal core and contributed projects.  What is new in Drupal 10?  Drupal 10 is a refined version of Drupal 9 with the certain features   Claro administration theme i</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Dec 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-ten-is-coming-in-a-few-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Migrate your site from Drupal 7 To Drupal 9?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate-your-site-from-drupal-seven-to-drupal-nine.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see what are the important things you need to understand for the migration of your Drupal 7 site to the Drupal 9 site. And if you see from your Business perspective, Drupal 7 was launched nine years ago and this is the perfect time for some reassessment of the needs of site users &amp; content managers. And if you see from Drupal’s end, Initially, Drupal 7 end of lif</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrate-your-site-from-drupal-seven-to-drupal-nine.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal 7 to Drupal 8/9 Audits</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal--to-drupalaudits.html</link>
			<description>Migration from Drupal 7 to Drupal 8/9 is more of a re-build than a simple upgrade. We can move the content. users and other configuration with the help of core system, But still their will be a need to re-write custom modules or themes and some times contrib ones as well. By having a list which helps us to Audit any D7 Project to Drupal 8/9 migration would help start quick.                        </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal--to-drupalaudits.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>