<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Munnar - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/munnar.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Ten best hill stations to Travel Solo in South India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in South India offers a unique blend of tranquility, adventure and scenic beauty.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in South India for solo travelers:   Munnar, Kerala   Known for its tea gardens, rolling hills and pleasant weather, Munnar is a great destination for solo travelers. The serene environment and numerous trekking trails make it ideal for exploring</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 08:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in South India to travel in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>South India offers several destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers due to their cooler climates, hill stations and coastal areas.  Here are some of the best places to visit in South India during the hot summer months, along with reasons, ways to travel and the best time to visit:    Ooty, Tamil Nadu:   Why: Ooty, also known as the &amp;quot;Queen of Hill Stations,&amp;quot; offers c</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 08:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Anamudi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-anamudi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Anamudi, standing as the highest peak in the Western Ghats and South India, is a wonderful destination for nature lovers and trekkers. It&amp;#39;s situated in the Eravikulam National Park near Munnar, Kerala.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip from Bangalore to Anamudi:  Bangalore to Munnar   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-anamudi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Munnar Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-munnar-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Munnar can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the picturesque tea plantations, misty hills and serene lakes of this charming hill station in Kerala. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey,  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Dindigul -&amp;gt; Munnar -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Salem -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Munnar   Start your trip early in</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-munnar-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>