<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Ooty - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ooty.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Ten best hill stations to Travel Solo in South India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in South India offers a unique blend of tranquility, adventure and scenic beauty.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in South India for solo travelers:   Munnar, Kerala   Known for its tea gardens, rolling hills and pleasant weather, Munnar is a great destination for solo travelers. The serene environment and numerous trekking trails make it ideal for exploring</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 08:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in South India to travel in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>South India offers several destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers due to their cooler climates, hill stations and coastal areas.  Here are some of the best places to visit in South India during the hot summer months, along with reasons, ways to travel and the best time to visit:    Ooty, Tamil Nadu:   Why: Ooty, also known as the &amp;quot;Queen of Hill Stations,&amp;quot; offers c</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 08:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kochi Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from&amp;nbsp;Bangalore&amp;nbsp;to Kochi, If you are&amp;nbsp;Solo&amp;nbsp;riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Kochi and one couple more quick visits in Mysore, Ooty and Coimbatore on the way.  Kochi, called as&amp;nbsp;Queen of the Arabian Sea, is one of the major port cities in the coast of India and also has </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Ooty Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</link>
			<description>Three days Trip from Bangalore  Ooty  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Ooty known as the Queen of the hill stations in South In</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>