<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>People - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>I’m Sorry, Why is apologizing so difficult?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/i-m-sorry-why-is-apologizing-so-difficult.html</link>
			<description>Apologizing can be difficult for several reasons, including:   Pride and Ego: Apologizing often requires admitting fault or wrongdoing, which can be challenging for individuals who are proud or have a strong sense of ego. Admitting mistakes may feel like a blow to one&amp;#39;s self-image or reputation. Fear of Rejection or Confrontation: Some people avoid apologizing because they fear negative reacti</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/i-m-sorry-why-is-apologizing-so-difficult.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why do I apologize for everything and How to avoid doing it?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-i-apologize-for-everything-and-how-to-avoid-doing-it.html</link>
			<description>Apologizing excessively for everything can stem from various underlying reasons, including a desire to avoid conflict, fear of rejection, low self-esteem, or a habit developed over time. While apologizing can be a positive behavior in appropriate situations, excessive apologies can undermine your self-confidence and convey a lack of assertiveness.  Here are some steps to avoid apologizing excessiv</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 17 Apr 2024 21:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-i-apologize-for-everything-and-how-to-avoid-doing-it.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What percentage of Indians are vegetarian?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</link>
			<description>Approximately 30-40% of the population in India is estimated to follow a vegetarian diet. However, this percentage can vary depending on the region, cultural practices and religious beliefs.  Why Indians Follow Vegetarianism:   Religious Beliefs:   Hinduism: Many Hindus follow a vegetarian diet as part of their religious beliefs, which promote compassion and non-violence (ahimsa). They believe in </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Few relationship events in life, those change people's personality?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/few-relationship-events-in-life-those-change-peoples-personality.html</link>
			<description>Relationship events can indeed have a significant impact on a person&amp;#39;s personality, shaping their behaviors, attitudes and emotional responses. These events can occur at any stage of a relationship, from the initial stages of courtship to long-term commitment.  Here are some relationship events that can lead to personality changes and the reasons behind them:   Falling in Love:   Falling in lo</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Apr 2024 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/few-relationship-events-in-life-those-change-peoples-personality.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>