<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Php - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/php.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Understanding the SOLID Principles in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</link>
			<description>The SOLID principles are a set of five fundamental design principles in object-oriented programming aimed at improving software design, making it more understandable, flexible, and maintainable. These principles are especially relevant for developers working with PHP and similar languages.  Let&amp;#39;s dive into each principle, exploring its meaning and how it can be applied effectively in PHP.  1. </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:17 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to PHP 8 and Key Differences from PHP 7</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-php--and-key-differences-from-php-.html</link>
			<description>PHP 8, released on November 26, 2020, introduces significant improvements and new features that enhance performance, syntax, and overall developer experience. This version emphasizes performance optimizations, new language features, and better error handling, streamlining the development process and providing developers with more tools to write clean, efficient code.  Key Differences Between PHP 8</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:17 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-php--and-key-differences-from-php-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to run PHPUnit test cases on your local machine for Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-run-phpunit-test-cases-on-your-local-machine-for-drupal.html</link>
			<description>Running PHPUnit tests helps ensure that your Drupal module behaves as expected and provides a reliable way to identify and fix issues during development.  To run PHPUnit test cases on your local machine for Drupal, follow these steps:  Install PHPUnit and its dependency:   Make sure you have PHP and Composer installed on your local machine. If you don&amp;#39;t have PHPUnit installed, you can install </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-run-phpunit-test-cases-on-your-local-machine-for-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of Local Php Security Checker for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how the Local PHP Security Checker library will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated security review. Here comes the Local PHP Security Checker library, which checks for any known vulnerabilities in the package dependencies.  Th</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PhpStan on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development and code review process. We have a similar helpful article related to Phpcs, have a check of this.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here come</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Twig Templates in Drupal?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how a developer can work with Twig templates, and how to override templates (if needed) and create template suggestions with hooks, so that templates could be easily managed.  Basically drupal allows people to override the existing twig templates, so that people can fully have control on the html generated via the custom theme.  First thing, we need to make sur</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Quick reference of Code Reviews for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how your Drupal team can do code reviews and available tools or libraries which help people in the team to do the code reviews seamlessly.  It&amp;rsquo;s pretty important to follow a few guidelines as well, so that all people or developers in the team are on the same page.  Firstly, for the code reviews to be at their best, the committed code should be more organis</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PHPCS on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  And to make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here comes the PHP codesniffer and Drupal coder module.  If you are maintaini</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Core</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-drupal-offers-as-responsive-web-design-within-core.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we gonna see What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Drupal Core for developers. While Drupal 8 was out and it had a buzz of being responsive, mobile friendly. And yes, the Internet is on the verge of being dominated by smartphones &amp; Drupal needs to be prepared.Mobile friendly will also mean the content is first. From a big screen to a little screen, elements would look</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-drupal-offers-as-responsive-web-design-within-core.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Know why Symfony framework was picked by Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/know-why-symfony-framework-was-picked-by-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we gonna see why Symfony was picked for Drupal and what it changes for developers. As we all know PHP evolved rapidly in the past years, and unfortunately, Drupal adjustment to this development was not satisfying, especially in the case of software engineering patterns adoption. And that is one of the reasons why Drupal Developers had to come up with creative ways to deal with suc</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/know-why-symfony-framework-was-picked-by-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understand why Twig is replacing PHP Template in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understand-why-twig-is-replacing-php-template-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>A completely new template engine is introduced in Drupal. The templating system in all previous versions of Drupal is using theme_* functions and PHP-based *.tpl.php files. Now, this has been completely replaced in Drupal 8. Instead of using theme functions and theme template files, Drupal is now using the Twig templating system.                            Twig is a PHP-based compiled templating l</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understand-why-twig-is-replacing-php-template-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>AES Encrypt &amp; Decrypt</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aes-encrypt-decrypt.html</link>
			<description>Advanced Encryption Standard, where we use AES-256 to encrypt the data with Cipher. Encrypt &amp;amp; Decrypt approach taken is &amp;#39;Cipher Block Chaining&amp;#39; method &amp;#39;AES-256-CBC&amp;#39;.  AES Encrypt   We would have the &amp;#39;Secret&amp;#39; stored in a file which is other than the web root.    $key = hash(&amp;#39;sha256&amp;#39;, $secret, true);   Hash the &amp;#39;Secret&amp;#39; with sha256, this gives you the &amp;#39</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aes-encrypt-decrypt.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Profiling Drupal Performance with Webgrind and Xdebug</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/profiling-drupal-performance-with-webgrind-and-xdebug.html</link>
			<description>Xdebug Profiling is all about measuring the performance of PHP code. In this article you gonna see how your measure the performance of your php code using webgrid and the xdebug.  Requirements:   Xdebug, with profiler enabled Webgrind Xdebug Addon plugin for browser   1. Xdebug with profiler enabled  For setting up the environment, edit the php.ini file and add following lines.  xdebug.profiler_en</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/profiling-drupal-performance-with-webgrind-and-xdebug.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Configuring &amp; Debugging Drupal on PHPStorm with XDebug on Ubuntu</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuring-debugging-drupal--phpstorm-xdebug-ubuntu.html</link>
			<description>Debugging the code is one of the important process for a developer, So now this article will help you to configure the Phpstorm for debugging the Drupal 7 application with the help of xDebug.  The configuration made in this article refers specifically to the Ubuntu machine, which has Apache2 webserver running and xDebug installed.   Initally open terminal, and check the php version   $ php -v   yo</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 16:14:18 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuring-debugging-drupal--phpstorm-xdebug-ubuntu.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>