<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Php - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/php.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Mastering Graph Algorithms in PHP: Implementing Traversals and Shortest Path Algorithms</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mastering-graph-algorithms-in-php-implementing-traversals-and-shortest-path-algorithms.html</link>
			<description>Graphs are one of the most powerful and flexible data structures in computer science, widely used for solving problems like shortest path finding, network analysis, and much more. In PHP 8, developers can leverage modern language features and optimized approaches to implement and optimize graph-related algorithms.  In this article, we will explore graph data structures, common graph traversals, an</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 07:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mastering-graph-algorithms-in-php-implementing-traversals-and-shortest-path-algorithms.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mastering Dynamic Programming in PHP: A Deep Dive into Classic Algorithms</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mastering-dynamic-programming-in-php-a-deep-dive-into-classic-algorithms.html</link>
			<description>Dynamic Programming (DP) is a powerful technique used to solve complex problems by breaking them down into simpler subproblems. It is particularly useful for optimization problems, where the goal is to find the best solution under given constraints. DP is often seen in algorithms that require making decisions at multiple steps, where solutions to subproblems are reused to avoid redundant calculati</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mastering-dynamic-programming-in-php-a-deep-dive-into-classic-algorithms.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Advanced Sorting and Searching Algorithms in PHP: Quick Sort, Merge Sort, Heap Sort, and Binary Search Trees</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advanced-sorting-and-searching-algorithms-in-php-quick-sort-merge-sort-heap-sort-and-binary-search-trees.html</link>
			<description>Sorting and searching are foundational operations in computer science. Understanding the efficient algorithms for these tasks can significantly enhance the performance of your applications.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore three advanced sorting algorithms &amp;mdash; Quick Sort, Merge Sort, and Heap Sort &amp;mdash; and dive into implementing Binary Search Trees (BST) in PHP 8.  We&amp;rsquo;ll include </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advanced-sorting-and-searching-algorithms-in-php-quick-sort-merge-sort-heap-sort-and-binary-search-trees.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Data Structures in PHP: Implementing Stacks, Queues, Linked Lists, and SPL Classes</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/data-structures-in-php-implementing-stacks-queues-linked-lists-and-spl-classes.html</link>
			<description>Data structures are an integral part of programming, offering efficient ways to store and organize data. As PHP evolves, understanding how to implement and utilize common data structures like Stacks, Queues, and Linked Lists will make you a more proficient PHP developer. PHP 8 provides a range of options, from manual implementations to built-in SPL (Standard PHP Library) classes that offer high pe</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 07:59:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/data-structures-in-php-implementing-stacks-queues-linked-lists-and-spl-classes.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Optimizing a Product Catalog Microservice with Profiling Tools in PHP Using DDEV and Visual Studio Code</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimizing-a-product-catalog-microservice-with-profiling-tools-in-php-using-ddev-and-visual-studio-code.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we will enhance the product catalog microservice we built earlier by integrating Xdebug for profiling, specifically tailored for development in Visual Studio Code (VS Code). We will include detailed setup instructions, ensuring a smooth experience while profiling your application.  Overview  Key Components   PHP 8: The programming language for our microservice. MySQL: The database</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 08:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimizing-a-product-catalog-microservice-with-profiling-tools-in-php-using-ddev-and-visual-studio-code.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Code Profiling and Performance Optimization of an Existing PHP Project</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/code-profiling-and-performance-optimization-of-an-existing-php-project.html</link>
			<description>As applications grow in complexity, ensuring optimal performance becomes critical. Code profiling and performance optimization are essential practices that help developers identify bottlenecks and improve the efficiency of their PHP applications.  In this article, we will explore the tools and techniques for code profiling and performance optimization in PHP 8.  What is Code Profiling?  Code profi</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 08:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/code-profiling-and-performance-optimization-of-an-existing-php-project.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Advanced OOP Features in PHP: Final Classes, Magic Methods, and Late Static Binding</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advanced-oop-features-in-php-final-classes-magic-methods-and-late-static-binding.html</link>
			<description>Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) is a programming paradigm that uses objects and classes to design and structure code. PHP, especially in its latest iteration, PHP 8, provides several advanced OOP features that enhance its capabilities and allow for more robust and maintainable code.  In this article, we will explore three advanced OOP features in PHP 8: final classes, magic methods, and late sta</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advanced-oop-features-in-php-final-classes-magic-methods-and-late-static-binding.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing a Redis Cache for Product Catalog Data in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-redis-cache-for-product-catalog-data-in-php.html</link>
			<description>Caching is a vital technique for improving application performance, especially in e-commerce platforms where product catalog data is frequently accessed. By using Redis as a caching layer, you can significantly reduce database load and improve response times for users.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the steps to implement a Redis cache for product catalog data in a PHP 8 application.  </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-redis-cache-for-product-catalog-data-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to Caching and Setting Up Redis in PHP 8</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-caching-and-setting-up-redis-in-php-.html</link>
			<description>Caching is a fundamental technique used in software development to enhance performance and efficiency by storing frequently accessed data in a temporary storage layer. In PHP 8, caching can significantly reduce load times and improve the overall user experience of web applications.  This article will provide an overview of caching, its benefits, and common use cases.  What is Caching?  Caching inv</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 10:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-caching-and-setting-up-redis-in-php-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing a Notification System Using the Observer Pattern in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-notification-system-using-the-observer-pattern-in-php.html</link>
			<description>The Observer pattern is a powerful design pattern that promotes a one-to-many dependency between objects. This pattern is particularly useful in scenarios where changes in one object need to be reflected across multiple objects. A classic use case for the Observer pattern is in building a notification system, where subscribers (observers) are notified of changes in a publisher (subject).  In this </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 15:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-notification-system-using-the-observer-pattern-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>When and How to Use Each Design Pattern in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-and-how-to-use-each-design-pattern-in-php.html</link>
			<description>Design patterns are proven solutions to common problems in software design. In PHP 8, these patterns can enhance code readability, maintainability and scalability.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore some of the most common design patterns, when to use them and how to implement them in PHP 8.  1. Singleton Pattern  When to Use   Use the Singleton pattern when you need to ensure that a class has </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 06:51:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-and-how-to-use-each-design-pattern-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Exploring Design Patterns in PHP 8: Strategy, Observer and Decorator</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/exploring-design-patterns-in-php--strategy-observer-and-decorator.html</link>
			<description>Design patterns are essential tools for software developers, providing proven solutions to common problems. In PHP 8, leveraging design patterns can lead to more maintainable, scalable and flexible code.  This article will explore three key design patterns: Strategy, Observer and Decorator. We will delve into their principles and provide practical examples to illustrate how they can be implemented</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 16:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/exploring-design-patterns-in-php--strategy-observer-and-decorator.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing a Logger System Using the Singleton Pattern in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-logger-system-using-the-singleton-pattern-in-php.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll create a simple logger system using the Singleton Pattern in PHP.  This logger will allow you to log messages to a file, ensuring that there is only one instance of the logger throughout your application.  Step-by-Step Implementation  Step 1: Create the Logger Class  We&amp;#39;ll start by defining a Logger class that follows the Singleton Pattern. This class will have metho</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 08:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-logger-system-using-the-singleton-pattern-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing Design Patterns in Real-World PHP Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-design-patterns-in-real-world-php-applications.html</link>
			<description>Design patterns are proven solutions to common software design problems. They help improve code readability, maintainability and scalability.  In this article, we&amp;#39;ll explore how to implement some of the most commonly used design patterns, Factory, Singleton and Dependency Injection, in real-world PHP applications using PHP 8.  1. Factory Pattern  Scenario  Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re developing an e-</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 20:39:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-design-patterns-in-real-world-php-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to Design Patterns: Factory, Singleton and Dependency Injection</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-design-patterns-factory-singleton-and-dependency-injection.html</link>
			<description>Design patterns are essential tools for developers looking to write clean, maintainable and scalable code. In PHP 8, leveraging design patterns can significantly enhance your software architecture.  This article introduces three fundamental design patterns: Factory, Singleton and Dependency Injection, explaining their purpose, use cases and providing practical examples.  1. Factory Pattern  What i</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-design-patterns-factory-singleton-and-dependency-injection.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Designing Efficient Schemas for Web Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/designing-efficient-schemas-for-web-applications.html</link>
			<description>The design of an efficient database schema is crucial for the performance, scalability and maintainability of any web application. A well-designed schema ensures that your web application can handle large volumes of data, retrieve information quickly and grow with the increasing needs of your users.  This article explores best practices for designing efficient schemas, focusing on the balance betw</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 08:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/designing-efficient-schemas-for-web-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding the SOLID Principles in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</link>
			<description>The SOLID principles are a set of five fundamental design principles in object-oriented programming aimed at improving software design, making it more understandable, flexible and maintainable. These principles are especially relevant for developers working with PHP and similar languages.  Let&amp;#39;s dive into each principle, exploring its meaning and how it can be applied effectively in PHP.  1. S</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to PHP 8 and Key Differences from PHP 7</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-php--and-key-differences-from-php-.html</link>
			<description>PHP 8, released on November 26, 2020, introduces significant improvements and new features that enhance performance, syntax and overall developer experience. This version emphasizes performance optimizations, new language features and better error handling, streamlining the development process and providing developers with more tools to write clean, efficient code.  Key Differences Between PHP 8 a</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 11:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-php--and-key-differences-from-php-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to run PHPUnit test cases on your local machine for Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-run-phpunit-test-cases-on-your-local-machine-for-drupal.html</link>
			<description>Running PHPUnit tests helps ensure that your Drupal module behaves as expected and provides a reliable way to identify and fix issues during development.  To run PHPUnit test cases on your local machine for Drupal, follow these steps:  Install PHPUnit and its dependency:   Make sure you have PHP and Composer installed on your local machine. If you don&amp;#39;t have PHPUnit installed, you can install </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-run-phpunit-test-cases-on-your-local-machine-for-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of Local Php Security Checker for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how the Local PHP Security Checker library will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated security review. Here comes the Local PHP Security Checker library, which checks for any known vulnerabilities in the package dependencies.  Th</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PhpStan on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development and code review process. We have a similar helpful article related to Phpcs, have a check of this.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here come</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Twig Templates in Drupal?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how a developer can work with Twig templates and how to override templates (if needed) and create template suggestions with hooks, so that templates could be easily managed.  Basically drupal allows people to override the existing twig templates, so that people can fully have control on the html generated via the custom theme.  First thing, we need to make sure</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Quick reference of Code Reviews for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how your Drupal team can do code reviews and available tools or libraries which help people in the team to do the code reviews seamlessly.  It&amp;rsquo;s pretty important to follow a few guidelines as well, so that all people or developers in the team are on the same page.  Firstly, for the code reviews to be at their best, the committed code should be more organis</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PHPCS on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  And to make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here comes the PHP codesniffer and Drupal coder module.  If you are maintaini</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Core</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-drupal-offers-as-responsive-web-design-within-core.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we gonna see What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Drupal Core for developers. While Drupal 8 was out and it had a buzz of being responsive, mobile friendly. And yes, the Internet is on the verge of being dominated by smartphones &amp; Drupal needs to be prepared.Mobile friendly will also mean the content is first. From a big screen to a little screen, elements would look</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-drupal-offers-as-responsive-web-design-within-core.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Know why Symfony framework was picked by Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/know-why-symfony-framework-was-picked-by-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we gonna see why Symfony was picked for Drupal and what it changes for developers. As we all know PHP evolved rapidly in the past years and unfortunately, Drupal adjustment to this development was not satisfying, especially in the case of software engineering patterns adoption. And that is one of the reasons why Drupal Developers had to come up with creative ways to deal with such</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/know-why-symfony-framework-was-picked-by-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understand why Twig is replacing PHP Template in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understand-why-twig-is-replacing-php-template-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>A completely new template engine is introduced in Drupal. The templating system in all previous versions of Drupal is using theme_* functions and PHP-based *.tpl.php files. Now, this has been completely replaced in Drupal 8. Instead of using theme functions and theme template files, Drupal is now using the Twig templating system.                            Twig is a PHP-based compiled templating l</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understand-why-twig-is-replacing-php-template-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>AES Encrypt &amp; Decrypt</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aes-encrypt-decrypt.html</link>
			<description>Advanced Encryption Standard, where we use AES-256 to encrypt the data with Cipher. Encrypt &amp;amp; Decrypt approach taken is &amp;#39;Cipher Block Chaining&amp;#39; method &amp;#39;AES-256-CBC&amp;#39;.  AES Encrypt   We would have the &amp;#39;Secret&amp;#39; stored in a file which is other than the web root.    $key = hash(&amp;#39;sha256&amp;#39;, $secret, true);   Hash the &amp;#39;Secret&amp;#39; with sha256, this gives you the &amp;#39</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/aes-encrypt-decrypt.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Profiling Drupal Performance with Webgrind and Xdebug</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/profiling-drupal-performance-with-webgrind-and-xdebug.html</link>
			<description>Xdebug Profiling is all about measuring the performance of PHP code. In this article you gonna see how your measure the performance of your php code using webgrid and the xdebug.  Requirements:   Xdebug, with profiler enabled Webgrind Xdebug Addon plugin for browser   1. Xdebug with profiler enabled  For setting up the environment, edit the php.ini file and add following lines.  xdebug.profiler_en</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/profiling-drupal-performance-with-webgrind-and-xdebug.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Configuring &amp; Debugging Drupal on PHPStorm with XDebug on Ubuntu</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuring-debugging-drupal--phpstorm-xdebug-ubuntu.html</link>
			<description>Debugging the code is one of the important process for a developer, So now this article will help you to configure the Phpstorm for debugging the Drupal 7 application with the help of xDebug.  The configuration made in this article refers specifically to the Ubuntu machine, which has Apache2 webserver running and xDebug installed.   Initally open terminal and check the php version   $ php -v   you</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 11:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuring-debugging-drupal--phpstorm-xdebug-ubuntu.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>