<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Politics - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/politics.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Crimes: Justice for Sowjanya Activist Mahesh Shetty Thimarodi Detained</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-crimes-sowjanya-justice-activist-mahesh-shetty-thimarodi-detained.html</link>
			<description>In a dramatic turn of events, Brahmavara police detained activist Mahesh Shetty Thimarodi from his residence on Thursday morning. Thimarodi, a well-known face in the ongoing struggle for justice in the Soujanya rape and murder case of 2012, has long been vocal against political interference and systemic failures in the case.  According to reports, the action against him came after he spoke on a Yo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-crimes-sowjanya-justice-activist-mahesh-shetty-thimarodi-detained.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Constitution (130th Amendment) Bill 2025 – What does it propose?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-the-constitution-one-hundred-and-thirtieth-amendment-bill--proposes.html</link>
			<description>New Delhi&amp;mdash; The Union government has introduced the Constitution (One Hundred and Thirtieth Amendment) Bill, 2025, a measure that would force the Prime Minister, Chief Ministers, and all Union/State (and NCT of Delhi) ministers to demit office if they remain in custody for 30 consecutive days in connection with an offence punishable with imprisonment of five years or more. The Lok Sabha has r</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Aug 2025 08:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-the-constitution-one-hundred-and-thirtieth-amendment-bill--proposes.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>India Stands Tall: Navigating Geopolitical Tensions Without Bowing to Pressure</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/india-stands-tall-navigating-geopolitical-tensions-without-bowing-to-pressure.html</link>
			<description>In today&amp;rsquo;s complex and volatile global environment, India is emerging not just as a regional power, but as a nation capable of making sovereign choices amidst growing international scrutiny. With Prime Minister Narendra Modi at the helm, India has demonstrated that it will not bend under external pressure&amp;mdash;be it from the West, the East, or any geopolitical bloc. At the heart of this sta</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/india-stands-tall-navigating-geopolitical-tensions-without-bowing-to-pressure.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The MiG-21: India’s First Supersonic Jet Retires After 62 Years of Glorious Service</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-mig--india-s-first-supersonic-jet-retires-after--years-of-glorious-service.html</link>
			<description>India&amp;rsquo;s journey toward becoming a modern air power took flight with the MiG‑21, a supersonic fighter aircraft that served the nation with distinction for over six decades. As the Indian Air Force prepares to bid farewell to this iconic aircraft in September 2025, it is a moment of reflection and pride for every Indian.  A Historic Induction  The MiG-21 was inducted into the Indian Air Forc</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-mig--india-s-first-supersonic-jet-retires-after--years-of-glorious-service.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Donald Trump and the Elusive Nobel Peace Prize: Past Attempts, Present Claims, and Persistent Barriers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/donald-trump-and-the-elusive-nobel-peace-prize-past-attempts-present-claims-and-persistent-barriers.html</link>
			<description>Few honors in the world carry as much symbolic and moral weight as the Nobel Peace Prize. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a medal&amp;mdash;it&amp;rsquo;s a historic recognition of an individual&amp;#39;s contribution to peace and human progress. Donald Trump, former U.S. President, has openly expressed his desire to receive this prestigious award.  Despite multiple nominations and public claims of deserving it, he remai</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/donald-trump-and-the-elusive-nobel-peace-prize-past-attempts-present-claims-and-persistent-barriers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>RCB, Alcohol Ownership, and the Public Spectacle: A Modern-Colosseum Distraction?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rcb-alcohol-ownership-and-the-public-spectacle-a-modern-colosseum-distraction.html</link>
			<description>Every April&amp;ndash;May from past 18 years, Bengaluru transforms into a sea of red and black as fans don RCB jerseys and pour into pubs, chanting their team&amp;rsquo;s praises. For many, RCB (Royal Challengers Bengaluru) isn&amp;rsquo;t just a cricket franchise&amp;mdash;it&amp;rsquo;s Karnataka pride incarnate. 🏏 But beneath the enthusiasm lies a deeper truth: RCB is owned by United Spirits, a subsidiary of Di</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rcb-alcohol-ownership-and-the-public-spectacle-a-modern-colosseum-distraction.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Should people really vote in democracy?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</link>
			<description>Yes, voting is a crucial aspect of a democratic society and it plays a fundamental role in shaping the governance and policies of a nation.  Here are some reasons why voting is important:   Representation: Voting allows individuals to have a say in choosing representatives who will make decisions on their behalf. By participating in elections, citizens can help ensure that their interests and conc</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Droupadi Murmu, New President of India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</link>
			<description>Droupadi Murmu was nominated to President elections and on 21st of July 2022 elections counting was finished and Droupadi Murmu won the elections and will be the New President of India, Murmu is likely to take oath on July 25 as President of India.  A few highlights of 15th President of India   Droupadi Murmu will be the first person belonging to a Scheduled Tribe (ST) community to be elected as t</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>President of India nominated Veerendra Heggade, P.T. Usha, Ilaiyaraaja and V. Vijayendra Prasad to the Rajya Sabha</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</link>
			<description>According to the Fourth Schedule (Articles 4(1) and 80(2)) of the Constitution of India, The President of India can nominate 12 members to Rajya Sabha for a term of six-years for their contributions towards Arts, Literature, Sciences and Social Services.  Maybe earlier most of the South Indian peoples, for this matter all the Indian people might not be aware that The President of India can nominat</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Karnataka Editors’ Jail Sentence Sparks Allegations of Intimidation</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/karnataka-editors-jail-sentence-sparks-allegations-of-intimidation.html</link>
			<description>Bengaluru  The controversy surrounding the Karnataka Assembly&amp;rsquo;s decision to sentence two editors to one year in prison for alleged defamation has deepened. Reports reveal one editor claims ongoing intimidation from a sitting legislator.  Assembly Verdict and Legal Roadmap  On June 21, 2017, the Assembly&amp;rsquo;s Privileges Committee found Anil Raj, editor of the Yelahanka tabloid Yelahanka Vo</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 08:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/karnataka-editors-jail-sentence-sparks-allegations-of-intimidation.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>