<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
<title>Quick Read - Peoples BLOG</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/index.html</link>
  <description/>
  <language>en</language>
  <item>
  <title>The Monkey and the Cap Seller</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-monkey-and-the-cap-seller.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a bustling market town, there lived a cap seller named Thomas. Thomas traveled from village to village, selling his colorful caps to the villagers. One sunny day, as Thomas journeyed through a dense forest, he grew tired from the heat and decided to take a nap under a shady tree.  Unbeknownst to Thomas, a mischievous troop of monkeys inhabited the trees above him. Curious abou</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 05 Apr 2024 12:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-monkey-and-the-cap-seller.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Rooster and the Pearl</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-rooster-and-the-pearl.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village nestled among green hills, there lived a proud rooster named Rufus. Rufus strutted around the village, boasting about his magnificent plumage and his loud, crowing voice that woke everyone up at dawn.  One day, while scratching around in the dirt near a farmer&amp;#39;s house, Rufus spotted something shiny buried beneath the soil. With great excitement, he dug fran</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 19:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-rooster-and-the-pearl.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Ant and the Grasshopper</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-ant-and-the-grasshopper.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a bustling meadow, there lived an industrious ant named Andy and a carefree grasshopper named Greg. Summer had arrived, and the meadow was abundant with vibrant flowers and lush greenery.  Andy, the ant, was a diligent worker. He spent his days collecting food and storing it in his anthill. He knew that winter would soon follow, and he needed to prepare for the cold months ahe</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 08:27:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-ant-and-the-grasshopper.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Fox and the Leopard</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-leopard.html</link>
  <description>In a dense forest, there lived a clever fox named Felix and a graceful leopard named Leona. Despite being very different in appearance and habits, they were good friends and often shared stories near a serene pond.  One day, as they lounged in the shade of a tall oak tree, Felix remarked, &amp;quot;Leona, my friend, have you ever wondered what it would be like to exchange our spots and tails? I&amp;#39;ve</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 27 Mar 2024 08:38:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-leopard.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Caged Bird and the Free Bird</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-caged-bird-and-the-free-bird.html</link>
  <description>In a lush and vibrant forest, there were two birds: one lived in a golden cage, and the other soared freely through the open skies.  The caged bird had vibrant plumage, and its melodic songs filled the air. However, no matter how beautiful its cage, the bird longed for the freedom it saw in the free bird that soared above the trees.  One day, the free bird landed on the golden bars of the cage, an</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 18:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-caged-bird-and-the-free-bird.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Boy and the Apple Tree</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-and-the-apple-tree.html</link>
  <description>In a quaint village nestled between rolling hills, there was a wise old apple tree that stood in the center of a small orchard. The villagers believed the tree possessed magical qualities, and it was said that it could grant a single wish to anyone who truly respected and cared for it.  One day, a curious boy named Oliver discovered the ancient apple tree. Intrigued by the stories he had heard, he</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 09:03:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-and-the-apple-tree.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Elephant’s Child</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-elephants-child.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in the High and Far-Off Times, there was a curious elephant&amp;#39;s child who had a very small nose. The other elephants in the jungle had long trunks, but the elephant&amp;#39;s child was curious about everything and wanted to know what the crocodile had for dinner.  So, one day, the elephant&amp;#39;s child went to the Limpopo River, where the great grey-green, greasy Limpopo River runs </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 20 Mar 2024 09:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-elephants-child.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Little Engine That Could</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-little-engine-that-could.html</link>
  <description>In a small town nestled between rolling hills, there was a little blue engine. It wasn&amp;#39;t the biggest or the strongest, but it had a heart full of determination. One day, a big train carrying toys and goodies for children broke down on its way over the mountain.  The toys and goodies were stranded, and the town was sad because the children were eagerly waiting for their treats. The big engines </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 19:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-little-engine-that-could.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Fox and the Hedgehog</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-hedgehog.html</link>
  <description>In a peaceful forest, there lived a clever fox named Finley and a wise hedgehog named Hazel. Despite their differences, they were good friends and often shared stories near a large oak tree.  One sunny afternoon, as they basked in the dappled sunlight, Finley said, &amp;quot;Hazel, my friend, I&amp;#39;ve heard that the meadow on the other side of the forest is filled with succulent berries and ripe fruit</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 11 Mar 2024 09:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-hedgehog.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Princess and the Seven Swans</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-princess-and-the-seven-swans.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a faraway kingdom, there was a wise and kind king who had seven sons and a beautiful daughter named Eliza. The queen, unfortunately, had passed away, and the king remarried. However, the new queen was an evil sorceress who despised the king&amp;#39;s children, especially Eliza.  One day, the wicked queen cast a spell on Eliza&amp;#39;s seven brothers, turning them into swans. The curs</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 14:23:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-princess-and-the-seven-swans.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Fox and the Rabbit</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-rabbit.html</link>
  <description>In a peaceful meadow bordered by a dense forest, there lived a wise and cunning fox named Felix and a timid but clever rabbit named Rosie. The two animals were neighbors, sharing the meadow as their home.  One day, Rosie discovered a bountiful patch of delicious carrots on the outskirts of the meadow. Knowing that winter was approaching and food would become scarce, she decided to collect and stor</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 12:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-rabbit.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Patty, the milkmaid</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/patty-the-milkmaid.html</link>
  <description>In a small village, there lived a young milkmaid named Patty. Every day, Patty would milk the cows and carry the pail of fresh milk to the market to sell. As she walked, she often daydreamed about the future.  One day, while on her way to the market, Patty began to imagine what she would do with the money she earned from selling the milk. &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ll buy a dozen eggs from the market,&amp;quot; she </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 16:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/patty-the-milkmaid.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Wicked Lion and the Hare</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wicked-lion-and-the-hare.html</link>
  <description>In a dense and vibrant forest, there lived a wicked lion named Karna. Karna was feared by all the animals because of his cruel and unjust ways. One day, he came across a wise and quick-witted hare named Hari.  Karna, driven by his wicked nature, decided to make Hari&amp;#39;s life miserable. He would often threaten the hare, boasting about his strength and power. However, Hari, being wise, always mana</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 04 Dec 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wicked-lion-and-the-hare.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Elephants and the King of Mice</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-elephants-and-the-king-of-mice.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a dense and ancient forest, there lived a mighty elephant herd. The elephants, known for their strength and wisdom, were led by a wise and noble elephant named Arjun. Arjun was not only respected by his fellow elephants but also by the other animals in the forest.  In the heart of the forest, there existed a community of mice ruled by their wise and just king, named Mahendra. </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 13:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-elephants-and-the-king-of-mice.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Crane and the Crab</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-crane-and-the-crab.html</link>
  <description>In a serene pond surrounded by lush greenery, lived a crane named Kamal. Kamal was known for his long legs and sharp beak, but more so for his sly and cunning nature. On the banks of the pond, there resided a wise crab named Chandan.  One day, Kamal approached Chandan with a proposition. &amp;quot;Dear Chandan,&amp;quot; said Kamal with a devious smile, &amp;quot;I&amp;#39;ve heard there&amp;#39;s a bountiful harvest</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 30 Nov 2023 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-crane-and-the-crab.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Hunter and the Magical Bird</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-hunter-and-the-magical-bird.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a dense and enchanted forest, there lived a hunter named Ravi. Ravi was known for his exceptional skill with a bow and arrow. One day, as he ventured deeper into the forest, he heard a melodious song, unlike any birdcall he had ever heard.  Intrigued, Ravi followed the enchanting melody until he stumbled upon a dazzling bird with feathers that shimmered in every color imaginab</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 29 Nov 2023 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-hunter-and-the-magical-bird.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The crow and the pitcher</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-crow-and-the-pitcher.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a scorching summer day, a thirsty crow searched desperately for water. After a long flight, the crow finally spotted a pitcher in a garden. Eager with anticipation, the crow hurriedly flew down to the pitcher, hoping to find relief from its thirst.  However, much to the crow&amp;#39;s disappointment, the water level in the pitcher was too low for it to reach with its beak. The crow tried pec</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-crow-and-the-pitcher.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The weaver and the princess</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-weaver-and-the-princess.html</link>
  <description>In a kingdom far, far away, there was a wise and talented weaver named Arvind. His intricate designs and vibrant patterns were known throughout the land, and his skill was unmatched. The kingdom&amp;#39;s princess, Princess Lila, had heard of Arvind&amp;#39;s craftsmanship and desired to have the most exquisite tapestry ever woven.  Arvind, upon receiving the royal request, eagerly set to work. He envisio</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-weaver-and-the-princess.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>A Daring Plan</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-daring-plan.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time in the peaceful town of Eldoria, there lived a young and courageous girl named Maya. Eldoria was known for its lush green fields and vibrant meadows, but it faced a looming threat from a neighboring kingdom. The ruthless King Zephyr had set his sights on Eldoria, craving its wealth and prosperity.  Maya, with a heart full of bravery, could not stand idly by as her town faced the i</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-daring-plan.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Real Mother</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-real-mother.html</link>
  <description>Two women came before King Solomon, each claiming to be the mother of the same baby. Both women lived in the same house and had given birth within days of each other. One of the babies had died, and now both women were fiercely arguing over who was the real mother of the living child.  Unable to resolve the dispute, King Solomon, known for his wisdom, devised a plan to reveal the true mother. He o</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Nov 2023 09:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-real-mother.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Stolen Crown</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-stolen-crown.html</link>
  <description>One day, the king&amp;#39;s crown went missing, and there was an uproar in the kingdom. The guards were questioned, and an investigation was launched. Suspicion fell on a few courtiers, and they were interrogated, but no one confessed.  In the midst of this chaos, Tenali Raman approached the king and said, &amp;quot;Your Majesty, I can find the thief and retrieve your crown, but I need a week to do so.&amp;qu</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2023 13:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-stolen-crown.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Golden Egg</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-golden-egg.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a peaceful village, there lived a poor farmer named John. Despite his modest lifestyle, John was content with his simple life. He owned a small piece of land, a humble house, and a few hens.  One day, while tending to his chores, John made a remarkable discovery. One of his hens had laid an egg that shone with a brilliant golden hue. Astonished and excited, John realized that </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-golden-egg.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Cat's Judgement</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-cats-judgement.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a lush and lively forest, there lived a proud and haughty cat named Jasper. Jasper was known far and wide for his sleek fur and graceful demeanor. He would often stroll through the forest, casting disdainful glances at the other animals.  One day, as Jasper was basking in the sunlight, he overheard a group of birds chatting about a grand feast that was to be held in the honor </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 07:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-cats-judgement.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Union is Strength</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/union-is-strength.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, there was an old man who had three sons. Despite their constant bickering and disagreements, the old man remained hopeful that his sons would learn the value of unity.  To teach them this important lesson, the old man handed each son a single stick and asked them to break it. Unsurprisingly, each son easily snapped his stick in half.  Then, the old man handed each son a bundle of</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 10:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/union-is-strength.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Loyal Mongoose</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-loyal-mongoose.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village, there lived a childless couple who longed for a family. One day, their wish was granted when they found a baby mongoose abandoned near their home. Filled with joy, they adopted the little creature and named him Raj.  As Raj grew, he became a beloved member of the family, providing companionship and filling their home with happiness. The couple, in turn, shower</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 09:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-loyal-mongoose.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Stork and the Crab</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-stork-and-the-crab.html</link>
  <description>In a serene lakeside, there lived a stork named Stanley and a clever crab named Clara. They had been neighbors for quite some time, observing each other&amp;#39;s unique ways of life.  One day, as Stanley was gracefully standing in the shallow waters, he noticed Clara scurrying along the muddy shore. The stork, known for his wisdom and curiosity, approached Clara and inquired about her peculiar way of</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-stork-and-the-crab.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Brahmin’s dream</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-brahmins-dream.html</link>
  <description>In a small village, there lived a kind-hearted Brahmin named Ravi. He was known for his honesty, generosity, and deep devotion to his spiritual practices. One night, after a long day of serving the community and studying ancient scriptures, Ravi fell into a deep sleep.  In his dream, Ravi found himself in a distant land where he discovered a magnificent treasure buried beneath a tree. The treasure</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-brahmins-dream.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The foolish thief</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-foolish-thief.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village, there lived a notorious thief named Jake. Jake was known for his cunning ways, as he would often devise elaborate plans to steal from the townspeople. However, despite his cleverness, Jake had a reputation for being rather foolish.  One day, Jake decided to target the village&amp;#39;s wealthiest resident, Mr. Roberts. He had heard rumors of a precious diamond hid</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2023 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-foolish-thief.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Monkey and the Crocodile</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-monkey-and-the-crocodile.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a lush jungle beside a glistening river, there lived a clever monkey named Max and a friendly crocodile named Cody. Max and Cody had developed an unlikely friendship, spending their days chatting and sharing stories on a large rock by the riverbank.  One day, as they sat together, Cody revealed a secret to Max. He explained that his wife, Clara, had fallen gravely ill, and the</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-monkey-and-the-crocodile.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Be wise while counting</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/be-wise-while-counting.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a bustling marketplace, there was a fruit vendor named Jack. Jack was known for his honesty and fair dealings. He took great pride in carefully counting and weighing each fruit to ensure accurate pricing for his customers.  One day, a young boy named Timmy approached Jack&amp;#39;s fruit stand. He wanted to buy some apples for his family. Jack greeted Timmy with a warm smile and b</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/be-wise-while-counting.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>A Wise Old Owl</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-wise-old-owl.html</link>
  <description>In the heart of a dense forest, perched high on a sturdy branch, lived a wise old owl named Oliver. With his sparkling eyes and a coat of feathers that glowed in the moonlight, Oliver was respected by all the animals of the forest for his wisdom and counsel.  One day, a young squirrel named Sammy came to Oliver seeking advice. Sammy was impulsive and often made hasty decisions without considering </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-wise-old-owl.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Milkmaid and Her Pail</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-milkmaid-and-her-pail.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a quaint village, there lived a young milkmaid named Emma. She was known for her dreams of a better life and her penchant for daydreaming. Emma&amp;#39;s family relied on the milk she sold each day to make a living.  One sunny morning, Emma set out for the market, carrying a pail filled to the brim with fresh milk. As she walked, she started to daydream about the possibilities tha</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-milkmaid-and-her-pail.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Proud Rose</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-proud-rose.html</link>
  <description>In a beautifully tended garden, there bloomed a magnificent rose. Its petals were vibrant and fragrant, capturing the admiration of all who beheld it. The rose, aware of its exquisite beauty, held its head high with pride.  Every day, as the garden&amp;#39;s other flowers swayed gently in the breeze, the proud rose would boast about its beauty and elegance. It would belittle the other flowers, conside</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-proud-rose.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Fox and the Grapes</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-grapes.html</link>
  <description>In a lush vineyard, basking under the warm sun, there hung a cluster of juicy, ripe grapes. Their vibrant colors and tantalizing aroma caught the attention of a clever and cunning fox named Felix.  Felix, known for his quick wit and sly nature, desired the sweet taste of those grapes. He jumped and leaped, reaching with all his might, but the grapes remained just out of his grasp. Undeterred, he t</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-grapes.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Tortoise and the Hare</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-tortoise-and-the-hare.html</link>
  <description>In a peaceful forest, there lived a confident and speedy hare and a slow but determined tortoise. The hare was known for his incredible speed and often boasted about his swiftness, making fun of the tortoise for his slow nature.  One day, tired of the hare&amp;#39;s constant bragging, the tortoise challenged him to a race. The hare laughed heartily at the tortoise&amp;#39;s proposition, unable to fathom h</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-tortoise-and-the-hare.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Boy Who Cried Wolf</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-who-cried-wolf.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village nestled among rolling hills, there lived a mischievous young shepherd boy named Peter. Peter&amp;#39;s job was to watch over the village&amp;#39;s flock of sheep and protect them from any harm. However, Peter had a tendency to get bored easily and seek attention in unusual ways.  One sunny day, while tending to his sheep, Peter decided to play a trick on the villagers.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-who-cried-wolf.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Golden Touch of Midas</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-golden-touch-of-midas.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a land far away, there lived a wealthy king named Midas. Although he had riches beyond imagination, he was not content with his wealth. He constantly craved for more and desired to possess everything he laid his eyes upon.  One day, as he was walking through his magnificent garden, Midas stumbled upon a mysterious creature. It was none other than the god Dionysus, who was plea</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-golden-touch-of-midas.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The boasting traveler</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boasting-traveler.html</link>
  <description>A man came back from a tour and boasted about his adventurous journeys. He talked at length about the different people he met and his amazing feats that got him fame and praise from people everywhere. He went on to say that he went to the Rhodes where he had leaped to such distances that no man could ever match his feat.  He even went on to say that there were witnesses who would vouch for his wor</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boasting-traveler.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The camel and the baby</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-camel-and-the-baby.html</link>
  <description>One day, a camel and her baby were chatting. The baby asked, &amp;ldquo;Mother, why do we have humps?&amp;rdquo; The mother replied, &amp;ldquo;Our humps are for storing water so that we can survive in the desert&amp;rdquo;.  &amp;ldquo;Oh&amp;rdquo;, said the child, &amp;ldquo;and why do we have rounded feet mother?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Because they are meant to help us walk comfortably in the desert. These legs help us move aroun</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-camel-and-the-baby.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The farmer and the well</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-farmer-and-the-well.html</link>
  <description>A farmer looking for a source of water for his farm bought a well from his neighbor. The neighbor was cunning, though, and refused to let the farmer take water from the well. On asking why, he replied, &amp;ldquo;I sold the well to you, not the water&amp;rdquo;, and walked away. The distraught farmer didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do. So he went to Birbal, a clever man and one of the nine courtiers of Emperor </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-farmer-and-the-well.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>True friends love you anyway</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/true-friends-love-you-anyway.html</link>
  <description>Lord Krishna and Sudama were childhood friends. While Krishna thrived and prospered, Sudama didn&amp;rsquo;t. He lead the life of a poor Brahmin man, living in a small hut with his wife and kids. Most days, the kids wouldn&amp;rsquo;t even get enough to eat from what Sudama got as alms. One day, his wife suggested that he go and ask his friend Krishna for help.  Sudama was reluctant to seek favors, but he</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/true-friends-love-you-anyway.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Elephant and friends</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/elephant-and-friends.html</link>
  <description>A lone elephant wandered the forest looking for friends. She came across a monkey and asked, &amp;ldquo;Will you be my friend, monkey?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;You are too big and cannot swing on trees as I do. So I cannot be your friend&amp;rdquo;, said the monkey.  The elephant them came across a rabbit and asked him if she could be his friend. &amp;ldquo;You are too big to fit inside my burrow. You cannot be my frien</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/elephant-and-friends.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The wolf and the shepherds</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wolf-and-the-shepherds.html</link>
  <description>This is one of the many Aesop&amp;rsquo;s fables that one can relate to in any day and age.  One day a wolf was chased away from a farm for trying to steal some of the sheep for food. Later that week, the wolf came back to the farm hoping to find some food. He peeped inside the house and found the farmer and his family feasting on lamb roast.  &amp;ldquo;Aha!&amp;rdquo;, he thought. &amp;ldquo;If I were to do the</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wolf-and-the-shepherds.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The young crab and his mother.</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-young-crab-and-his-mother.html</link>
  <description>One day, a young crab and his mother were on the beach, spending some time together. The young crab gets up to move, but it can only walk sideways. His mother scolds him for walking sideways and asks him to walk forward by pointing his toes out front. The young crab responds, &amp;ldquo;I would like to walk forward mom, but I do not know how to&amp;rdquo;.  Hearing this, his mom gets up to show him how, b</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-young-crab-and-his-mother.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The other side of the wall</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-other-side-of-the-wall.html</link>
  <description>A young woman inherited a beautiful garden from her grandmother. She loved gardening too and was very proud of her garden. One day, she saw a very beautiful plant in a catalog and wanted that for her garden. She ordered it and planted it at the base of the stonewall in her backyard. She took great care of the plant, which grew quickly and had beautiful green leaves on it.  Months passed, but not a</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-other-side-of-the-wall.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The dog at the well</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-dog-at-the-well.html</link>
  <description>A dog and her pups lived on a farm, where there was a well. The mother dog told the pups, do not go near the well or play around it. One of the pups wondered why they shouldn&amp;rsquo;t go to the well and decided to explore it. He went to the well. Climbed up the wall and peeked inside.  In there, he saw his reflection and thought it was another dog. The pup saw that the other dog in the well (his re</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-dog-at-the-well.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Controlling anger</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/controlling-anger.html</link>
  <description>There was once a young boy who had problem controlling his temper. When he became angry, he would just say anything that came to his mind and hurt people. So his father gave him a bag of nails and a hammer and said, &amp;ldquo;Every time you get angry, hammer one nail into the fence in our backyard&amp;rdquo;.  The first few days the boy hammered so many nails that he emptied half the bag. Over the weeks,</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/controlling-anger.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Wet Pants</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wet-pants.html</link>
  <description>A nine-year-old boy was sitting at his desk in class, when suddenly, his pants felt wet, and there was a puddle at his feet. His heart almost skipped a beat, as he got worried that his classmates would see that and make fun of him.  He quickly wanted to do something, and saw the teacher and his classmate Susie walking towards him. Susie was carrying a bowl of goldfish. As they came closer, the boy</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wet-pants.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Bad Habits</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/bad-habits.html</link>
  <description>A wealthy businessman was worried about his son&amp;rsquo;s bad habits. He sought counsel from a wise, old man. The old man met the man&amp;rsquo;s son and took him out for a stroll. They walked into the woods, and the old man showed the boy a small sapling and asked him to pull it out. The boy did so with ease, and they walked on.  The old man then asked the boy to pull out a small plant. The boy did tha</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/bad-habits.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>How to Think Positive and Best out of a Situation? with King's Painting</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/how-to-think-positive-and-best-out-of-a-situation-with-kings-painting.html</link>
  <description>We people might have heard a saying to think positive, many times. In this quick read we are gonna see how a painter thinks positively with a situation to draw a King&amp;rsquo;s painting.  Once upon a time, there was a Kingdom. The king there only had one leg and one eye, but he was very intelligent and kind. Everyone in his kingdom lived a happy and healthy life because of their king. One day the ki</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/how-to-think-positive-and-best-out-of-a-situation-with-kings-painting.html</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>