<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
<title>Quick Read - Peoples BLOG</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/index.html</link>
  <description/>
  <language>en</language>
  <item>
  <title>The Pig and the Sheep</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-pig-and-the-sheep.html</link>
  <description>My dear children, let me tell you a story from long, long ago. It carries a lesson that life has taught me, and I want you to remember it as you grow.  There was once a small village where a kind farmer lived. In his barnyard, he kept many animals&amp;mdash;among them were a pig and a sheep. Now, though they lived close together, the two were very different in nature.  The pig was restless and loud. I</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 14:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-pig-and-the-sheep.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Goose That Laid the Golden Eggs</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-goose-that-laid-the-golden-eggs.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village, there lived a poor farmer and his wife. They worked very hard every day but still found it difficult to earn enough to live comfortably. One morning, while feeding their animals, the farmer discovered something unusual in the nest of his goose.  To his surprise, the goose had laid a shiny golden egg! At first, he thought it must be a trick, but when he picked </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 09 Sep 2025 17:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-goose-that-laid-the-golden-eggs.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Three Little Pigs</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-three-little-pigs.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, there were three little pigs who lived with their mother. One day, their mother said, &amp;ldquo;My dear children, you are grown now. Go out into the world and build homes of your own. But remember&amp;mdash;whatever you do, do it well.&amp;rdquo;  So the three little pigs set off on their journey.  The first little pig was in a hurry. He wanted to play and have fun, so he built his house qu</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 19 Aug 2025 16:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-three-little-pigs.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Cinderella</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/cinderella.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a faraway land, there lived a sweet and gentle girl named Cinderella. She was kind to everyone, whether it was people, animals, or even the tiniest bird in the garden. Sadly, her life was not easy. After her mother passed away, her father remarried, and Cinderella gained a stepmother and two stepsisters.  The stepmother was proud and cruel, and her daughters were selfish and u</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 16 Aug 2025 13:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/cinderella.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Snow White</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/snow-white.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a peaceful kingdom in the hills of Himachal Pradesh, there lived a kind and gentle queen. One day, as she sat by her window, sewing by the snow, she pricked her finger. As she looked at the drop of blood on the white snow, she whispered, &amp;ldquo;I wish for a daughter with skin as fair as snow, lips as red as a rose, and hair as black as the night.&amp;rdquo;  Not long after, the qu</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jul 2025 18:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/snow-white.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Ugly Duckling</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-ugly-duckling.html</link>
  <description>In a quiet village pond in India, surrounded by lotus flowers and chirping birds, lived a mother duck named Kaveri. One fine morning, she sat on her nest, waiting for her eggs to hatch. One by one, the eggs cracked open, and out came six fluffy little ducklings. But the last egg, which was larger than the rest, took a little longer.  When it finally hatched, out came a duckling that looked quite d</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 22 May 2025 15:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-ugly-duckling.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Boy Who Cried Tiger</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-who-cried-tiger.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village near the forests of South India, there lived a mischievous boy named Arjun. Every day, his parents sent him to take their goats to graze near the edge of the forest. Arjun was a cheerful boy, but he often felt bored and lonely while watching the goats.  One afternoon, Arjun decided to have some fun. He ran toward the village shouting, &amp;ldquo;Tiger! Tiger! A tig</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 May 2025 12:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-who-cried-tiger.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Lion and the Mouse</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-lion-and-the-mouse.html</link>
  <description>In a vast jungle in India, there lived a mighty lion named Sheru. He was strong, feared by all, and considered the king of the forest. One afternoon, after a hearty meal, Sheru lay down beneath a shady tree and dozed off into a deep sleep.  While he was sleeping, a little mouse named Meenu, who lived nearby, came out of her hole to play. She ran up and down, squeaking with joy, and accidentally sc</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 07 Apr 2025 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-lion-and-the-mouse.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Wind and The Sun</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wind-and-the-sun.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time in a peaceful land in India, the Wind and the Sun were having a friendly argument. Each claimed to be stronger than the other.  The Wind blew hard and fast and said, &amp;ldquo;I am clearly the strongest. I can knock down trees, push boats across rivers, and fly kites into the sky!&amp;rdquo;  The Sun smiled gently and replied, &amp;ldquo;True strength doesn&amp;rsquo;t always come from force. So</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wind-and-the-sun.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Fisherman and His Wife</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fisherman-and-his-wife.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small coastal village in India, there lived a poor fisherman named Ravi and his wife, Kamala. They lived in a tiny hut near the sea and survived on whatever fish Ravi could catch each day. Though they had little, Ravi was content with his life. However, Kamala was always dissatisfied and wanted more.  One day, while fishing in the ocean, Ravi caught a beautiful golden fish. </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2025 08:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fisherman-and-his-wife.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Farmer and the Snake</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-farmer-and-the-snake.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village in India, there lived a kind-hearted farmer named Gopal. He was known for his generosity and willingness to help anyone in need. He worked hard on his farm, and though he was not very rich, he was always content with what he had.  One winter morning, as Gopal was walking through his fields, he saw something unusual lying on the ground. As he moved closer, he re</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 30 Mar 2025 18:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-farmer-and-the-snake.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Golden Goose</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-golden-goose.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village near a dense forest, there lived a poor farmer named Ramu. He worked tirelessly on his small piece of land but barely earned enough to feed his family. Despite his struggles, Ramu was kind-hearted and never wished harm upon anyone.  One day, while working in his field, he found a shimmering golden egg lying in the nest of his old goose. His eyes widened in disb</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-golden-goose.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Honest Woodcutter</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-honest-woodcutter.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village near a dense forest, there lived a poor but hardworking woodcutter named Harish. Every day, he would go into the forest, chop wood, and sell it in the market to earn a living. Though he had little, he was honest and content with what he earned.  One morning, Harish went to the forest as usual. He found a large, sturdy tree near a river and began chopping it dow</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2025 07:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-honest-woodcutter.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Dog and the Bone</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-dog-and-the-bone.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small town named Rampur, there lived a hungry stray dog named Bhola. He roamed the streets in search of food every day. One afternoon, after hours of searching, he finally found a delicious, meaty bone outside a butcher&amp;rsquo;s shop. Excited, he quickly grabbed it in his mouth and ran to a quiet place to enjoy his meal.  On his way, Bhola had to cross a small wooden bridge o</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-dog-and-the-bone.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Greedy Dog</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-greedy-dog.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village named Sonpur, there lived a stray dog called Moti. He was always on the lookout for food and never liked to share anything with others. His greed often got him into trouble, but he never learned his lesson.  One day, while wandering through the village, Moti found a juicy bone outside a butcher&amp;rsquo;s shop. His eyes sparkled with joy. What a delicious treat! h</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 04 Mar 2025 08:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-greedy-dog.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Bear and the Two Friends</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-bear-and-the-two-friends.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village nestled near a dense forest, there lived two friends named Sam and Leo. They were inseparable and did everything together. One day, they decided to venture into the forest to gather berries and explore. Before leaving, an old villager warned them, &amp;quot;The forest is beautiful but dangerous. Stay together, and be cautious.&amp;quot;  As they wandered deeper into th</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2025 07:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-bear-and-the-two-friends.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Magic Pot</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-magic-pot.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in the quaint village of Dharmapur, there lived a poor but kind-hearted farmer named Ramu. He worked hard every day on his small plot of land, but the rocky soil yielded very little, and he struggled to make ends meet. Despite his hardships, Ramu always helped anyone in need, earning him the love and respect of the villagers.  One day, while digging in his field, Ramu struck some</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 13:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-magic-pot.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Little Red Hen</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-little-red-hen.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a peaceful Indian village called Surajpur, there lived a hardworking little hen named Lal Pari. Lal Pari was kind and industrious, always busy tending to her small field and taking care of her chicks. She lived with a lazy goat named Gopu, a laid-back cat named Sundari, and a sleepy buffalo named Bhola.  One bright morning, as Lal Pari was scratching the ground near her field,</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 08:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-little-red-hen.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Crow and the Fox</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-crow-and-the-fox.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a dense forest near the Indian village of Champapur, there lived a clever fox named Gopal and a proud crow named Kalu. Kalu, the crow, was known for his arrogance and often flaunted his finds to the other animals.  One sunny morning, Kalu found a large, delicious piece of roti smeared with ghee near the village. Excited by his treasure, he quickly picked it up in his beak and </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 07:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-crow-and-the-fox.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Princess and the Pea</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-princess-and-the-pea.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in the vibrant kingdom of Rajapur, there lived a young prince named Veer. He was kind, noble, and wise, but he had one wish that had not been fulfilled&amp;mdash;he longed to marry a true princess. The queen, his mother, was equally determined to find the perfect bride for her son, someone who was truly noble in heart and nature.  Many princesses from far-off lands came to the palace</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2025 08:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-princess-and-the-pea.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Pied Piper of Hamelin</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-pied-piper-of-hamelin.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in the small Indian town of Nandipur, there was a terrible problem. The town was overrun by rats. They were everywhere&amp;mdash;running through the streets, eating the grain, and even sneaking into people&amp;#39;s homes. The townspeople tried everything they could think of to get rid of the rats, but nothing worked. They were desperate and didn&amp;#39;t know what to do.  One day, a myster</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 08:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-pied-piper-of-hamelin.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Little Match Girl</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-little-match-girl.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in the bustling streets of a small Indian town, a little girl named Meera lived with her cruel stepmother. Meera&amp;#39;s stepmother made her work hard every day, forcing her to sell matchsticks in the market. Though Meera worked tirelessly, her stepmother never showed her any love or care.  One chilly winter evening, as the town celebrated the festival of lights, Deepavali, the str</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 12:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-little-match-girl.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Emperor's New Clothes</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-emperor-s-new-clothes.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in the bustling kingdom of Vijayanagar, there lived a proud and vain emperor named Raja Veerendra. He was obsessed with his appearance and loved wearing the finest silk and brocade garments. His courtiers knew how much he loved compliments, so they constantly praised his clothing and flattered him.  One day, two cunning weavers named Raju and Balu arrived in the kingdom. They had</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 08:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-emperor-s-new-clothes.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Gingerbread Man</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-gingerbread-man.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village in India, there lived an old woman named Kamala and her husband, Ramesh. One day, Kamala decided to bake something special. &amp;quot;I will make a gingerbread man today,&amp;quot; she said. So she mixed flour, jaggery, and spices, shaped the dough into a little man, and carefully decorated him with raisins for eyes, cloves for buttons, and a big smile made of sugar sy</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 09:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-gingerbread-man.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Magic Fish</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-magic-fish.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village in India, there lived a poor fisherman named Ramesh. He lived with his wife, Leela, in a tiny hut by the river. Every day, Ramesh would go out to the river to catch fish, which they would either eat or sell in the market to make a living. Though their life was simple, Ramesh and Leela often wished for more wealth and comfort.  One day, as Ramesh was fishing, he</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 08:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-magic-fish.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Selfish Giant</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-selfish-giant.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village in India, there was a beautiful garden owned by a wealthy but selfish giant named Bhim Singh. The garden was full of colorful flowers, lush green grass, and tall fruit-bearing trees. Birds chirped joyfully, and children from the nearby village loved to come and play in the garden. Their laughter echoed all around, filling the garden with life.  But Bhim Singh, </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 08:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-selfish-giant.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Giant Turnip</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-giant-turnip.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village in India, there lived a kind-hearted farmer named Ramu. He lived with his family in a humble hut surrounded by lush green fields. Ramu loved to grow vegetables in his field, and he took great care of his crops.  One day, Ramu sowed a few turnip seeds in his garden. To his surprise, one of the turnips grew and grew until it became absolutely enormous! It was the</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-giant-turnip.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Tale of Mischievous Rabbit</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-tale-of-mischievous-rabbit.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a lush green forest in India, there were four little rabbits named Chintu, Mintu, Bittu, and Raja. They lived with their Amma (mother) in a cozy burrow beneath the roots of a big banyan tree.  One morning, their Amma said, &amp;quot;Children, you may go and play in the fields or by the river, but do not go into Lala Kisan&amp;#39;s (Farmer Lala&amp;#39;s) garden. Your father had an accide</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-tale-of-mischievous-rabbit.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Emperor and the Nightingale</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-emperor-and-the-nightingale.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a grand palace in China, there lived an emperor who was known for his love of beautiful things. His palace was adorned with the finest silks, golden statues and rare jewels. But what fascinated people the most was the emperor&amp;#39;s garden, which was filled with exotic flowers and magnificent trees. Beyond the garden lay a forest and deep within this forest was a nightingale wi</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 29 Oct 2024 12:23:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-emperor-and-the-nightingale.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Cat in Boots</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-cat-in-boots.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, there lived a poor miller who had three sons. When the miller passed away, he left his mill to the eldest son, his donkey to the second son and to the youngest son, all he left was a cat. The youngest son was disappointed. &amp;quot;What can I do with just a cat?&amp;quot; he wondered. &amp;quot;I&amp;rsquo;ll surely starve.&amp;quot;  But this was no ordinary cat. The cat, who wore a pair of clever</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 17:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-cat-in-boots.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Greedy Wolf</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-greedy-wolf.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a thick forest, there lived a greedy wolf. He was always hungry and would never be satisfied with what he had. No matter how much food he ate, he always wanted more.  One day, the wolf was wandering through the forest when he came across a sheep that had wandered away from its flock. The wolf&amp;#39;s mouth watered at the sight of the sheep and he thought to himself, &amp;quot;What a</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 19:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-greedy-wolf.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Wise Judge</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wise-judge.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village, there lived a wise and fair judge. People from all around the village came to him whenever they had disputes or disagreements, for he was known for his ability to see through lies and deliver justice.  One day, two women came to the judge, each claiming to be the mother of a young baby boy. The first woman said, &amp;quot;This baby is mine! She is lying and trying</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 07:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wise-judge.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Selfish Elephant</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-selfish-elephant.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a dense forest, there lived a mighty but selfish elephant. He was the largest animal in the jungle and used his size to bully and intimidate the smaller animals. The elephant cared only for himself and never helped anyone. Whenever he came across a smaller animal, he would chase them away, trample on their food, or push them aside.  One scorching summer, the forest experienced</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 20 Oct 2024 14:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-selfish-elephant.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Fox and the Stork</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-stork.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, a clever fox invited a stork to dinner. The fox, known for being sly, had something mischievous in mind and thought it would be fun to play a trick on the stork.  The day of the dinner arrived and the fox prepared a delicious soup. However, when it was time to serve, the fox poured the soup into shallow plates. The fox licked up his soup with ease, but the poor stork, with her lo</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-stork.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Town Mouse and the Country Mouse</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-town-mouse-and-the-country-mouse.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, a town mouse went to visit his cousin, a country mouse, who lived in a peaceful meadow. The country mouse, thrilled to have a visitor, welcomed his cousin with great warmth and enthusiasm. He wanted to share the simple joys of his life with the town mouse.  The country mouse prepared a humble meal of fresh seeds, nuts and grains, gathered from the fields nearby. As they sat down </description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-town-mouse-and-the-country-mouse.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Magic Fountain</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-magic-fountain.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small, sleepy village nestled between green hills and winding rivers, there was a legend that spoke of a magical fountain hidden deep within the Enchanted Forest. This fountain, it was said, could grant a single wish to anyone who found it, but only if they proved themselves worthy through their heart&amp;#39;s true desires.  In this village lived a young girl named Sandhya. She</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 15 Oct 2024 10:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-magic-fountain.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Princess and the Frog</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-princess-and-the-frog.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a grand and beautiful kingdom, there lived a kind and gentle princess named Nisha. She had everything a princess could wish for luxurious dresses, a beautiful palace and all the comforts of royal life. But despite all this, Princess Nisha was lonely and longed for a true friend.  One fine day, while walking through the lush palace gardens, Princess Nisha came upon a beautiful </description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2024 17:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-princess-and-the-frog.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Frog and the Scorpion</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-frog-and-the-scorpion.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a lush and verdant forest, there lived a wise old frog named Manas. Manas was known throughout the forest for his keen intellect and his ability to see the best in everyone, even those with a less-than-stellar reputation.  One day, as Manas was basking in the warm glow of the sun near the edge of a tranquil pond, he heard a small voice calling out to him.  &amp;quot;Excuse me, Mr.</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 05 Sep 2024 15:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-frog-and-the-scorpion.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Red Shoes</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-red-shoes.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a quaint village nestled at the foot of a towering mountain, there lived a young girl named Lakshmi. Lakshmi was a sweet and innocent child with a passion for dancing and she dreamed of one day becoming a great ballerina.  One day, while exploring the village marketplace, Lakshmi came across a beautiful pair of red shoes displayed in the window of a small shoemaker&amp;#39;s shop.</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 07:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-red-shoes.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Wise Parrot</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wise-parrot.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a lush forest teeming with life, there lived a wise and colorful parrot named Pavo. Pavo was unlike any other parrot in the forest; he possessed a keen intellect and a gift for wisdom that set him apart from his feathered companions.  Every day, creatures from all corners of the forest would flock to Pavo&amp;#39;s perch, seeking his advice and guidance on matters both great and s</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 07:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wise-parrot.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Boy and the Magic Lamp</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-and-the-magic-lamp.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village on the edge of a vast desert, there lived a young boy named Ali. Ali was an orphan who lived with his elderly grandmother in a humble mud-brick house.  Despite their poverty, Ali and his grandmother shared a close bond and worked hard to make ends meet. Ali would spend his days exploring the desert, searching for scraps of wood and metal to sell in the village </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 07:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-and-the-magic-lamp.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Talking Tree</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-talking-tree.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a mystical forest shrouded in mystery, there stood a magnificent tree known as the Whispering Willow. This ancient tree was said to possess the ability to speak, its branches swaying gently in the breeze as it shared its wisdom with all who sought its counsel.  Legends of the Whispering Willow had been passed down through generations and travelers from far and wide would journ</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Aug 2024 08:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-talking-tree.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Farmer's Lazy Sons</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-farmer-s-lazy-sons.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a peaceful village nestled among rolling hills, there lived a hardworking farmer named Janardhana. Janardhana had two sons, Deva and Madhava, who were known throughout the village for their laziness and lack of ambition.  Despite his best efforts to instill a strong work ethic in his sons, Janardhana watched with disappointment as Deva and Madhava whiled away their days loungi</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 08:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-farmer-s-lazy-sons.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Little Mermaid</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-little-mermaid.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in the depths of the ocean, there lived a beautiful young mermaid named Marina. Marina was the youngest daughter of King Triton, ruler of the sea and she was known throughout the underwater kingdom for her stunning voice and her adventurous spirit.  Despite the wonders of her underwater world, Marina often found herself gazing wistfully at the surface of the ocean, longing to exp</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 11:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-little-mermaid.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Clever Rabbit</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-clever-rabbit.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a lush green forest, there lived a clever rabbit named Rupa. Rupa was known far and wide for his quick wit and cunning, which he used to outsmart predators and protect himself and his fellow forest dwellers.  One day, as Rupa was hopping through the forest, he came across a group of hungry wolves prowling near the edge of the trees. The wolves spotted Rupa and immediately bega</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 08:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-clever-rabbit.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Talking Cave</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-talking-cave.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a lush and verdant forest, there stood a cave unlike any other. This cave was not only known for its impressive size and mysterious depths but also for its unique ability to speak. Legend has it that the cave possessed ancient wisdom and knowledge and those who dared to enter its depths were said to emerge with newfound insight and understanding.  Many adventurers and seekers </description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:27:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-talking-cave.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Sun and the Moon</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-sun-and-the-moon.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in the vast expanse of the sky, there existed two celestial beings: the Sun and the Moon. The Sun was radiant and powerful, filling the world with warmth and light during the day, while the Moon was gentle and serene, casting a soft glow upon the earth at night.  Despite their differences, the Sun and the Moon were the best of friends and they spent their days and nights together</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 08 Aug 2024 13:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-sun-and-the-moon.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Brave Little Tailor</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-brave-little-tailor.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a quaint village nestled at the edge of a dense forest, there lived a humble tailor named Janardana. Janardana was known throughout the village for his skill with a needle and thread, but he longed for adventure beyond the confines of his small shop.  One day, as Janardana sat sewing by the window, he overheard the villagers talking excitedly about a fearsome giant that had be</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 07 Aug 2024 08:56:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-brave-little-tailor.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Magic Carpet</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-magic-carpet.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a bustling city filled with merchants, storytellers and artisans, there lived a young boy named Anand. Anand&amp;#39;s family was poor and they struggled to make ends meet, living in a small, cramped apartment in the heart of the city.  Despite their hardships, Anand dreamed of adventure and excitement beyond the narrow streets and crowded marketplaces of the city. He longed to ex</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 07:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-magic-carpet.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Drummer Boy</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-drummer-boy.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village nestled among rolling hills, there lived a young boy named Tanmay. Tanmay had a passion for music that burned bright within him and he spent his days wandering the village, drumming on pots and pans and tapping out rhythms on any surface he could find.  Despite his love for music, Tanmay was often overlooked by the villagers, who were too busy with their daily </description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 07:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-drummer-boy.html</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>