<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
<title>Quick Read - Peoples BLOG</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/index.html</link>
  <description/>
  <language>en</language>
  <item>
  <title>The Monkey and the Crocodile</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-monkey-and-the-crocodile.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a lush jungle beside a glistening river, there lived a clever monkey named Max and a friendly crocodile named Cody. Max and Cody had developed an unlikely friendship, spending their days chatting and sharing stories on a large rock by the riverbank.  One day, as they sat together, Cody revealed a secret to Max. He explained that his wife, Clara, had fallen gravely ill, and the</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-monkey-and-the-crocodile.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Be wise while counting</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/be-wise-while-counting.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a bustling marketplace, there was a fruit vendor named Jack. Jack was known for his honesty and fair dealings. He took great pride in carefully counting and weighing each fruit to ensure accurate pricing for his customers.  One day, a young boy named Timmy approached Jack&amp;#39;s fruit stand. He wanted to buy some apples for his family. Jack greeted Timmy with a warm smile and b</description>
  <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/be-wise-while-counting.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>A Wise Old Owl</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-wise-old-owl.html</link>
  <description>In the heart of a dense forest, perched high on a sturdy branch, lived a wise old owl named Oliver. With his sparkling eyes and a coat of feathers that glowed in the moonlight, Oliver was respected by all the animals of the forest for his wisdom and counsel.  One day, a young squirrel named Sammy came to Oliver seeking advice. Sammy was impulsive and often made hasty decisions without considering </description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-wise-old-owl.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Milkmaid and Her Pail</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-milkmaid-and-her-pail.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a quaint village, there lived a young milkmaid named Emma. She was known for her dreams of a better life and her penchant for daydreaming. Emma&amp;#39;s family relied on the milk she sold each day to make a living.  One sunny morning, Emma set out for the market, carrying a pail filled to the brim with fresh milk. As she walked, she started to daydream about the possibilities tha</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-milkmaid-and-her-pail.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Proud Rose</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-proud-rose.html</link>
  <description>In a beautifully tended garden, there bloomed a magnificent rose. Its petals were vibrant and fragrant, capturing the admiration of all who beheld it. The rose, aware of its exquisite beauty, held its head high with pride.  Every day, as the garden&amp;#39;s other flowers swayed gently in the breeze, the proud rose would boast about its beauty and elegance. It would belittle the other flowers, conside</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-proud-rose.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Fox and the Grapes</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-grapes.html</link>
  <description>In a lush vineyard, basking under the warm sun, there hung a cluster of juicy, ripe grapes. Their vibrant colors and tantalizing aroma caught the attention of a clever and cunning fox named Felix.  Felix, known for his quick wit and sly nature, desired the sweet taste of those grapes. He jumped and leaped, reaching with all his might, but the grapes remained just out of his grasp. Undeterred, he t</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-fox-and-the-grapes.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Tortoise and the Hare</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-tortoise-and-the-hare.html</link>
  <description>In a peaceful forest, there lived a confident and speedy hare and a slow but determined tortoise. The hare was known for his incredible speed and often boasted about his swiftness, making fun of the tortoise for his slow nature.  One day, tired of the hare&amp;#39;s constant bragging, the tortoise challenged him to a race. The hare laughed heartily at the tortoise&amp;#39;s proposition, unable to fathom h</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-tortoise-and-the-hare.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Boy Who Cried Wolf</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-who-cried-wolf.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a small village nestled among rolling hills, there lived a mischievous young shepherd boy named Peter. Peter&amp;#39;s job was to watch over the village&amp;#39;s flock of sheep and protect them from any harm. However, Peter had a tendency to get bored easily and seek attention in unusual ways.  One sunny day, while tending to his sheep, Peter decided to play a trick on the villagers.</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boy-who-cried-wolf.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Golden Touch of Midas</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-golden-touch-of-midas.html</link>
  <description>Once upon a time, in a land far away, there lived a wealthy king named Midas. Although he had riches beyond imagination, he was not content with his wealth. He constantly craved for more and desired to possess everything he laid his eyes upon.  One day, as he was walking through his magnificent garden, Midas stumbled upon a mysterious creature. It was none other than the god Dionysus, who was plea</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-golden-touch-of-midas.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The boasting traveler</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boasting-traveler.html</link>
  <description>A man came back from a tour and boasted about his adventurous journeys. He talked at length about the different people he met and his amazing feats that got him fame and praise from people everywhere. He went on to say that he went to the Rhodes where he had leaped to such distances that no man could ever match his feat.  He even went on to say that there were witnesses who would vouch for his wor</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 10 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-boasting-traveler.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The camel and the baby</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-camel-and-the-baby.html</link>
  <description>One day, a camel and her baby were chatting. The baby asked, &amp;ldquo;Mother, why do we have humps?&amp;rdquo; The mother replied, &amp;ldquo;Our humps are for storing water so that we can survive in the desert&amp;rdquo;.  &amp;ldquo;Oh&amp;rdquo;, said the child, &amp;ldquo;and why do we have rounded feet mother?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;Because they are meant to help us walk comfortably in the desert. These legs help us move aroun</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-camel-and-the-baby.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The farmer and the well</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-farmer-and-the-well.html</link>
  <description>A farmer looking for a source of water for his farm bought a well from his neighbor. The neighbor was cunning, though, and refused to let the farmer take water from the well. On asking why, he replied, &amp;ldquo;I sold the well to you, not the water&amp;rdquo;, and walked away. The distraught farmer didn&amp;rsquo;t know what to do. So he went to Birbal, a clever man and one of the nine courtiers of Emperor </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-farmer-and-the-well.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>True friends love you anyway</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/true-friends-love-you-anyway.html</link>
  <description>Lord Krishna and Sudama were childhood friends. While Krishna thrived and prospered, Sudama didn&amp;rsquo;t. He lead the life of a poor Brahmin man, living in a small hut with his wife and kids. Most days, the kids wouldn&amp;rsquo;t even get enough to eat from what Sudama got as alms. One day, his wife suggested that he go and ask his friend Krishna for help.  Sudama was reluctant to seek favors, but he</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/true-friends-love-you-anyway.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Elephant and friends</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/elephant-and-friends.html</link>
  <description>A lone elephant wandered the forest looking for friends. She came across a monkey and asked, &amp;ldquo;Will you be my friend, monkey?&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;You are too big and cannot swing on trees as I do. So I cannot be your friend&amp;rdquo;, said the monkey.  The elephant them came across a rabbit and asked him if she could be his friend. &amp;ldquo;You are too big to fit inside my burrow. You cannot be my frien</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 20 May 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/elephant-and-friends.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The wolf and the shepherds</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wolf-and-the-shepherds.html</link>
  <description>This is one of the many Aesop&amp;rsquo;s fables that one can relate to in any day and age.  One day a wolf was chased away from a farm for trying to steal some of the sheep for food. Later that week, the wolf came back to the farm hoping to find some food. He peeped inside the house and found the farmer and his family feasting on lamb roast.  &amp;ldquo;Aha!&amp;rdquo;, he thought. &amp;ldquo;If I were to do the</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wolf-and-the-shepherds.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The young crab and his mother.</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-young-crab-and-his-mother.html</link>
  <description>One day, a young crab and his mother were on the beach, spending some time together. The young crab gets up to move, but it can only walk sideways. His mother scolds him for walking sideways and asks him to walk forward by pointing his toes out front. The young crab responds, &amp;ldquo;I would like to walk forward mom, but I do not know how to&amp;rdquo;.  Hearing this, his mom gets up to show him how, b</description>
  <pubDate>Wed, 08 Mar 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-young-crab-and-his-mother.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The other side of the wall</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-other-side-of-the-wall.html</link>
  <description>A young woman inherited a beautiful garden from her grandmother. She loved gardening too and was very proud of her garden. One day, she saw a very beautiful plant in a catalog and wanted that for her garden. She ordered it and planted it at the base of the stonewall in her backyard. She took great care of the plant, which grew quickly and had beautiful green leaves on it.  Months passed, but not a</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-other-side-of-the-wall.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The dog at the well</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-dog-at-the-well.html</link>
  <description>A dog and her pups lived on a farm, where there was a well. The mother dog told the pups, do not go near the well or play around it. One of the pups wondered why they shouldn&amp;rsquo;t go to the well and decided to explore it. He went to the well. Climbed up the wall and peeked inside.  In there, he saw his reflection and thought it was another dog. The pup saw that the other dog in the well (his re</description>
  <pubDate>Sat, 18 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-dog-at-the-well.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Controlling anger</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/controlling-anger.html</link>
  <description>There was once a young boy who had problem controlling his temper. When he became angry, he would just say anything that came to his mind and hurt people. So his father gave him a bag of nails and a hammer and said, &amp;ldquo;Every time you get angry, hammer one nail into the fence in our backyard&amp;rdquo;.  The first few days the boy hammered so many nails that he emptied half the bag. Over the weeks,</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 10 Feb 2023 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/controlling-anger.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>The Wet Pants</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wet-pants.html</link>
  <description>A nine-year-old boy was sitting at his desk in class, when suddenly, his pants felt wet, and there was a puddle at his feet. His heart almost skipped a beat, as he got worried that his classmates would see that and make fun of him.  He quickly wanted to do something, and saw the teacher and his classmate Susie walking towards him. Susie was carrying a bowl of goldfish. As they came closer, the boy</description>
  <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/the-wet-pants.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Bad Habits</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/bad-habits.html</link>
  <description>A wealthy businessman was worried about his son&amp;rsquo;s bad habits. He sought counsel from a wise, old man. The old man met the man&amp;rsquo;s son and took him out for a stroll. They walked into the woods, and the old man showed the boy a small sapling and asked him to pull it out. The boy did so with ease, and they walked on.  The old man then asked the boy to pull out a small plant. The boy did tha</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/bad-habits.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>How to Think Positive and Best out of a Situation? with King's Painting</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/how-to-think-positive-and-best-out-of-a-situation-with-kings-painting.html</link>
  <description>We people might have heard a saying to think positive, many times. In this quick read we are gonna see how a painter thinks positively with a situation to draw a King&amp;rsquo;s painting.  Once upon a time, there was a Kingdom. The king there only had one leg and one eye, but he was very intelligent and kind. Everyone in his kingdom lived a happy and healthy life because of their king. One day the ki</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/how-to-think-positive-and-best-out-of-a-situation-with-kings-painting.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Keep good company if you want to be a good person</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/keep-good-company-if-you-want-to-be-a-good-person.html</link>
  <description>Two parrots built a nest in a banyan tree. They lived with their two young ones, which they took good care of. The mother and the father parrot went out to gather food in the morning and came back home by evening. One day, when their parents were away, the young parrots were taken by a cruel hunter.  One of the birds managed to escape and flew away from the hunter. He ended up at a hermitage and g</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/keep-good-company-if-you-want-to-be-a-good-person.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Dara Singh Randhawa (Dara Singh)</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/dara-singh-randhawa.html</link>
  <description>Dara Singh was an Indian Professional Wrestler, Actor, Director and Politician.  He was born on 19th November 1928 in a Jat Sikh family, to Surat Singh Randhawa and Balwant Kaur.  He is known for his undefeated worldwide streak in wrestling. His flooring of King Kong is still remembered. According to Thesz, Dara Sing was an authentic wrestler, he was superbly conditioned and had no problem losing </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/dara-singh-randhawa.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>ISRO launched three Singapore Satellites with PSLV</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-launched-three-singapore-satellites-with-pslv.html</link>
  <description>On Thursday 30th Jun 2022 at 18:02 hours IST, India successfully placed into orbit three Singaporean satellites exactly as planned, which will make it the second successful rocket and satellite launch mission in 2022.  It was the PSLV-C53 rocket which took up the Satellites into space from the Satish Dhawan Space Centre, Sriharikota. And with this successful mission, the PSLV rocket has launched 3</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-launched-three-singapore-satellites-with-pslv.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Legislative Assistants for Members of Parliament (LAMP) Fellowship</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/legislative-assistants-for-members-of-parliament-lamp-fellowship.html</link>
  <description>LAMP Fellowship is an opportunity for young people in India, provided by the Indian Government, to be mentored by a Member of Parliament, during this course of the Fellowship, people will get the opportunity to engage with experts from diverse sectors and understand important policy and development issues of the country.   Primary role is to provide research support to the Member of Parliament (wh</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Hanukkah John</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/legislative-assistants-for-members-of-parliament-lamp-fellowship.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>A Comet which is twice the Everest's size is heading toward Earth</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-comet-which-is-twice-the-everest-size-is-heading-toward-earth.html</link>
  <description>A massive comet named C/2017 K2 (PanSTARRS) is heading toward the Earth. It is twice the size of Mount Everest and will make its closest approach on July 14.  It was first spotted in 2017. It mostly consists of ice and will not pose any danger to general people, but an astronomer will be more excited.  Let&amp;#39;s see what we know about it and how can we watch it?   This C/2017 K2 has been active fo</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-comet-which-is-twice-the-everest-size-is-heading-toward-earth.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Fourth QUAD meet on 11th February 2022</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/fourth-quad-meet-on-th-february-.html</link>
  <description>A Joint statement by QUAD member countries Australia, India, Japan, and United States was released post the fourth meeting that happened on 11th Feb 2022 in Melbourne, Australia. This Fourth QUAD meeting was with Marise Payne, Minister for Foreign Affairs Australia, Subrahmanyam Jaishankar, External Affairs Minister of India, Hayashi Yoshimasa, Minister of Foreign Affairs of Japan &amp; Antony Blinken</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/fourth-quad-meet-on-th-february-.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Vikram Misri Is New Deputy National Security Advisor</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/vikram-misri-is-new-deputy-national-security-advisor.html</link>
  <description>Vikram Misri is a career diplomat from the 1989 batch of the Indian Foreign Service. He was born in Srinagar, Vikram Misri attended the Scindia School before graduating from Delhi's Hindu College. He also holds an MBA degree. And before joining the civil services, he had worked in advertising and ad film-making for three years. Earlier Vikram Misri has served at the Ministry of External Affairs of</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/vikram-misri-is-new-deputy-national-security-advisor.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Olympics and Paralympics are two different Olympic Games</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/olympics-and-paralympics-are-two-different-olympic-games.html</link>
  <description>There is a key difference between the Olympics and the Paralympics, where in the Olympics the participants will be able-bodied people and whereas in Paralympics the participants will have some form of physical or intellectual disabilities.
                            Paralympics was originally started as a way to help soldiers who had been wounded in World War II.
                            Paral</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/olympics-and-paralympics-are-two-different-olympic-games.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Indian Astrophysicists spotted rare merger of three massive black holes</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/indian-astrophysicists-spotted-rare-merger-of-three-massive-black-holes.html</link>
  <description>According to the Press Information Bureau, Astrophysicists in India have spotted a rare merging of three supermassive black holes. They were observing the merging of two galaxies named NGC7733 and NGC7734 in our celestial neighbour.
                            When they detected unusual emissions from the centre of the latter and also a curious movement of a large bright clump having a different v</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/indian-astrophysicists-spotted-rare-merger-of-three-massive-black-holes.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>India, Russia to assess Taliban actions, before taking any action on Taliban</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/india-russia-to-assess-taliban-actions-before-taking-any-action-on-taliban.html</link>
  <description>Russian President Vladimir Putin and Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi agreed on the rise of Islamic radicalization in the region and are concerned over spread of terrorism by Taliban affiliated groups in Pakistan.
                            The two countries have also decided to set up combined teams of foreign ministry and national security officials of each country to conduct a detailed asse</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/india-russia-to-assess-taliban-actions-before-taking-any-action-on-taliban.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Virtual QUAD meet on 12th August, 2021</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/virtual-quad-meet-on-twelfth-august-twenty-twenty-one.html</link>
  <description>On August 12th, 2021 Senior Officials from four democracies - Australia, India, Japan, and the U.S. - met virtually to discuss Quad initiatives on economic recovery, maritime security, and human rights that promote a free and open IndoPacific region.
                            The four democracies acknowledged that global security and prosperity depends on the region remaining inclusive, resilien</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/virtual-quad-meet-on-twelfth-august-twenty-twenty-one.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>GSLV-F10 to launch Earth Observation Satellite</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/gslv-f-ten-to-launch-earth-observation-satellite.html</link>
  <description>GSLV-F10 is slated to launch Earth Observation Satellite, EOS-03 on August 12th, 2021 from Satish Dhawan Space Centre SHAR, Sriharikota.
                            Countdown for the launch of GSLV-F10/EOS-03 mission commenced on August 11th at 03:43 Hrs (IST) from Satish Dhawan Space Centre (SDSC) SHAR, Sriharikota
                            GSLV-F10 launch took place today (12th Aug) at 05:43 H</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/gslv-f-ten-to-launch-earth-observation-satellite.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>July 26th - Kargil Vijay Diwas</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-sixth-kargil-vijay-diwas.html</link>
  <description>In 1999, India successfully took command of high outposts on this date. The Kargil war was fought for more than 60 days &amp; ended on this date.
                            Pakistani army took advantage of the melting snow &amp; took command of high outposts of India, by betraying the bilateral agreement of both the nations that posts would remain unattended during winter season.
                        </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-sixth-kargil-vijay-diwas.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>July 23rd - National Broadcasting Day</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-third-national-broadcasting-day.html</link>
  <description>During the British Raj, Broadcasting began in June 1923 with the programs by the Bombay Presidency Radio Club and other radio clubs.
                            
                                The private Indian Broadcasting Company Ltd (IBC) was authorized to operate two radio stations in an agreement on 23 July 1927.
                                IBC started with two stations, one in Bombay (</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-third-national-broadcasting-day.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>ISRO successfully conducted the Third Test on Vikas Engine for Gaganyaan</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-successfully-conducted-the-third-test-on-vikas-engine-for-gaganyaan.html</link>
  <description>On July 14, 2021, ISRO has successfully conducted the third long-duration hot test of the liquid propellant Vikas Engine for the core L110 liquid stage of the human-rated GSLV MkIII vehicle, as part of the engine qualification requirements for the Gaganyaan Programme.
                            The engine was fired for a duration of 240 seconds at the engine test facility of ISRO Propulsion Compl</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-successfully-conducted-the-third-test-on-vikas-engine-for-gaganyaan.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Heat on Earth’s Atmosphere is Heating much as it did fifteen years ago</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/heat-on-earths-atmosphere-is-heating-much-as-it-did-fifteen-years-ago.html</link>
  <description>Earth's energy imbalance doubled between 2005 - 2019, this was identified by a team from NASA &amp; NOAA. Energy Im-balance is the difference between the amount of energy absorbed by Earth and the amount of energy emitted by Earth.
                            Means, if there is any energy imbalance on earth, Earth will be gaining energy which will lead to heat up more.
                            So t</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/heat-on-earths-atmosphere-is-heating-much-as-it-did-fifteen-years-ago.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Device with Two Atoms thick, World’s thinnest device</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/device-with-two-atoms-thick-worlds-thinnest-device.html</link>
  <description>World’s thinnest piece of technology has been developed by the Scientists, which is a device with only two Atoms thick, very tiny. It can be used to store electronic information.
                            This device consists of 2 layers one with Boron &amp; other with Nitrogen, which are arranged in a repeating hexagonal structure.
                            Electrons from Boron &amp; Nitrogen atoms</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/device-with-two-atoms-thick-worlds-thinnest-device.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Powerful Solar Storm approaching Earth</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/powerful-solar-storm-approaching-earth.html</link>
  <description>According to website spaceweather.com, a powerful solar storm is approaching the Earth at a speed of 1.6 million kilometers and this storm will hit the Earth someday on 11th July - 13th July 2021. As per the website spaceweather.com, the storm that originated from the Sun's atmosphere can have a significant impact on a region of space dominated by Earth's magnetic field.
                          </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/powerful-solar-storm-approaching-earth.html</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>