<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
<title>Quick Read - Peoples BLOG</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/index.html</link>
  <description/>
  <language>en</language>
  <item>
  <title>Bad Habits</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/bad-habits.html</link>
  <description>A wealthy businessman was worried about his son&amp;rsquo;s bad habits. He sought counsel from a wise, old man. The old man met the man&amp;rsquo;s son and took him out for a stroll. They walked into the woods, and the old man showed the boy a small sapling and asked him to pull it out. The boy did so with ease, and they walked on.  The old man then asked the boy to pull out a small plant. The boy did tha</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/bad-habits.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>How to Think Positive and Best out of a Situation? with King's Painting</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/how-to-think-positive-and-best-out-of-a-situation-with-kings-painting.html</link>
  <description>We people might have heard a saying to think positive, many times. In this quick read we are gonna see how a painter thinks positively with a situation to draw a King&amp;rsquo;s painting.  Once upon a time, there was a Kingdom. The king there only had one leg and one eye, but he was very intelligent and kind. Everyone in his kingdom lived a happy and healthy life because of their king. One day the ki</description>
  <pubDate>Fri, 13 Jan 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/how-to-think-positive-and-best-out-of-a-situation-with-kings-painting.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Keep good company if you want to be a good person</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/keep-good-company-if-you-want-to-be-a-good-person.html</link>
  <description>Two parrots built a nest in a banyan tree. They lived with their two young ones, which they took good care of. The mother and the father parrot went out to gather food in the morning and came back home by evening. One day, when their parents were away, the young parrots were taken by a cruel hunter.  One of the birds managed to escape and flew away from the hunter. He ended up at a hermitage and g</description>
  <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/keep-good-company-if-you-want-to-be-a-good-person.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Dara Singh Randhawa (Dara Singh)</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/dara-singh-randhawa.html</link>
  <description>Dara Singh was an Indian Professional Wrestler, Actor, Director and Politician.  He was born on 19th November 1928 in a Jat Sikh family, to Surat Singh Randhawa and Balwant Kaur.  He is known for his undefeated worldwide streak in wrestling. His flooring of King Kong is still remembered. According to Thesz, Dara Sing was an authentic wrestler, he was superbly conditioned and had no problem losing </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/dara-singh-randhawa.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>ISRO launched three Singapore Satellites with PSLV</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-launched-three-singapore-satellites-with-pslv.html</link>
  <description>On Thursday 30th Jun 2022 at 18:02 hours IST, India successfully placed into orbit three Singaporean satellites exactly as planned, which will make it the second successful rocket and satellite launch mission in 2022.  It was the PSLV-C53 rocket which took up the Satellites into space from the Satish Dhawan Space Centre, Sriharikota. And with this successful mission, the PSLV rocket has launched 3</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-launched-three-singapore-satellites-with-pslv.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Legislative Assistants for Members of Parliament (LAMP) Fellowship</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/legislative-assistants-for-members-of-parliament-lamp-fellowship.html</link>
  <description>LAMP Fellowship is an opportunity for young people in India, provided by the Indian Government, to be mentored by a Member of Parliament, during this course of the Fellowship, people will get the opportunity to engage with experts from diverse sectors and understand important policy and development issues of the country.   Primary role is to provide research support to the Member of Parliament (wh</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Hanukkah John</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/legislative-assistants-for-members-of-parliament-lamp-fellowship.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>A Comet which is twice the Everest's size is heading toward Earth</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-comet-which-is-twice-the-everest-size-is-heading-toward-earth.html</link>
  <description>A massive comet named C/2017 K2 (PanSTARRS) is heading toward the Earth. It is twice the size of Mount Everest and will make its closest approach on July 14.  It was first spotted in 2017. It mostly consists of ice and will not pose any danger to general people, but an astronomer will be more excited.  Let&amp;#39;s see what we know about it and how can we watch it?   This C/2017 K2 has been active fo</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/a-comet-which-is-twice-the-everest-size-is-heading-toward-earth.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Fourth QUAD meet on 11th February 2022</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/fourth-quad-meet-on-th-february-.html</link>
  <description>A Joint statement by QUAD member countries Australia, India, Japan, and United States was released post the fourth meeting that happened on 11th Feb 2022 in Melbourne, Australia. This Fourth QUAD meeting was with Marise Payne, Minister for Foreign Affairs Australia, Subrahmanyam Jaishankar, External Affairs Minister of India, Hayashi Yoshimasa, Minister of Foreign Affairs of Japan &amp; Antony Blinken</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/fourth-quad-meet-on-th-february-.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Vikram Misri Is New Deputy National Security Advisor</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/vikram-misri-is-new-deputy-national-security-advisor.html</link>
  <description>Vikram Misri is a career diplomat from the 1989 batch of the Indian Foreign Service. He was born in Srinagar, Vikram Misri attended the Scindia School before graduating from Delhi's Hindu College. He also holds an MBA degree. And before joining the civil services, he had worked in advertising and ad film-making for three years. Earlier Vikram Misri has served at the Ministry of External Affairs of</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/vikram-misri-is-new-deputy-national-security-advisor.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Olympics and Paralympics are two different Olympic Games</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/olympics-and-paralympics-are-two-different-olympic-games.html</link>
  <description>There is a key difference between the Olympics and the Paralympics, where in the Olympics the participants will be able-bodied people and whereas in Paralympics the participants will have some form of physical or intellectual disabilities.
                            Paralympics was originally started as a way to help soldiers who had been wounded in World War II.
                            Paral</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/olympics-and-paralympics-are-two-different-olympic-games.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Indian Astrophysicists spotted rare merger of three massive black holes</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/indian-astrophysicists-spotted-rare-merger-of-three-massive-black-holes.html</link>
  <description>According to the Press Information Bureau, Astrophysicists in India have spotted a rare merging of three supermassive black holes. They were observing the merging of two galaxies named NGC7733 and NGC7734 in our celestial neighbour.
                            When they detected unusual emissions from the centre of the latter and also a curious movement of a large bright clump having a different v</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/indian-astrophysicists-spotted-rare-merger-of-three-massive-black-holes.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>India, Russia to assess Taliban actions, before taking any action on Taliban</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/india-russia-to-assess-taliban-actions-before-taking-any-action-on-taliban.html</link>
  <description>Russian President Vladimir Putin and Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi agreed on the rise of Islamic radicalization in the region and are concerned over spread of terrorism by Taliban affiliated groups in Pakistan.
                            The two countries have also decided to set up combined teams of foreign ministry and national security officials of each country to conduct a detailed asse</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/india-russia-to-assess-taliban-actions-before-taking-any-action-on-taliban.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Virtual QUAD meet on 12th August, 2021</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/virtual-quad-meet-on-twelfth-august-twenty-twenty-one.html</link>
  <description>On August 12th, 2021 Senior Officials from four democracies - Australia, India, Japan, and the U.S. - met virtually to discuss Quad initiatives on economic recovery, maritime security, and human rights that promote a free and open IndoPacific region.
                            The four democracies acknowledged that global security and prosperity depends on the region remaining inclusive, resilien</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/virtual-quad-meet-on-twelfth-august-twenty-twenty-one.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>GSLV-F10 to launch Earth Observation Satellite</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/gslv-f-ten-to-launch-earth-observation-satellite.html</link>
  <description>GSLV-F10 is slated to launch Earth Observation Satellite, EOS-03 on August 12th, 2021 from Satish Dhawan Space Centre SHAR, Sriharikota.
                            Countdown for the launch of GSLV-F10/EOS-03 mission commenced on August 11th at 03:43 Hrs (IST) from Satish Dhawan Space Centre (SDSC) SHAR, Sriharikota
                            GSLV-F10 launch took place today (12th Aug) at 05:43 H</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/gslv-f-ten-to-launch-earth-observation-satellite.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>July 26th - Kargil Vijay Diwas</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-sixth-kargil-vijay-diwas.html</link>
  <description>In 1999, India successfully took command of high outposts on this date. The Kargil war was fought for more than 60 days &amp; ended on this date.
                            Pakistani army took advantage of the melting snow &amp; took command of high outposts of India, by betraying the bilateral agreement of both the nations that posts would remain unattended during winter season.
                        </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-sixth-kargil-vijay-diwas.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>July 23rd - National Broadcasting Day</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-third-national-broadcasting-day.html</link>
  <description>During the British Raj, Broadcasting began in June 1923 with the programs by the Bombay Presidency Radio Club and other radio clubs.
                            
                                The private Indian Broadcasting Company Ltd (IBC) was authorized to operate two radio stations in an agreement on 23 July 1927.
                                IBC started with two stations, one in Bombay (</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/july-twenty-third-national-broadcasting-day.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>ISRO successfully conducted the Third Test on Vikas Engine for Gaganyaan</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-successfully-conducted-the-third-test-on-vikas-engine-for-gaganyaan.html</link>
  <description>On July 14, 2021, ISRO has successfully conducted the third long-duration hot test of the liquid propellant Vikas Engine for the core L110 liquid stage of the human-rated GSLV MkIII vehicle, as part of the engine qualification requirements for the Gaganyaan Programme.
                            The engine was fired for a duration of 240 seconds at the engine test facility of ISRO Propulsion Compl</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/isro-successfully-conducted-the-third-test-on-vikas-engine-for-gaganyaan.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Heat on Earth’s Atmosphere is Heating much as it did fifteen years ago</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/heat-on-earths-atmosphere-is-heating-much-as-it-did-fifteen-years-ago.html</link>
  <description>Earth's energy imbalance doubled between 2005 - 2019, this was identified by a team from NASA &amp; NOAA. Energy Im-balance is the difference between the amount of energy absorbed by Earth and the amount of energy emitted by Earth.
                            Means, if there is any energy imbalance on earth, Earth will be gaining energy which will lead to heat up more.
                            So t</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/heat-on-earths-atmosphere-is-heating-much-as-it-did-fifteen-years-ago.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Device with Two Atoms thick, World’s thinnest device</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/device-with-two-atoms-thick-worlds-thinnest-device.html</link>
  <description>World’s thinnest piece of technology has been developed by the Scientists, which is a device with only two Atoms thick, very tiny. It can be used to store electronic information.
                            This device consists of 2 layers one with Boron &amp; other with Nitrogen, which are arranged in a repeating hexagonal structure.
                            Electrons from Boron &amp; Nitrogen atoms</description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/device-with-two-atoms-thick-worlds-thinnest-device.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Questions to ask Dentist before Dental Implant</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/questions-to-ask-dentist-before-dental-implant.html</link>
  <description>Here are a few questions to remember and ask your dentist before you proceed with your dental implant.
                                
                                    Will there be any Discomfort?
                                    Can my body reject Dental Implant?
                                    Are there any chances of infection after Dental Implant?
                                  </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Jyothi</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/questions-to-ask-dentist-before-dental-implant.html</guid>
</item><item>
  <title>Powerful Solar Storm approaching Earth</title>
  <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/powerful-solar-storm-approaching-earth.html</link>
  <description>According to website spaceweather.com, a powerful solar storm is approaching the Earth at a speed of 1.6 million kilometers and this storm will hit the Earth someday on 11th July - 13th July 2021. As per the website spaceweather.com, the storm that originated from the Sun's atmosphere can have a significant impact on a region of space dominated by Earth's magnetic field.
                          </description>
  <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
  <dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/quick-read/powerful-solar-storm-approaching-earth.html</guid>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>