<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Recipe - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/recipe.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to prepare Green Mango Salad</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-green-mango-salad.html</link>
			<description>Green Mango Salad, also known as Som Tum in Thai cuisine, is a refreshing and tangy dish that combines the tartness of green mangoes with the crunch of vegetables and the kick of spices. It&amp;#39;s perfect as a light meal or a side dish.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how to prepare a delicious Green Mango Salad at home:  Ingredients:   2 medium green mangoes, peeled and julienned 1 medium carrot, peeled and julienn</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Aug 2024 08:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-green-mango-salad.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Dal Palak</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-dal-palak.html</link>
			<description>Dal Palak is a nutritious and delicious dish made with lentils and spinach. It&amp;#39;s a popular Indian recipe that combines the health benefits of dal (lentils) and palak (spinach) into a flavorful and wholesome meal.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how you can prepare Dal Palak at home:  Ingredients:  For the Dal:   1 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) or moong dal (split yellow lentils) 4 cups water 1/2 teaspoon tur</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 12:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-dal-palak.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pani Puri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pani-puri.html</link>
			<description>Pani Puri is a fun and delicious twist on the classic Indian street food, Pani Puri (or Golgappa). This snack involves small, crispy puris filled with a tangy, spicy, and flavorful water (pani) along with a savory filling.  Here&amp;#39;s how to prepare Pani Puri:  Ingredients:  For the Puris:   1 packet of ready-made puris (available at Indian grocery stores) or you can make them at home if you prefe</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2024 10:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pani-puri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Kala Khatta Gola</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kala-khatta-gola.html</link>
			<description>Kala Khatta Gola, also known as Kala Khatta Ice Gola or Black Currant Ice Gola, is a popular Indian street treat, especially during the summer. This refreshing dessert is made with crushed ice, flavored syrup, and a blend of tangy and spicy seasonings.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can prepare Kala Khatta Gola at home:  Ingredients:  For the Kala Khatta Syrup:   1 cup black currants (or use black currant sy</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2024 08:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kala-khatta-gola.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Dhokla</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-dhokla.html</link>
			<description>Dhokla is a popular Gujarati snack that is steamed and made from fermented rice and chickpea flour (besan). It&amp;#39;s light, spongy, and usually served with green chutney.  Here&amp;#39;s a detailed recipe to prepare traditional Dhokla at home:  Ingredients:  For the Dhokla Batter:   1 cup rice 1/2 cup chana dal (split chickpeas) 1/2 cup urad dal (split black gram) 1/2 cup yogurt 1 tablespoon ginger-gr</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-dhokla.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Sattu Paratha</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sattu-paratha.html</link>
			<description>Sattu Paratha is a delicious and nutritious stuffed flatbread popular in the Indian states of Bihar, Jharkhand, and Uttar Pradesh. It is made with sattu (roasted gram flour) and various spices, creating a savory filling wrapped in a whole wheat dough.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how to prepare it:  Ingredients:  For the Dough:   2 cups whole wheat flour (atta) 1 tablespoon oil or ghee A pinch of salt Water (as </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 12:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sattu-paratha.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Tamarind Rice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-tamarind-rice.html</link>
			<description>The tamarind rice dish you&amp;#39;re referring to sounds like Tamarind Rice, also known as Puliyodarai or Pulihora, which is a popular South Indian dish.  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe to prepare it:  Ingredients:  For the Rice:   1 cup rice (preferably sona masoori or any medium-grain rice) 2 cups water A pinch of salt   For the Tamarind Paste:   1 lemon-sized ball of tamarind (or 2-3 tablespoons of tamarind </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-tamarind-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Mango Coconut Rice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-coconut-rice.html</link>
			<description>Mango Coconut Rice is a delicious and fragrant dish made with ripe mangoes, coconut milk, and aromatic spices.  Here&amp;#39;s how to prepare it:  Ingredients:   1 cup basmati rice, washed and soaked for 30 minutes 1 ripe mango, peeled, pitted, and diced 1 cup coconut milk 1/2 cup water 1 tablespoon oil or ghee 1 teaspoon mustard seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1-2 green chilies, slit lengthwise (adjust </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 09:18:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-coconut-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Methi Thepla</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-methi-thepla.html</link>
			<description>Methi Thepla is a popular Gujarati flatbread made with fresh fenugreek leaves, whole wheat flour, and spices. It&amp;#39;s a delicious and nutritious dish that can be enjoyed as a snack or as part of a meal.  Here&amp;#39;s how to prepare Methi Thepla:  Ingredients:   1 cup whole wheat flour (atta) 1 cup fresh fenugreek leaves (methi), washed and finely chopped 2 tablespoons yogurt (curd) 1 tablespoon gra</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-methi-thepla.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Kokum Rasam</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kokum-rasam.html</link>
			<description>Kokum Rasam is a tangy and flavorful South Indian soup made with kokum extract, tomatoes, spices, and other aromatic ingredients.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe to prepare Kokum Rasam:  Ingredients:   1 tablespoon kokum extract (kokum juice) 2 medium-sized tomatoes, chopped 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon black peppercorns 1/2 teaspoon mustard seeds 1/2 teaspoon fenugreek seeds 1-2 dry red chilies </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 07 May 2024 09:27:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kokum-rasam.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Coconut Ladoo?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-coconut-ladoo.html</link>
			<description>Coconut ladoo is a delicious Indian sweet made from grated coconut, condensed milk, and cardamom.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe to prepare coconut ladoo:  Ingredients:   2 cups grated coconut (fresh or desiccated) 1 cup sweetened condensed milk 1/2 teaspoon ground cardamom (optional) 2 tablespoons chopped nuts (such as almonds, cashews, or pistachios) for garnish (optional)    Google Ad 1   Instruct</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-coconut-ladoo.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Different spices are used to make a garam masala mix?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-spices-are-used-to-make-a-garam-masala-mix.html</link>
			<description>Garam masala is a quintessential spice blend used in Indian cuisine. It adds warmth, depth, and complexity to dishes, and its composition can vary widely based on regional preferences and personal taste.  Here&amp;#39;s a breakdown of the different spices commonly used to make garam masala, along with why, how, and when it&amp;#39;s used:  What is Garam Masala?   Garam masala is a blend of ground spices c</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 14:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-spices-are-used-to-make-a-garam-masala-mix.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Samosas - Snack from the Indian subcontinent</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/samosas-snack-from-the-indian-subcontinent.html</link>
			<description>Samosas are a popular savory snack originating from the Indian subcontinent. They are triangular-shaped pastries filled with a savory mixture of spiced potatoes, peas, and sometimes other ingredients.  Here&amp;#39;s how samosas are typically cooked, along with some background information:  What Are Samosas?   	Ingredients: The outer pastry shell of samosas is typically made from all-purpose flour, wa</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/samosas-snack-from-the-indian-subcontinent.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cabbage fried rice recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cabbage-fried-rice-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for preparing Cabbage Fried Rice at home:  Ingredients:   2 cups cooked basmati rice (preferably leftover and cooled) 1 cup finely shredded cabbage 1/2 cup carrots, finely chopped 1/2 cup green peas 1/2 cup onions, finely chopped 2-3 green chilies, finely chopped 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 2 tablespoons soy sauce 1 tablespoon chili sauce (adjust to taste) 1/2 teasp</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cabbage-fried-rice-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Carrot Fried Rice Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/carrot-fried-rice-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for Carrot Fried Rice in Andhra style:  Ingredients:   2 cups cooked basmati rice (preferably leftover and cooled) 1 cup carrots, finely chopped 1/2 cup green peas 1/2 cup onions, finely chopped 2-3 green chilies, finely chopped 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 2 tablespoons oil 1/2 teaspoon mustard seeds     (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    1/2 teas</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/carrot-fried-rice-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg Biryani Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Egg Biryani in Andhra style:  Ingredients:  For the rice:   2 cups basmati rice 4 cups water 1 bay leaf 2 green cardamom pods 2 cloves Salt to taste   For the egg marinade:   6 boiled eggs, peeled and pricked with a fork 1/2 cup yogurt 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder 1/2 teaspoon garam masala powder Salt to taste    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vegetable Biryani Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vegetable-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Vegetable Biryani in Andhra style:  Ingredients:  For the rice:   2 cups basmati rice 4 cups water 1 bay leaf 2 green cardamom pods 2 cloves Salt to taste   For the vegetable mixture:   2 tablespoons oil or ghee 1 large onion, thinly sliced 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 1 cup mixed vegetables (such as carrots, peas, beans, cauliflower), c</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vegetable-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Jonna roti with chili chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jonna-roti-with-chili-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Jonna Roti (Sorghum Roti) with Chilli Chutney in Andhra style:  For Jonna Roti:  Ingredients:   2 cups jowar flour (sorghum flour) Water as needed Salt to taste Oil or ghee for cooking   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the jowar flour and salt. Gradually add water and knead the flour to form a soft and pliable dough. Add water as needed to achieve the right consis</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 09:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jonna-roti-with-chili-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ragi roti with tomato chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ragi-roti-with-tomato-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Ragi Roti with Tomato Chutney in Andhra style:  For Ragi Roti:  Ingredients:   1 cup ragi flour (finger millet flour) 1/4 cup finely chopped onions 1/4 cup grated carrots 2 green chilies, finely chopped 2 tablespoons chopped coriander leaves Salt to taste Water as needed Oil for cooking      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    Instructions:   In a mixing b</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 29 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ragi-roti-with-tomato-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Gongura Pappu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gongura-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Gongura Pappu, a popular Andhra-style lentil curry made with Gongura leaves (sorrel leaves):  Ingredients:   1 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 cups Gongura leaves, washed and chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 08:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gongura-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vankaya Pappu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vankaya-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Vankaya Pappu, an Andhra-style lentil and eggplant curry:  Ingredients:   1 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 small eggplants (brinjals), chopped into cubes 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon coriander powder </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vankaya-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pasta at home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pasta-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for making pasta at home:  Ingredients:   8 ounces (225 grams) dried pasta (such as spaghetti, penne, or fettuccine) Water for boiling Salt for seasoning Olive oil (optional)   Instructions:   Fill a large pot with water and bring it to a boil over high heat. Add a generous amount of salt to the boiling water. Once the water is boiling, add the pasta to the pot. Stir gen</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pasta-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pizza at home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pizza-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for homemade pizza:  For the Pizza Dough:  Ingredients:   2 &amp;frac12; cups all-purpose flour 2 &amp;frac14; teaspoons instant yeast 1 teaspoon sugar 1 teaspoon salt 1 cup warm water 2 tablespoons olive oil   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the flour, instant yeast, sugar, and salt. Gradually add the warm water while stirring the mixture. Knead the dough for about 5-7 minut</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pizza-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare paneer kulcha at home - Paneer Kulcha Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-paneer-kulcha-at-home-paneer-kulcha-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Paneer Kulcha, a popular Indian bread stuffed with paneer (Indian cottage cheese):  For the Kulcha Dough:  Ingredients:   2 cups all-purpose flour (maida) 1/2 teaspoon baking powder 1/2 teaspoon baking soda 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/2 cup plain yogurt 2 tablespoons oil Water as needed   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine all-purpose flour, baking powder, baking soda, and s</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-paneer-kulcha-at-home-paneer-kulcha-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare gobi manchurian at home - Gobi Manchurian Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-gobi-manchurian-at-home-gobi-manchurian-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Gobi Manchurian, a popular Indo-Chinese dish made with cauliflower:  Ingredients:  For the batter:   1 medium-sized cauliflower, cut into florets 1/2 cup all-purpose flour (maida) 1/4 cup cornstarch 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder 1/2 teaspoon soy sauce 1/2 teaspoon vinegar Salt to taste Water as needed Oil for deep frying   For the sauce:   1 t</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 10:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-gobi-manchurian-at-home-gobi-manchurian-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cook Onion Rava Dosa at home - Onion Rava Dosa Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-onion-rava-dosa-at-home-onion-rava-dosa-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Onion Rava Dosa, a popular South Indian crepe made with semolina (rava) and onions:  Ingredients:   1 cup semolina (rava) 1/2 cup rice flour 1/4 cup all-purpose flour (maida) 1 onion, finely chopped 2 green chilies, finely chopped 1/4 cup chopped coriander leaves 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon black pepper, coarsely crushed 1/2 teaspoon grated ginger Salt to taste Water </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-onion-rava-dosa-at-home-onion-rava-dosa-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cook Lemon Rice at home - Lemon Rice Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-lemon-rice-at-home-lemon-rice-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Lemon Rice, a tangy and flavorful rice dish:  Ingredients:   1 cup basmati rice (or any long-grain rice) 2 tablespoons oil 1 teaspoon mustard seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/4 cup peanuts 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 curry leaves 1/4 teaspoon turmeric powder Juice of 1 lemon Salt to taste Fresh coriander leaves for garnishing           </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-lemon-rice-at-home-lemon-rice-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Veg Kurma at Home - Veg Kurma Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-veg-kurma-at-home-veg-kurma-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Veg Kurma, a creamy and flavorful Indian dish made with mixed vegetables:  Ingredients:   2 cups mixed vegetables (carrots, beans, potatoes, peas, cauliflower, etc.), chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 cup grated coconut 1/4 cup cashew nuts 1 teaspoon fennel seeds 1 teaspoon cumin </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-veg-kurma-at-home-veg-kurma-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Bisi bele bhath at Home - Bisi bele bhath Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-bisi-bele-bhath-at-home-bisi-bele-bhath-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Bisi Bele Bhath, a flavorful and traditional dish from Karnataka, India:  Ingredients:  For the spice paste:   2 tablespoons chana dal (Bengal gram) 1 tablespoon urad dal (split black gram) 1 tablespoon coriander seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon fenugreek seeds 6-8 dried red chilies 1/2 teaspoon peppercorns 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder                      (adsbygoog</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-bisi-bele-bhath-at-home-bisi-bele-bhath-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cook Pongal at Home - Pongal Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Pongal, a popular South Indian dish made with rice and lentils:  Ingredients:   1 cup raw rice 1/4 cup split yellow moong dal (split yellow lentils) 4 cups water 2 tablespoons ghee (clarified butter) 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon whole black peppercorns 1 tablespoon grated ginger A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 cashew nuts 10-12 curry leaves Salt to taste            </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Cauliflower Peas Masala at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Cauliflower Peas Masala:  Ingredients:   1 small cauliflower, cut into florets 1 cup green peas 2 onions, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon coriander powder 1/2 teaspoon garam masala Salt to tast</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Sambar at Home - Sambar recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sambar-at-home-sambar-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Andhra-style vegetable sambar, a delicious South Indian dish made with lentils and mixed vegetables, Here&amp;#39;s the recipe:  Ingredients:   1/2 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 cups mixed vegetables (such as drumsticks, carrots, beans, brinjal, pumpkin, etc.), chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, chopped 2 tablespoons tamarind pulp 2 tablespoons sambar powder 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sambar-at-home-sambar-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Palak Paneer at Home - Palak Paneer Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Palak paneer is a popular North Indian dish made with spinach and paneer (Indian cheese).  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing palak paneer at home for serving four people:  Ingredients:   2 cups chopped spinach (palak) 200g paneer, cut into small cubes 1 medium-sized onion, chopped 2 medium-sized tomatoes, chopped 1 tbsp ginger-garlic paste 1 green chili, chopped                                    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Mango Pickle at Home - Mango Pickle Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Mango pickle is a popular Indian condiment made with raw mangoes and spices.  Mango pickle is a variety of pickles prepared using mango. It is very popular in South and Southeast Asia. The pickling process in India differs from other regions mainly due to an additional spice mixture added to them after anaerobic fermentation.  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing mango pickle at home:  Ingredients:  </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Apr 2024 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian style Spanish omelette, Egg + Potato + Onion</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</link>
			<description>Egg with Potato plus Onion will make a delicious and healthy breakfast, You have have it as a Breakfast or you can have it as a Snack in the day, will also be a great starter in the barbecue. This combination of dish is called Spanish omelette, but lets make it in Indian Style.  Ingredients Needed?  3 Eggs, 4 medium sized Potato (chopped in small) &amp;amp; 4 medium sized Onion (chopped in small), 4-5</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg Stuffed Paratha Home made Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Egg Stuffed Paratha is a delicious and healthy Paratha dish, filled with egg mixture. Both the eggs and whole wheat are healthy as it provides the right amount of proteins and carbs. The egg mixture has finely chopped onions, green chili and coriander leaves. This is then slided into the half cooked paratha pockets and cooked further. The Egg Stuffed Parathas are quite filling in itself.  Ingredie</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pudina chutney Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Pudina Chutney is a flavorful condiment and aromatic chutney to serve with rice, mudde, idli, dosa. Pudina Chutney can also be served with snacks like bonda, bajji too.  People sometimes are confused pudina chutney with mint chutney or green chutney that is served along with chats and tandoori platter, but it&amp;#39;s not the same which we serve with rice or mudde or idle, and this chutney is more au</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
			<description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Chintakaya Pachadi Recipe, Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi chintakaya pachadi (Green raw tamarind pickle) is an age-old dish, which is generally eaten with Rice &amp; some also eaten with Ghee for even better taste. As we Indians love the tangy &amp; sweetish taste of pickle, this delicious Pachi chintakaya pachadi is enjoyed by all age groups and in fact, the recipe is one among the famous Indian dishes. This dish also has many health benefits</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Pulusu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi Pulusu Recipe is a thin rasam made with freshly extracted tamarind water and mixed with sliced onions and freshly cut coriander leaves. Comfort food at its best when served with some steamed rice for a simple meal.                                It is a different way of creating a rasam that has been followed by the people from Andhra Pradesh and Telangana. This rasam is not hea</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Raw Mango Chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Raw mango chutney is a flavorful condiment made with raw mangos, coriander leaves, onions and some spices. Raw Mango Chutney is a must-try recipe when raw mangoes are in season. Raw mangoes are packed with minerals and vitamins and are good to beat the summer heat.                                This raw mango chutney aids digestion and enhances the taste, aroma, and nutrition of any dish. We usua</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>