<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Recipe - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/recipe.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Egg Stuffed Paratha Home made Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Egg Stuffed Paratha is a delicious and healthy Paratha dish, filled with egg mixture. Both the eggs and whole wheat are healthy as it provides the right amount of proteins and carbs. The egg mixture has finely chopped onions, green chili and coriander leaves. This is then slided into the half cooked paratha pockets and cooked further. The Egg Stuffed Parathas are quite filling in itself.  Ingredie</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pudina chutney Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Pudina Chutney is a flavorful condiment and aromatic chutney to serve with rice, mudde, idli, dosa. Pudina Chutney can also be served with snacks like bonda, bajji too.  People sometimes are confused pudina chutney with mint chutney or green chutney that is served along with chats and tandoori platter, but it&amp;#39;s not the same which we serve with rice or mudde or idle, and this chutney is more au</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
			<description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Chintakaya Pachadi Recipe, Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi chintakaya pachadi (Green raw tamarind pickle) is an age-old dish, which is generally eaten with Rice &amp; some also eaten with Ghee for even better taste. As we Indians love the tangy &amp; sweetish taste of pickle, this delicious Pachi chintakaya pachadi is enjoyed by all age groups and in fact, the recipe is one among the famous Indian dishes. This dish also has many health benefits</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Pulusu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi Pulusu Recipe is a thin rasam made with freshly extracted tamarind water and mixed with sliced onions and freshly cut coriander leaves. Comfort food at its best when served with some steamed rice for a simple meal.
                                It is a different way of creating a rasam that has been followed by the people from Andhra Pradesh and Telangana. This rasam is not he</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Raw Mango Chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Raw mango chutney is a flavorful condiment made with raw mangos, coriander leaves, onions and some spices. Raw Mango Chutney is a must-try recipe when raw mangoes are in season. Raw mangoes are packed with minerals and vitamins and are good to beat the summer heat.
                                This raw mango chutney aids digestion and enhances the taste, aroma, and nutrition of any dish. We usu</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>