<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Recipe - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/recipe.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to prepare Mango Lassi: A Creamy Yogurt Drink with the Goodness of Ripe Mangoes</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-lassi-a-creamy-yogurt-drink-with-the-goodness-of-ripe-mangoes.html</link>
			<description>Mango Lassi is one of India&amp;rsquo;s most loved summer drinks&amp;mdash;rich, creamy, and bursting with the tropical sweetness of ripe mangoes. Blended with smooth yogurt and lightly sweetened with sugar or honey, this drink is both refreshing and indulgent. Served chilled, it makes for a perfect companion to a spicy Indian meal or as a cooling treat on a hot day.  As an experienced cook, I can assure </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Sep 2025 15:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-lassi-a-creamy-yogurt-drink-with-the-goodness-of-ripe-mangoes.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Dahi Vada: Soft Lentil Dumplings in Creamy Yogurt with Tangy Chutneys</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dahi-vada-soft-lentil-dumplings-in-creamy-yogurt-with-tangy-chutneys.html</link>
			<description>Dahi Vada is one of those timeless Indian chaats that brings together a perfect balance of flavors&amp;mdash;soft and spongy lentil dumplings (vadas) soaked in silky yogurt, topped with tangy tamarind chutney, fresh coriander chutney, and a sprinkle of chaat masala. Every bite is a burst of sweetness, spice, and tang, making it a beloved dish at festive occasions, family gatherings, and street food st</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Aug 2025 11:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dahi-vada-soft-lentil-dumplings-in-creamy-yogurt-with-tangy-chutneys.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Kulfi: Traditional Indian Ice Cream with Saffron, Cardamom &amp; Nuts</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kulfi-traditional-indian-ice-cream-with-saffron-cardamom-nuts.html</link>
			<description>Kulfi is the quintessential Indian frozen dessert&amp;mdash;rich, dense, and full of flavor. Unlike Western ice creams, kulfi is not whipped, which gives it a firm, creamy texture that slowly melts in your mouth. Flavored with aromatic saffron, fragrant cardamom, and crunchy nuts like pistachios and almonds, this age-old dessert is a favorite at Indian celebrations, street-side stalls, and summer feas</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 31 Jul 2025 19:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kulfi-traditional-indian-ice-cream-with-saffron-cardamom-nuts.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Kesar Pista Milkshake</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kesar-pista-milkshake.html</link>
			<description>Kesar Pista Milkshake is a rich and creamy Indian beverage made with saffron (kesar), pistachios (pista), and chilled milk. This royal drink is not only a treat for the taste buds but also packed with nutritional benefits. It&amp;rsquo;s perfect for summers, festive occasions, or just when you&amp;#39;re in the mood for something indulgent and refreshing.  Ingredients   2 cups chilled full cream milk 2 ta</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 04 Apr 2025 08:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kesar-pista-milkshake.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Moong Dal Salad</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-moong-dal-salad.html</link>
			<description>Moong Dal Salad is a light, protein-packed, and flavorful dish that makes for a perfect snack or side option. It is easy to prepare and requires minimal ingredients, making it an excellent choice for anyone seeking a healthy and delicious meal.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how you can make this refreshing salad at home.  Ingredients  To prepare this wholesome salad, you will need:   1 cup split yellow moong dal </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 15:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-moong-dal-salad.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Kokum Sherbet</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kokum-sherbet.html</link>
			<description>Kokum Sherbet is a tangy and refreshing drink made from kokum (Garcinia indica), a fruit commonly used in Indian cuisine, especially in coastal regions. It&amp;#39;s not only delicious but also has cooling properties, making it a perfect drink for hot weather.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple recipe to prepare Kokum Sherbet:  Ingredients:   1/2 cup dried kokum (about 8-10 pieces) 4 cups water 1/2 to 3/4 cup sug</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 17:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kokum-sherbet.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Curd Rice?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-curd-rice.html</link>
			<description>Curd Rice is a popular South Indian dish known for its simplicity and soothing flavors. It&amp;#39;s often served as a comfort food and is particularly cooling during hot weather.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe to prepare Curd Rice:  Ingredients:   1 cup cooked rice (preferably short-grain rice like Sona Masuri or any leftover rice) 1 cup plain yogurt (curd), whisked until smooth 1 tablespoon oil or ghee</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 09:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-curd-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Sattu Drink?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sattu-drink.html</link>
			<description>Sattu Drink is a traditional and nutritious beverage from the Indian subcontinent, particularly popular in the states of Bihar and Uttar Pradesh. It&amp;#39;s made with roasted gram flour (sattu), water and spices and it&amp;#39;s known for its cooling and energizing properties, especially during hot summers.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe to prepare Sattu Drink:  Ingredients:   3 tablespoons sattu (roasted </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 07:18:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sattu-drink.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Kairi Ki Sabzi?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kairi-ki-sabzi.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe to prepare Kairi Ki Sabzi, a delicious curry made with raw mangoes:  Ingredients:   2 medium-sized raw mangoes (kairi), peeled and chopped into cubes 2 tablespoons oil 1 teaspoon mustard seeds 1/2 teaspoon fenugreek seeds (methi seeds) 1/2 teaspoon asafoetida (hing) 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) Salt to taste 1 tablespoon jagg</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Nov 2024 18:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kairi-ki-sabzi.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare a Cucumber Mint Cooler?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-a-cucumber-mint-cooler.html</link>
			<description>Cucumber Mint Cooler is a refreshing drink perfect for hot summer days.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple recipe to prepare it at home:  Ingredients:   1 large cucumber, peeled and chopped 10-12 fresh mint leaves Juice of 1 lemon 2-3 tablespoons sugar syrup (adjust to taste) 2 cups chilled water or sparkling water Ice cubes Mint sprigs and cucumber slices, for garnish (optional)   Instructions:   Prepare the</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 11:03:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-a-cucumber-mint-cooler.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Stuffed Bell Peppers?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-stuffed-bell-peppers.html</link>
			<description>Stuffed bell peppers filled with spicy potato filling are a delicious and satisfying dish.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step recipe to prepare stuffed bell peppers:  Ingredients:   4 large bell peppers (any color you prefer) 3-4 medium-sized potatoes, boiled and mashed 1 onion, finely chopped 2 green chilies, finely chopped (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/2 t</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 18 Oct 2024 15:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-stuffed-bell-peppers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Paneer Tikka?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-paneer-tikka.html</link>
			<description>Paneer Tikka is a well-loved Indian starter made with paneer (a type of Indian cheese) that is marinated in spices and yogurt, then grilled or baked for a smoky, tasty treat.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can make it at home in easy-to-understand language:  Ingredients:   250 grams paneer, cut into cubes &amp;frac12; cup thick yogurt (hung curd) 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 1 tablespoon lemon juice 1 teaspo</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-paneer-tikka.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Mango Pickle?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle.html</link>
			<description>Making mango pickle, or aam ka achar, is a fun way to keep the tangy taste of raw mangoes using tasty spices.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple recipe to make mango pickle at home:  Ingredients:   3-4 raw mangoes (about 500 grams), firm and sour 1/2 cup mustard oil (or any cooking oil) 2 tablespoons mustard seeds 1 tablespoon fenugreek seeds 1 tablespoon fennel seeds 1/2 teaspoon asafoetida 2 teaspoons turme</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Moong Dal Khichdi</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-moong-dal-khichdi.html</link>
			<description>Moong Dal Khichdi is a healthy and comforting dish made with rice, split yellow moong dal (lentils) and mild spices. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to digest and is especially enjoyed during cold weather or when you&amp;#39;re not feeling well.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple recipe for making Moong Dal Khichdi:  Ingredients:   1 cup rice (basmati rice works well) 1/2 cup split yellow moong dal (lentils) 3 cups water 1 table</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 16 Sep 2024 09:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-moong-dal-khichdi.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Tomato Soup</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-tomato-soup.html</link>
			<description>Tomato soup is a classic comfort food that is easy to prepare and perfect for any time of the year.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple recipe to make delicious homemade tomato soup:  Ingredients:   1 kg tomatoes, ripe and juicy, roughly chopped 1 onion, chopped 2-3 cloves garlic, minced 1 tablespoon olive oil or butter 1 tablespoon tomato paste (optional, for extra richness) 1 teaspoon sugar (optional, to bal</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-tomato-soup.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Palak Patta Chaat</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-patta-chaat.html</link>
			<description>Palak Patta Chaat is a delightful Indian snack made with crispy spinach leaves topped with tangy and spicy chutneys, yogurt and sev. It&amp;#39;s a wonderful combination of textures and flavors, making it a popular street food.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how you can prepare Palak Patta Chaat at home:  Ingredients:  For the Spinach Fritters (Palak Patta):   15-20 fresh spinach leaves (medium-sized) 1 cup besan (gra</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-patta-chaat.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Chana Chaat</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-chana-chaat.html</link>
			<description>Chana Chaat is a delicious, tangy and healthy Indian street food made with chickpeas, fresh vegetables and flavorful spices. It&amp;#39;s quick to prepare and perfect as a snack or light meal.  Here&amp;#39;s a detailed recipe to prepare Chana Chaat at home:  Ingredients:   1 cup dried chickpeas (or 1 can of chickpeas, drained and rinsed) 1 medium onion, finely chopped 1 medium tomato, finely chopped 1 me</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-chana-chaat.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare JalJeera</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-jaljeera.html</link>
			<description>JalJeera is a traditional Indian summer drink known for its refreshing and tangy taste. Made with a blend of spices, herbs and tangy lemon, it is both a thirst quencher and an appetizer.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can prepare JalJeera at home:  Ingredients:  For the JalJeera Powder:   2 tablespoons cumin seeds 1 teaspoon black peppercorns 1 teaspoon fennel seeds 1 teaspoon black salt (kala namak) 1 teasp</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 12 Aug 2024 08:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-jaljeera.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pudina Rice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pudina-rice.html</link>
			<description>Pudina Rice, also known as Mint Rice, is a flavorful and aromatic dish made with fresh mint leaves, rice and spices. It&amp;#39;s a refreshing and light meal that can be served as a main dish or a side.  Here&amp;#39;s a detailed recipe to prepare Pudina Rice at home:  Ingredients:  For the Rice:   1 cup basmati rice 2 cups water 1 tablespoon oil or ghee Salt to taste   For the Pudina (Mint) Paste:   1 cu</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pudina-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Green Mango Salad</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-green-mango-salad.html</link>
			<description>Green Mango Salad, also known as Som Tum in Thai cuisine, is a refreshing and tangy dish that combines the tartness of green mangoes with the crunch of vegetables and the kick of spices. It&amp;#39;s perfect as a light meal or a side dish.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how to prepare a delicious Green Mango Salad at home:  Ingredients:   2 medium green mangoes, peeled and julienned 1 medium carrot, peeled and julienn</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-green-mango-salad.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Dal Palak</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-dal-palak.html</link>
			<description>Dal Palak is a nutritious and delicious dish made with lentils and spinach. It&amp;#39;s a popular Indian recipe that combines the health benefits of dal (lentils) and palak (spinach) into a flavorful and wholesome meal.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how you can prepare Dal Palak at home:  Ingredients:  For the Dal:   1 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) or moong dal (split yellow lentils) 4 cups water 1/2 teaspoon tur</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 12:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-dal-palak.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pani Puri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pani-puri.html</link>
			<description>Pani Puri is a fun and delicious twist on the classic Indian street food, Pani Puri (or Golgappa). This snack involves small, crispy puris filled with a tangy, spicy and flavorful water (pani) along with a savory filling.  Here&amp;#39;s how to prepare Pani Puri:  Ingredients:  For the Puris: 1 packet of ready-made puris (available at Indian grocery stores) or you can make them at home if you prefer. </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pani-puri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Kala Khatta Gola</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kala-khatta-gola.html</link>
			<description>Kala Khatta Gola, also known as Kala Khatta Ice Gola or Black Currant Ice Gola, is a popular Indian street treat, especially during the summer. This refreshing dessert is made with crushed ice, flavored syrup and a blend of tangy and spicy seasonings. Here&amp;#39;s how you can prepare Kala Khatta Gola at home:  Ingredients:  For the Kala Khatta Syrup:   1 cup black currants (or use black currant syru</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kala-khatta-gola.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Dhokla</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-dhokla.html</link>
			<description>Dhokla is a popular Gujarati snack that is steamed and made from fermented rice and chickpea flour (besan). It&amp;#39;s light, spongy and usually served with green chutney.  Here&amp;#39;s a detailed recipe to prepare traditional Dhokla at home:  Ingredients:  For the Dhokla Batter:   1 cup rice 1/2 cup chana dal (split chickpeas) 1/2 cup urad dal (split black gram) 1/2 cup yogurt 1 tablespoon ginger-gre</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-dhokla.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Sattu Paratha</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sattu-paratha.html</link>
			<description>Sattu Paratha is a delicious and nutritious stuffed flatbread popular in the Indian states of Bihar, Jharkhand and Uttar Pradesh. It is made with sattu (roasted gram flour) and various spices, creating a savory filling wrapped in a whole wheat dough.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how to prepare it:  Ingredients:  For the Dough:   2 cups whole wheat flour (atta) 1 tablespoon oil or ghee A pinch of salt Water (as n</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 12:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sattu-paratha.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Tamarind Rice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-tamarind-rice.html</link>
			<description>The tamarind rice dish you&amp;#39;re referring to sounds like Tamarind Rice, also known as Puliyodarai or Pulihora, which is a popular South Indian dish.  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe to prepare it:  Ingredients:  For the Rice:   1 cup rice (preferably sona masoori or any medium-grain rice) 2 cups water A pinch of salt   For the Tamarind Paste:   1 lemon-sized ball of tamarind (or 2-3 tablespoons of tamarind </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 27 May 2024 09:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-tamarind-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Mango Coconut Rice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-coconut-rice.html</link>
			<description>Mango Coconut Rice is a delicious and fragrant dish made with ripe mangoes, coconut milk and aromatic spices.  Here&amp;#39;s how to prepare it:  Ingredients:   1 cup basmati rice, washed and soaked for 30 minutes 1 ripe mango, peeled, pitted and diced 1 cup coconut milk 1/2 cup water 1 tablespoon oil or ghee 1 teaspoon mustard seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1-2 green chilies, slit lengthwise (adjust to</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 May 2024 09:18:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-coconut-rice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Methi Thepla</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-methi-thepla.html</link>
			<description>Methi Thepla is a popular Gujarati flatbread made with fresh fenugreek leaves, whole wheat flour and spices. It&amp;#39;s a delicious and nutritious dish that can be enjoyed as a snack or as part of a meal.  Here&amp;#39;s how to prepare Methi Thepla:  Ingredients:   1 cup whole wheat flour (atta) 1 cup fresh fenugreek leaves (methi), washed and finely chopped 2 tablespoons yogurt (curd) 1 tablespoon gram</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2024 09:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-methi-thepla.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Kokum Rasam</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kokum-rasam.html</link>
			<description>Kokum Rasam is a tangy and flavorful South Indian soup made with kokum extract, tomatoes, spices and other aromatic ingredients.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe to prepare Kokum Rasam:  Ingredients:   1 tablespoon kokum extract (kokum juice) 2 medium-sized tomatoes, chopped 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon black peppercorns 1/2 teaspoon mustard seeds 1/2 teaspoon fenugreek seeds 1-2 dry red chilies 2</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 19:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-kokum-rasam.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Coconut Ladoo?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-coconut-ladoo.html</link>
			<description>Coconut ladoo is a delicious Indian sweet made from grated coconut, condensed milk and cardamom.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe to prepare coconut ladoo:  Ingredients:   2 cups grated coconut (fresh or desiccated) 1 cup sweetened condensed milk 1/2 teaspoon ground cardamom (optional) 2 tablespoons chopped nuts (such as almonds, cashews, or pistachios) for garnish (optional)    Google Ad 1   Instructi</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 02 May 2024 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-coconut-ladoo.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Different spices are used to make a garam masala mix?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-spices-are-used-to-make-a-garam-masala-mix.html</link>
			<description>Garam masala is a quintessential spice blend used in Indian cuisine. It adds warmth, depth and complexity to dishes and its composition can vary widely based on regional preferences and personal taste.  Here&amp;#39;s a breakdown of the different spices commonly used to make garam masala, along with why, how and when it&amp;#39;s used:  What is Garam Masala?   Garam masala is a blend of ground spices comm</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 Apr 2024 14:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-spices-are-used-to-make-a-garam-masala-mix.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Samosas - Snack from the Indian subcontinent</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/samosas-snack-from-the-indian-subcontinent.html</link>
			<description>Samosas are a popular savory snack originating from the Indian subcontinent. They are triangular-shaped pastries filled with a savory mixture of spiced potatoes, peas and sometimes other ingredients.  Here&amp;#39;s how samosas are typically cooked, along with some background information:  What Are Samosas?   	Ingredients: The outer pastry shell of samosas is typically made from all-purpose flour, wat</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Apr 2024 11:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/samosas-snack-from-the-indian-subcontinent.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cabbage fried rice recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cabbage-fried-rice-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for preparing Cabbage Fried Rice at home:  Ingredients:   2 cups cooked basmati rice (preferably leftover and cooled) 1 cup finely shredded cabbage 1/2 cup carrots, finely chopped 1/2 cup green peas 1/2 cup onions, finely chopped 2-3 green chilies, finely chopped 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 2 tablespoons soy sauce 1 tablespoon chili sauce (adjust to taste) 1/2 teasp</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Nov 2023 13:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cabbage-fried-rice-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Carrot Fried Rice Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/carrot-fried-rice-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for Carrot Fried Rice in Andhra style:  Ingredients:   2 cups cooked basmati rice (preferably leftover and cooled) 1 cup carrots, finely chopped 1/2 cup green peas 1/2 cup onions, finely chopped 2-3 green chilies, finely chopped 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 2 tablespoons oil 1/2 teaspoon mustard seeds     (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    1/2 teas</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 08:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/carrot-fried-rice-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg Biryani Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Egg Biryani in Andhra style:  Ingredients:  For the rice:   2 cups basmati rice 4 cups water 1 bay leaf 2 green cardamom pods 2 cloves Salt to taste   For the egg marinade:   6 boiled eggs, peeled and pricked with a fork 1/2 cup yogurt 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder 1/2 teaspoon garam masala powder Salt to taste    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Oct 2023 18:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vegetable Biryani Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vegetable-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Vegetable Biryani in Andhra style:  Ingredients:  For the rice:   2 cups basmati rice 4 cups water 1 bay leaf 2 green cardamom pods 2 cloves Salt to taste   For the vegetable mixture:   2 tablespoons oil or ghee 1 large onion, thinly sliced 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 1 cup mixed vegetables (such as carrots, peas, beans, cauliflower), c</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Sep 2023 13:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vegetable-biryani-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Jonna roti with chili chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jonna-roti-with-chili-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Jonna Roti (Sorghum Roti) with Chilli Chutney in Andhra style:  For Jonna Roti:  Ingredients:   2 cups jowar flour (sorghum flour) Water as needed Salt to taste Oil or ghee for cooking   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the jowar flour and salt. Gradually add water and knead the flour to form a soft and pliable dough. Add water as needed to achieve the right consis</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Sep 2023 09:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jonna-roti-with-chili-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ragi roti with tomato chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ragi-roti-with-tomato-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Ragi Roti with Tomato Chutney in Andhra style:  #1 For Ragi Roti:   1 cup ragi flour (finger millet flour) 1/4 cup finely chopped onions 1/4 cup grated carrots 2 green chilies, finely chopped 2 tablespoons chopped coriander leaves Salt to taste Water as needed Oil for cooking   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the ragi flour, chopped onions, grated carrots, green c</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ragi-roti-with-tomato-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Gongura Pappu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gongura-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Gongura Pappu, a popular Andhra-style lentil curry made with Gongura leaves (sorrel leaves):  Ingredients:   1 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 cups Gongura leaves, washed and chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2023 08:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gongura-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vankaya Pappu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vankaya-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Vankaya Pappu, an Andhra-style lentil and eggplant curry:  Ingredients:   1 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 small eggplants (brinjals), chopped into cubes 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon coriander powder </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vankaya-pappu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pasta at home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pasta-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a simple recipe for making pasta at home:  Ingredients:   8 ounces (225 grams) dried pasta (such as spaghetti, penne, or fettuccine) Water for boiling Salt for seasoning Olive oil (optional)   Instructions:   Fill a large pot with water and bring it to a boil over high heat. Add a generous amount of salt to the boiling water. Once the water is boiling, add the pasta to the pot. Stir gen</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:41:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pasta-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Pizza at home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pizza-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for homemade pizza:  For the Pizza Dough:  Ingredients:   2 &amp;frac12; cups all-purpose flour 2 &amp;frac14; teaspoons instant yeast 1 teaspoon sugar 1 teaspoon salt 1 cup warm water 2 tablespoons olive oil   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine the flour, instant yeast, sugar and salt. Gradually add the warm water while stirring the mixture. Knead the dough for about 5-7 minute</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 20:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-pizza-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare paneer kulcha at home - Paneer Kulcha Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-paneer-kulcha-at-home-paneer-kulcha-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Paneer Kulcha, a popular Indian bread stuffed with paneer (Indian cottage cheese):  For the Kulcha Dough:  Ingredients:   2 cups all-purpose flour (maida) 1/2 teaspoon baking powder 1/2 teaspoon baking soda 1/2 teaspoon salt 1/2 cup plain yogurt 2 tablespoons oil Water as needed   Instructions:   In a mixing bowl, combine all-purpose flour, baking powder, baking soda and sa</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 17:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-paneer-kulcha-at-home-paneer-kulcha-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare gobi manchurian at home - Gobi Manchurian Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-gobi-manchurian-at-home-gobi-manchurian-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Gobi Manchurian, a popular Indo-Chinese dish made with cauliflower:  Ingredients:  For the batter:   1 medium-sized cauliflower, cut into florets 1/2 cup all-purpose flour (maida) 1/4 cup cornstarch 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder 1/2 teaspoon soy sauce 1/2 teaspoon vinegar Salt to taste Water as needed Oil for deep frying   For the sauce:   1 t</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-gobi-manchurian-at-home-gobi-manchurian-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cook Onion Rava Dosa at home - Onion Rava Dosa Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-onion-rava-dosa-at-home-onion-rava-dosa-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Onion Rava Dosa is a popular South Indian crepe made with semolina (rava), rice flour, and a mix of spices and onions. It is thin, crispy, and doesn&amp;#39;t require fermentation, making it a quick and tasty meal option.  Ingredients   1 cup semolina (rava) 1/2 cup rice flour 1/4 cup all-purpose flour (maida) 1 medium onion, finely chopped 2 green chilies, finely chopped 1/4 cup coriander leaves, cho</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:38:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-onion-rava-dosa-at-home-onion-rava-dosa-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cook Lemon Rice at home - Lemon Rice Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-lemon-rice-at-home-lemon-rice-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Lemon Rice, a tangy and flavorful rice dish:  Ingredients:   1 cup basmati rice (or any long-grain rice) 2 tablespoons oil 1 teaspoon mustard seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/4 cup peanuts 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 curry leaves 1/4 teaspoon turmeric powder Juice of 1 lemon Salt to taste Fresh coriander leaves for garnishing           </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-lemon-rice-at-home-lemon-rice-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Veg Kurma at Home - Veg Kurma Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-veg-kurma-at-home-veg-kurma-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Veg Kurma, a creamy and flavorful Indian dish made with mixed vegetables:  Ingredients:   2 cups mixed vegetables (carrots, beans, potatoes, peas, cauliflower, etc.), chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 cup grated coconut 1/4 cup cashew nuts 1 teaspoon fennel seeds 1 teaspoon cumin </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-veg-kurma-at-home-veg-kurma-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Bisi bele bhath at Home - Bisi bele bhath Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-bisi-bele-bhath-at-home-bisi-bele-bhath-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Bisi Bele Bhath, a flavorful and traditional dish from Karnataka, India:  Ingredients:  For the spice paste:   2 tablespoons chana dal (Bengal gram) 1 tablespoon urad dal (split black gram) 1 tablespoon coriander seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon fenugreek seeds 6-8 dried red chilies 1/2 teaspoon peppercorns 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder                      (adsbygoog</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-bisi-bele-bhath-at-home-bisi-bele-bhath-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cook Pongal at Home - Pongal Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Pongal, a popular South Indian dish made with rice and lentils:  Ingredients:   1 cup raw rice 1/4 cup split yellow moong dal (split yellow lentils) 4 cups water 2 tablespoons ghee (clarified butter) 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon whole black peppercorns 1 tablespoon grated ginger A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 cashew nuts 10-12 curry leaves Salt to taste            </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Cauliflower Peas Masala at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Cauliflower Peas Masala:  Ingredients:   1 small cauliflower, cut into florets 1 cup green peas 2 onions, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon coriander powder 1/2 teaspoon garam masala Salt to tast</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>