<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Recipe - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/recipe.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to prepare gobi manchurian at home - Gobi Manchurian Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-gobi-manchurian-at-home-gobi-manchurian-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Gobi Manchurian, a popular Indo-Chinese dish made with cauliflower:  Ingredients:  For the batter:   1 medium-sized cauliflower, cut into florets 1/2 cup all-purpose flour (maida) 1/4 cup cornstarch 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 teaspoon red chili powder 1/2 teaspoon soy sauce 1/2 teaspoon vinegar Salt to taste Water as needed Oil for deep frying   For the sauce:   1 t</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 10:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-gobi-manchurian-at-home-gobi-manchurian-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cook Onion Rava Dosa at home - Onion Rava Dosa Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-onion-rava-dosa-at-home-onion-rava-dosa-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Onion Rava Dosa, a popular South Indian crepe made with semolina (rava) and onions:  Ingredients:   1 cup semolina (rava) 1/2 cup rice flour 1/4 cup all-purpose flour (maida) 1 onion, finely chopped 2 green chilies, finely chopped 1/4 cup chopped coriander leaves 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon black pepper, coarsely crushed 1/2 teaspoon grated ginger Salt to taste Water </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 15:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-onion-rava-dosa-at-home-onion-rava-dosa-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to cook Lemon Rice at home - Lemon Rice Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-lemon-rice-at-home-lemon-rice-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Lemon Rice, a tangy and flavorful rice dish:  Ingredients:   1 cup basmati rice (or any long-grain rice) 2 tablespoons oil 1 teaspoon mustard seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/4 cup peanuts 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 curry leaves 1/4 teaspoon turmeric powder Juice of 1 lemon Salt to taste Fresh coriander leaves for garnishing           </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 07:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-cook-lemon-rice-at-home-lemon-rice-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Veg Kurma at Home - Veg Kurma Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-veg-kurma-at-home-veg-kurma-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Veg Kurma, a creamy and flavorful Indian dish made with mixed vegetables:  Ingredients:   2 cups mixed vegetables (carrots, beans, potatoes, peas, cauliflower, etc.), chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 tablespoon ginger-garlic paste 1/2 cup grated coconut 1/4 cup cashew nuts 1 teaspoon fennel seeds 1 teaspoon cumin </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 11:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-veg-kurma-at-home-veg-kurma-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Bisi bele bhath at Home - Bisi bele bhath Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-bisi-bele-bhath-at-home-bisi-bele-bhath-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Bisi Bele Bhath, a flavorful and traditional dish from Karnataka, India:  Ingredients:  For the spice paste:   2 tablespoons chana dal (Bengal gram) 1 tablespoon urad dal (split black gram) 1 tablespoon coriander seeds 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon fenugreek seeds 6-8 dried red chilies 1/2 teaspoon peppercorns 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder                      (adsbygoog</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-bisi-bele-bhath-at-home-bisi-bele-bhath-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cook Pongal at Home - Pongal Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Pongal, a popular South Indian dish made with rice and lentils:  Ingredients:   1 cup raw rice 1/4 cup split yellow moong dal (split yellow lentils) 4 cups water 2 tablespoons ghee (clarified butter) 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1 teaspoon whole black peppercorns 1 tablespoon grated ginger A pinch of asafoetida (hing) 10-12 cashew nuts 10-12 curry leaves Salt to taste            </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cook-pongal-at-home-pongal-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Prepare Cauliflower Peas Masala at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for Cauliflower Peas Masala:  Ingredients:   1 small cauliflower, cut into florets 1 cup green peas 2 onions, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, finely chopped 2 green chilies, slit lengthwise 1 teaspoon ginger-garlic paste 1 teaspoon cumin seeds 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to taste) 1 teaspoon coriander powder 1/2 teaspoon garam masala Salt to tast</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/prepare-cauliflower-peas-masala-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Sambar at Home - Sambar recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sambar-at-home-sambar-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Andhra-style vegetable sambar, a delicious South Indian dish made with lentils and mixed vegetables, Here&amp;#39;s the recipe:  Ingredients:   1/2 cup toor dal (split pigeon peas) 2 cups mixed vegetables (such as drumsticks, carrots, beans, brinjal, pumpkin, etc.), chopped 1 onion, finely chopped 2 tomatoes, chopped 2 tablespoons tamarind pulp 2 tablespoons sambar powder 1/2 teaspoon turmeric powder </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-sambar-at-home-sambar-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Palak Paneer at Home - Palak Paneer Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Palak paneer is a popular North Indian dish made with spinach and paneer (Indian cheese).  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing palak paneer at home for serving four people:  Ingredients:   2 cups chopped spinach (palak) 200g paneer, cut into small cubes 1 medium-sized onion, chopped 2 medium-sized tomatoes, chopped 1 tbsp ginger-garlic paste 1 green chili, chopped                                    </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-palak-paneer-at-home-palakpaneer-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prepare Mango Pickle at Home - Mango Pickle Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Mango pickle is a popular Indian condiment made with raw mangoes and spices.  Mango pickle is a variety of pickles prepared using mango. It is very popular in South and Southeast Asia. The pickling process in India differs from other regions mainly due to an additional spice mixture added to them after anaerobic fermentation.  Here&amp;#39;s a recipe for preparing mango pickle at home:  Ingredients:  </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prepare-mango-pickle-at-home-mango-pickle-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian style Spanish omelette, Egg + Potato + Onion</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</link>
			<description>Egg with Potato plus Onion will make a delicious and healthy breakfast, You have have it as a Breakfast or you can have it as a Snack in the day, will also be a great starter in the barbecue. This combination of dish is called Spanish omelette, but lets make it in Indian Style.  Ingredients Needed?  3 Eggs, 4 medium sized Potato (chopped in small) &amp;amp; 4 medium sized Onion (chopped in small), 4-5</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-style-spanish-omellete.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg Stuffed Paratha Home made Recipe</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</link>
			<description>Egg Stuffed Paratha is a delicious and healthy Paratha dish, filled with egg mixture. Both the eggs and whole wheat are healthy as it provides the right amount of proteins and carbs. The egg mixture has finely chopped onions, green chili and coriander leaves. This is then slided into the half cooked paratha pockets and cooked further. The Egg Stuffed Parathas are quite filling in itself.  Ingredie</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-stuffed-paratha-home-made-recipe.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pudina chutney Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Pudina Chutney is a flavorful condiment and aromatic chutney to serve with rice, mudde, idli, dosa. Pudina Chutney can also be served with snacks like bonda, bajji too.  People sometimes are confused pudina chutney with mint chutney or green chutney that is served along with chats and tandoori platter, but it&amp;#39;s not the same which we serve with rice or mudde or idle, and this chutney is more au</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pudina-chutney-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
			<description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Chintakaya Pachadi Recipe, Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi chintakaya pachadi (Green raw tamarind pickle) is an age-old dish, which is generally eaten with Rice &amp; some also eaten with Ghee for even better taste. As we Indians love the tangy &amp; sweetish taste of pickle, this delicious Pachi chintakaya pachadi is enjoyed by all age groups and in fact, the recipe is one among the famous Indian dishes. This dish also has many health benefits</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-chintakaya-pachadi-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pachi Pulusu Recipe - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Andhra Style Pachi Pulusu Recipe is a thin rasam made with freshly extracted tamarind water and mixed with sliced onions and freshly cut coriander leaves. Comfort food at its best when served with some steamed rice for a simple meal.
                                It is a different way of creating a rasam that has been followed by the people from Andhra Pradesh and Telangana. This rasam is not he</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pachi-pulusu-recipe-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Raw Mango Chutney - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>Raw mango chutney is a flavorful condiment made with raw mangos, coriander leaves, onions and some spices. Raw Mango Chutney is a must-try recipe when raw mangoes are in season. Raw mangoes are packed with minerals and vitamins and are good to beat the summer heat.
                                This raw mango chutney aids digestion and enhances the taste, aroma, and nutrition of any dish. We usu</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/raw-mango-chutney-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>