<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Relationship - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/relationship.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Horrible secrets that you cannot share with your partner and why?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/horrible-secrets-that-you-cannot-share-with-your-partner-and-why.html</link>
			<description>While open communication and honesty are generally important in a healthy relationship, there might be certain situations where it may not be necessary or beneficial to share certain information with your partner. However, it&amp;#39;s crucial to note that the concept of &amp;quot;horrible secrets&amp;quot; varies from person to person, and the decision to disclose or withhold information ultimately depends o</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 08:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/horrible-secrets-that-you-cannot-share-with-your-partner-and-why.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Seven tips to have a healthy relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/seven-tips-to-have-a-healthy-relationship.html</link>
			<description>Building and maintaining a healthy relationship requires effort, communication, and mutual respect. Here are seven tips to help foster a healthy and fulfilling relationship:   Effective Communication: Communication is key to any successful relationship. Foster open and honest communication by actively listening, expressing yourself clearly, and being receptive to your partner&amp;#39;s thoughts and fe</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/seven-tips-to-have-a-healthy-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten Best Romantic Relationship Tips</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-romantic-relationship-tips.html</link>
			<description>Building a strong and healthy romantic relationship requires effort, communication, and mutual respect. Here are some tips to help you foster a fulfilling and loving romantic relationship:   Effective Communication: Communication is key to any successful relationship. Be open, honest, and willing to listen to your partner. Express your thoughts, feelings, and needs clearly, and encourage your part</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-romantic-relationship-tips.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>People who cares the least has the most power in a Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-who-cares-the-least-has-the-most-power-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>The statement &amp;quot;People who care the least have the most power in a relationship&amp;quot; is a common belief, but it is not necessarily true or healthy for a relationship. Here&amp;#39;s why:   Power dynamics: Viewing relationships as power struggles can create an imbalance and undermine the foundation of trust, mutual respect, and equality. A healthy relationship is built on mutual care, understandin</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-who-cares-the-least-has-the-most-power-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Psychological facts about Attracting People</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/psychological-facts-about-attracting-people.html</link>
			<description>Psychological attraction is a complex and multifaceted topic influenced by various factors. Here are some psychological facts that may play a role in attracting people:   Physical appearance matters: Physical attractiveness can have an initial impact on attracting others. Studies have shown that certain features, such as symmetry, averageness, and healthy appearance, are generally perceived as mor</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/psychological-facts-about-attracting-people.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How do you take space in a Relationship without breaking up?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-you-take-space-in-a-relationship-without-breaking-up.html</link>
			<description>Taking space in a relationship can be healthy and necessary for both individuals to maintain their well-being and strengthen the relationship.  Here are some suggestions for taking space without breaking up:   Communicate openly: Talk to your partner about the need for space and the reasons behind it. Express your feelings, desires, and concerns in a calm and honest manner. Explain that taking spa</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 02 Jun 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-you-take-space-in-a-relationship-without-breaking-up.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lessons to be learnt from Marriage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-to-be-learnt-from-marriage.html</link>
			<description>Marriage is a complex and deeply personal experience, and the lessons one can learn from it can vary based on individual circumstances. However, here are some common lessons that people often learn from their marriages:   Communication is key: Effective communication is crucial for a healthy and thriving marriage. Learning to express your thoughts, emotions, and needs openly and honestly, while al</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-to-be-learnt-from-marriage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>UnConditional Love in a Couples Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>It is commonly said that Women are complex in mental nature while Men remain easy to understand and simple. Whatever be the reasons that backup this comment,&amp;nbsp;in relationships both Men and Women follow slightly diverted paths.&amp;nbsp;What Men look for in a relationship is not what motivates Women to fall in relationships. The differences in desires, mentalities, passion, expression levels etc., </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 28 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/un-conditional-love-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Expectations and Freedom in a Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</link>
			<description>People having expectations in a relationship and willing to have freedom in relationships are few of the main reasons for not having a peaceful and healthy relationship with each other.  Having or Setting some unrealistic expectations to have in a relationship can contribute to ending their marriage.  Honestly both the people should be open in communication to each other in terms of the expectatio</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2023 07:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/expectations-and-freedom-in-a-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tips to Overcome Suicidal Thoughts</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-overcome-suicidal-thoughts.html</link>
			<description>When you are having suicidal thoughts, first thing you need to tell your mind is you can overcome this, whatever the problem or situation is, you can overcome.  Suicidal thoughts are very difficult to handle or they are difficult to understand or explain. Sometimes they can be just going around your mind or sometimes they can become a thing, which you wish to do right away. In either case you have</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-to-overcome-suicidal-thoughts.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Stop Overthinking your Thoughts of Future</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</link>
			<description>Overthinking your thoughts will lead you to even more worry. If you are an overthinker or a person who thinks to take precautions for the future, then you will know exactly how it goes. Generally a problem comes to your mind, for example a worry or health or a problem at work or some sort of issue in a relationship, because of the thoughts you will be thinking about it a lot and you will try to ge</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Having Good Sex at any Age! Is it Really Possible?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/having-good-sex-at-any-age-is-it-really-possible.html</link>
			<description>No matter what is your gender, you can always enjoy sex for as long as you wish. And naturally sex at age of 70 or 80&amp;nbsp;may not be same&amp;nbsp;like it is at would be at 20 or 30, but It would be better in some ways.  Sex can be one of the powerful emotional experience and one of the great tool for protecting or improving your health, And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean, you can have it only at young age. Y</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/having-good-sex-at-any-age-is-it-really-possible.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>South Indian Hindu Marriage - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</link>
			<description>South Indian weddings are traditionally going to be planned or happen for one or more than a day, which involve having mehndi for the bride particularly, in some cases times groom as well have mehndi. Few of the south Indians have Haldi ceremonies as well. Groom's arrival itself is celebrated. And the wedding ceremony begins with a few pooja’s &amp; traditions. And at the end, the couple will be sen</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/south-indian-hindu-marriage-andhra-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>UNSAID CONFESSIONS - Some insights that one can take</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unsaid-confessions.html</link>
			<description>What does confessing something, which concerns you, to one who cares about you, does to your life? Confession means when you admit that you have done something wrong. Here, we have our fellow being Anand, who had an argument with his brother over property issues and ended up not interacting with his brother for years.
                                After 10 years, when he had gone for a health ch</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unsaid-confessions.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lessons Learnt from three years of Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-learnt-from-three-years-of-relationship.html</link>
			<description>Living together for almost three years is a good amount of journey in your life. For me atleast like, part of me feels like time is absolutely flying and the other half feels like we have been married for three years. We have certainly not been perfect, but I'm gonna share fews lessons which I learnt out of these three years which I spent in my relationship.
                            1. Importan</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/lessons-learnt-from-three-years-of-relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Fighting in a Couple's Relationship is Normal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fighting-in-a-relationship-is-normal.html</link>
			<description>Every Couple will fight &amp; it's completely Normal, unless its scares both of them. No two people are exactly the same way, each of them are unique. Couples can occasionally or often might have conflicts or disagreements which might lead to an argument of fight. If that particular conflict of argument is taken as a healthy discussion, then you will be knowing more about your partner and you both wil</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fighting-in-a-relationship-is-normal.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>