<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Relationship - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Relationship.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Stop Overthinking your Thoughts of Future</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</link>
			<description>Overthinking your thoughts will lead you to even more worry. If you are an overthinker or a person who thinks to take precautions for the future, then you will know exactly how it goes. Generally a problem comes to your mind, for example a worry or health or a problem at work or some sort of issue in a relationship, because of the thoughts you will be thinking about it a lot and you will try to ge</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 24 Jul 2022 15:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/stop-overthinking-your-thoughts-of-future.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>South Indian Hindu Marriage - Andhra Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/South-Indian-Hindu-Marriage-Andhra-Style.html</link>
			<description>South Indian weddings are traditionally going to be planned or happen for one or more than a day, which involve having mehndi for the bride particularly, in some cases times groom as well have mehndi. Few of the south Indians have Haldi ceremonies as well. Groom's arrival itself is celebrated. And the wedding ceremony begins with a few pooja’s &amp; traditions. And at the end, the couple will be sen</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Jun 2021 16:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/South-Indian-Hindu-Marriage-Andhra-Style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>UNSAID CONFESSIONS - Some insights that one can take</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/UNSAID-CONFESSIONS.html</link>
			<description>What does confessing something, which concerns you, to one who cares about you, does to your life? Confession means when you admit that you have done something wrong. Here, we have our fellow being Anand, who had an argument with his brother over property issues and ended up not interacting with his brother for years.
                                After 10 years, when he had gone for a health ch</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 05 Mar 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/UNSAID-CONFESSIONS.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Lessons Learnt from three years of Relationship</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Lessons-Learnt-from-three-years-of-Relationship.html</link>
			<description>Living together for almost three years is a good amount of journey in your life. For me atleast like, part of me feels like time is absolutely flying and the other half feels like we have been married for three years. We have certainly not been perfect, but I'm gonna share fews lessons which I learnt out of these three years which I spent in my relationship.
                            1. Importan</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Jul 2021 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Lessons-Learnt-from-three-years-of-Relationship.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Fighting in a Couple's Relationship is Normal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Fighting-in-a-Relationship-is-Normal.html</link>
			<description>Every Couple will fight &amp; it's completely Normal, unless its scares both of them. No two people are exactly the same way, each of them are unique. Couples can occasionally or often might have conflicts or disagreements which might lead to an argument of fight. If that particular conflict of argument is taken as a healthy discussion, then you will be knowing more about your partner and you both wil</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 04 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Fighting-in-a-Relationship-is-Normal.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>