<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Sci-Tech - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sci-tech.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Ant Farm Observation, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ant-farm-observation-discovering-the-secret-life-of-ants.html</link>
			<description>Have you ever wondered what ants do underground, where we cannot see them? By making a simple DIY ant farm, you can peek into their busy little world and learn how they live, work, and build amazing colonies. This experiment is not only fun but also teaches us about teamwork, survival, and nature&amp;rsquo;s tiny engineers.  Materials You Will Need   A clear glass jar or plastic container Clean sand o</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Sep 2025 10:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ant-farm-observation-discovering-the-secret-life-of-ants.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Nature Scavenger Hunt, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/nature-scavenger-hunt-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>A nature scavenger hunt is a delightful and educational science experiment that encourages children to explore the outdoors while learning about their natural environment. This activity combines adventure with observation, helping children develop their understanding of nature, enhance their observational skills and foster a sense of curiosity. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to organizing a nat</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Aug 2025 10:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/nature-scavenger-hunt-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rain Gauge, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rain-gauge-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a DIY rain gauge is a fantastic science experiment for children to understand meteorology and hydrology. A rain gauge measures the amount of precipitation that falls over a period of time. This simple project allows children to observe and record rainfall, helping them learn about weather patterns and data collection. Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to making a basic rain gauge.  Materi</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 10 Aug 2025 15:33:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rain-gauge-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Shadow Tracing, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/shadow-tracing-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Shadow tracing is an excellent way for children to explore concepts related to the Earth&amp;#39;s rotation, the position of the sun and how these factors affect shadow length and direction. This simple science experiment demonstrates how the position of the sun in the sky changes throughout the day and how this affects the shadows cast by objects. Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed guide on how to conduct this </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 May 2025 17:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/shadow-tracing-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why Choose Drupal for your Blogging Website in 2025?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-choose-drupal-for-your-blogging-website-in-.html</link>
			<description>With so many blogging platforms available in 2025, why should you consider Drupal over WordPress, Ghost, or Joomla? While WordPress is widely known for personal and small-scale blogging, Drupal excels in flexibility, security, and scalability, making it an excellent choice for professional bloggers and content-heavy websites.  If you&amp;rsquo;re serious about blogging and need a powerful, future-proo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 12:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-choose-drupal-for-your-blogging-website-in-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Geodesic Dome, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-geodesic-dome-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a geodesic dome is an exciting and educational science experiment that helps children understand geometric principles, engineering concepts and structural design. A geodesic dome is a spherical structure composed of interconnected triangles, which provides a strong and stable framework.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide for creating a DIY geodesic dome using paper or straws.  Materials N</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 09:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-geodesic-dome-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Pi Day Celebration, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pi-day-celebration-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Pi Day, celebrated on March 14th (3/14, reflecting the first three digits of pi, 3.14), is a perfect opportunity to engage children in learning about the mathematical constant pi (&amp;pi;). This activity involves measuring the circumference and diameter of circles to understand how pi relates to these measurements.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a fun and educational science experiment to celebrate Pi Day and explore</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Jan 2025 08:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pi-day-celebration-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Deploying Drupal on Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/deploying-drupal-on-azure-kubernetes-service-aks.html</link>
			<description>Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS), offered by Microsoft Azure, is a fully managed container orchestration service that leverages Kubernetes to manage, deploy, and scale applications in containers. Kubernetes is the go-to platform for automating the deployment, scaling, and management of containerized applications, making it an ideal choice for running complex web applications like Drupal.  Drupal, an</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 19:24:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/deploying-drupal-on-azure-kubernetes-service-aks.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding Azure Key Vault: Key Concepts and Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-key-vault-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>In the modern cloud-driven world, security is more critical than ever. Organizations are increasingly migrating their data, applications, and infrastructure to the cloud, but with this transition comes the need to protect sensitive information such as secrets, keys, certificates, and passwords. Azure Key Vault is a cloud service provided by Microsoft Azure designed specifically to safeguard and ma</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Jan 2025 07:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-key-vault-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tesselation Art, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tesselation-art-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Tessellation art is a wonderful way for children to explore geometry and symmetry through creative expression. Tessellations involve creating patterns that cover a surface without any gaps or overlaps using geometric shapes. This activity helps children understand concepts such as shape, symmetry and repetition in a fun and engaging way.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to creating tessellation </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 07 Jan 2025 08:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tesselation-art-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding Azure Active Directory &amp; Azure App Registrations: Key Concepts and Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-active-directory-azure-app-registrations-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>In the modern world of cloud computing, managing identity and access is crucial to securing enterprise applications and data. Microsoft Azure provides a comprehensive identity and access management solution through Azure Active Directory (Azure AD). Whether you are managing an enterprise IT environment or building cloud-based applications, understanding Azure AD and Azure App Registrations is foun</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 13:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-active-directory-azure-app-registrations-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding Azure Front Door and CDN Profiles: Key Concepts and Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-front-door-and-cdn-profiles-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>In today&amp;rsquo;s cloud-first world, providing fast, reliable, and secure access to web applications is critical for a positive user experience. With users across different geographic regions, ensuring low-latency content delivery and application optimization is key to improving performance. Azure Front Door and Azure Content Delivery Network (CDN) are two essential services in Azure that help orga</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2024 09:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-front-door-and-cdn-profiles-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding Azure Storage Accounts: Key Concepts and Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-storage-accounts-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>Azure Storage is a cloud service provided by Microsoft Azure that allows users to store and manage data in a highly scalable, secure, and cost-effective manner. One of the core components of Azure Storage is the Azure Storage Account. An Azure Storage Account provides a unique namespace for storing data in Azure and serves as the container for different types of storage services, such as Blob Stor</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 08:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-storage-accounts-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS): Key Concepts and Best Practices</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-kubernetes-service-aks-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</link>
			<description>As the adoption of cloud-native technologies grows, Kubernetes has become the de facto standard for orchestrating containerized applications. Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) is Microsoft&amp;#39;s managed Kubernetes offering in the Azure cloud, designed to simplify the deployment, management, and scaling of containerized applications. AKS helps organizations take advantage of Kubernetes&amp;#39; robust fea</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-azure-kubernetes-service-aks-key-concepts-and-best-practices.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Migrating from JSStream to Vimeo Using Drupal Migration API</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrating-from-jsstream-to-vimeo-using-drupal-migration-api.html</link>
			<description>Migrating video content from JSStream (a custom video streaming platform) to Vimeo can be a crucial task if you&amp;#39;re looking for a more scalable, feature-rich platform for hosting and managing your videos. While manual migration might work for small datasets, automating the process via Drupal&amp;rsquo;s Migration API can save significant time and reduce errors, especially for larger video libraries</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Dec 2024 08:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/migrating-from-jsstream-to-vimeo-using-drupal-migration-api.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to Create a Document Library in SharePoint and Configure Content Types, Terms, User Groups, and Permissions</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-create-a-document-library-in-sharepoint-and-configure-content-types-terms-user-groups-and-permissions.html</link>
			<description>SharePoint is a robust collaboration platform that helps organizations manage and share documents and other content. One of the key features of SharePoint is the ability to create Document Libraries, which serve as centralized repositories for storing, organizing, and managing documents. These libraries can be highly customized with features like Content Types, Managed Metadata (Terms), User Group</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 08:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-create-a-document-library-in-sharepoint-and-configure-content-types-terms-user-groups-and-permissions.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding SharePoint Document Libraries, Content Types, Terms, User Groups and Permissions</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sharepoint-document-libraries-content-types-terms-user-groups-and-permissions.html</link>
			<description>SharePoint is a powerful collaboration platform that allows organizations to store, manage, and share content efficiently. One of the core features of SharePoint is the Document Library, which provides a centralized location for storing files and documents. To enhance document management, SharePoint allows for a range of customization options, including Content Types, Managed Metadata (Terms), Use</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sharepoint-document-libraries-content-types-terms-user-groups-and-permissions.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding SharePoint Documents vs. Document Sets: Key Differences and Use Cases</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sharepoint-documents-vs-document-sets-key-differences-and-use-cases.html</link>
			<description>When working with SharePoint, a robust collaboration and document management platform, it&amp;#39;s important to understand the different ways you can organize and manage your files. Two key features for managing files in SharePoint are Documents and Document Sets. Although they may seem similar at first glance, they serve different purposes and offer distinct features to help you manage your content </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 07:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sharepoint-documents-vs-document-sets-key-differences-and-use-cases.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mastering Graph Algorithms in PHP: Implementing Traversals and Shortest Path Algorithms</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mastering-graph-algorithms-in-php-implementing-traversals-and-shortest-path-algorithms.html</link>
			<description>Graphs are one of the most powerful and flexible data structures in computer science, widely used for solving problems like shortest path finding, network analysis, and much more. In PHP 8, developers can leverage modern language features and optimized approaches to implement and optimize graph-related algorithms.  In this article, we will explore graph data structures, common graph traversals, an</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 07:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mastering-graph-algorithms-in-php-implementing-traversals-and-shortest-path-algorithms.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mastering Dynamic Programming in PHP: A Deep Dive into Classic Algorithms</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mastering-dynamic-programming-in-php-a-deep-dive-into-classic-algorithms.html</link>
			<description>Dynamic Programming (DP) is a powerful technique used to solve complex problems by breaking them down into simpler subproblems. It is particularly useful for optimization problems, where the goal is to find the best solution under given constraints. DP is often seen in algorithms that require making decisions at multiple steps, where solutions to subproblems are reused to avoid redundant calculati</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mastering-dynamic-programming-in-php-a-deep-dive-into-classic-algorithms.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Math Board Games, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-math-board-games-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating and playing math-based board games is a fantastic way for children to learn math concepts while having fun. These DIY games can be tailored to various age groups and skill levels, making math practice engaging and interactive.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to designing and playing your own math board games.  Materials Needed:   Cardboard or Poster Board: For the game board. Markers o</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 08:07:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-math-board-games-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Advanced Sorting and Searching Algorithms in PHP: Quick Sort, Merge Sort, Heap Sort, and Binary Search Trees</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advanced-sorting-and-searching-algorithms-in-php-quick-sort-merge-sort-heap-sort-and-binary-search-trees.html</link>
			<description>Sorting and searching are foundational operations in computer science. Understanding the efficient algorithms for these tasks can significantly enhance the performance of your applications.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore three advanced sorting algorithms &amp;mdash; Quick Sort, Merge Sort, and Heap Sort &amp;mdash; and dive into implementing Binary Search Trees (BST) in PHP 8.  We&amp;rsquo;ll include </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Nov 2024 07:53:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advanced-sorting-and-searching-algorithms-in-php-quick-sort-merge-sort-heap-sort-and-binary-search-trees.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Data Structures in PHP: Implementing Stacks, Queues, Linked Lists, and SPL Classes</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/data-structures-in-php-implementing-stacks-queues-linked-lists-and-spl-classes.html</link>
			<description>Data structures are an integral part of programming, offering efficient ways to store and organize data. As PHP evolves, understanding how to implement and utilize common data structures like Stacks, Queues, and Linked Lists will make you a more proficient PHP developer. PHP 8 provides a range of options, from manual implementations to built-in SPL (Standard PHP Library) classes that offer high pe</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 07:59:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/data-structures-in-php-implementing-stacks-queues-linked-lists-and-spl-classes.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Optimizing a Product Catalog Microservice with Profiling Tools in PHP Using DDEV and Visual Studio Code</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimizing-a-product-catalog-microservice-with-profiling-tools-in-php-using-ddev-and-visual-studio-code.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we will enhance the product catalog microservice we built earlier by integrating Xdebug for profiling, specifically tailored for development in Visual Studio Code (VS Code). We will include detailed setup instructions, ensuring a smooth experience while profiling your application.  Overview  Key Components   PHP 8: The programming language for our microservice. MySQL: The database</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 08:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimizing-a-product-catalog-microservice-with-profiling-tools-in-php-using-ddev-and-visual-studio-code.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Code Profiling and Performance Optimization of an Existing PHP Project</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/code-profiling-and-performance-optimization-of-an-existing-php-project.html</link>
			<description>As applications grow in complexity, ensuring optimal performance becomes critical. Code profiling and performance optimization are essential practices that help developers identify bottlenecks and improve the efficiency of their PHP applications.  In this article, we will explore the tools and techniques for code profiling and performance optimization in PHP 8.  What is Code Profiling?  Code profi</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Nov 2024 08:36:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/code-profiling-and-performance-optimization-of-an-existing-php-project.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Advanced OOP Features in PHP: Final Classes, Magic Methods, and Late Static Binding</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advanced-oop-features-in-php-final-classes-magic-methods-and-late-static-binding.html</link>
			<description>Object-Oriented Programming (OOP) is a programming paradigm that uses objects and classes to design and structure code. PHP, especially in its latest iteration, PHP 8, provides several advanced OOP features that enhance its capabilities and allow for more robust and maintainable code.  In this article, we will explore three advanced OOP features in PHP 8: final classes, magic methods, and late sta</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Nov 2024 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/advanced-oop-features-in-php-final-classes-magic-methods-and-late-static-binding.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing a Redis Cache for Product Catalog Data in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-redis-cache-for-product-catalog-data-in-php.html</link>
			<description>Caching is a vital technique for improving application performance, especially in e-commerce platforms where product catalog data is frequently accessed. By using Redis as a caching layer, you can significantly reduce database load and improve response times for users.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll walk through the steps to implement a Redis cache for product catalog data in a PHP 8 application.  </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 09:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-redis-cache-for-product-catalog-data-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to Caching and Setting Up Redis in PHP 8</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-caching-and-setting-up-redis-in-php-.html</link>
			<description>Caching is a fundamental technique used in software development to enhance performance and efficiency by storing frequently accessed data in a temporary storage layer. In PHP 8, caching can significantly reduce load times and improve the overall user experience of web applications.  This article will provide an overview of caching, its benefits, and common use cases.  What is Caching?  Caching inv</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 10:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-caching-and-setting-up-redis-in-php-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing a Notification System Using the Observer Pattern in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-notification-system-using-the-observer-pattern-in-php.html</link>
			<description>The Observer pattern is a powerful design pattern that promotes a one-to-many dependency between objects. This pattern is particularly useful in scenarios where changes in one object need to be reflected across multiple objects. A classic use case for the Observer pattern is in building a notification system, where subscribers (observers) are notified of changes in a publisher (subject).  In this </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 15:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-notification-system-using-the-observer-pattern-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Origami Geometry, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/origami-geometry-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Origami is a fantastic way to explore and understand geometric concepts through hands-on activity. By folding paper to create different shapes and structures, children can visualize and learn about various geometric principles.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed article to a &amp;quot;Origami Geometry&amp;quot; science experiment for children, focusing on basic geometric shapes and concepts.  Materials Needed:   Or</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 14:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/origami-geometry-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>When and How to Use Each Design Pattern in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-and-how-to-use-each-design-pattern-in-php.html</link>
			<description>Design patterns are proven solutions to common problems in software design. In PHP 8, these patterns can enhance code readability, maintainability and scalability.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore some of the most common design patterns, when to use them and how to implement them in PHP 8.  1. Singleton Pattern  When to Use   Use the Singleton pattern when you need to ensure that a class has </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 06:51:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-and-how-to-use-each-design-pattern-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Exploring Design Patterns in PHP 8: Strategy, Observer and Decorator</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/exploring-design-patterns-in-php--strategy-observer-and-decorator.html</link>
			<description>Design patterns are essential tools for software developers, providing proven solutions to common problems. In PHP 8, leveraging design patterns can lead to more maintainable, scalable and flexible code.  This article will explore three key design patterns: Strategy, Observer and Decorator. We will delve into their principles and provide practical examples to illustrate how they can be implemented</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 16:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/exploring-design-patterns-in-php--strategy-observer-and-decorator.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing a Logger System Using the Singleton Pattern in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-logger-system-using-the-singleton-pattern-in-php.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we&amp;#39;ll create a simple logger system using the Singleton Pattern in PHP.  This logger will allow you to log messages to a file, ensuring that there is only one instance of the logger throughout your application.  Step-by-Step Implementation  Step 1: Create the Logger Class  We&amp;#39;ll start by defining a Logger class that follows the Singleton Pattern. This class will have metho</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 28 Oct 2024 08:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-a-logger-system-using-the-singleton-pattern-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing Design Patterns in Real-World PHP Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-design-patterns-in-real-world-php-applications.html</link>
			<description>Design patterns are proven solutions to common software design problems. They help improve code readability, maintainability and scalability.  In this article, we&amp;#39;ll explore how to implement some of the most commonly used design patterns, Factory, Singleton and Dependency Injection, in real-world PHP applications using PHP 8.  1. Factory Pattern  Scenario  Imagine you&amp;rsquo;re developing an e-</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Oct 2024 20:39:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-design-patterns-in-real-world-php-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to Design Patterns: Factory, Singleton and Dependency Injection</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-design-patterns-factory-singleton-and-dependency-injection.html</link>
			<description>Design patterns are essential tools for developers looking to write clean, maintainable and scalable code. In PHP 8, leveraging design patterns can significantly enhance your software architecture.  This article introduces three fundamental design patterns: Factory, Singleton and Dependency Injection, explaining their purpose, use cases and providing practical examples.  1. Factory Pattern  What i</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2024 08:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-design-patterns-factory-singleton-and-dependency-injection.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding SQL Query Execution Plans and Optimizing Joins</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sql-query-execution-plans-and-optimizing-joins.html</link>
			<description>In the realm of database management, performance is paramount. One of the most effective ways to enhance SQL query efficiency is through a deep understanding of query execution plans and the optimization of joins.  This article will provide a comprehensive overview of these concepts, helping you to write faster, more efficient SQL queries.  What is an SQL Query Execution Plan?  An SQL query execut</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 18:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sql-query-execution-plans-and-optimizing-joins.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Using Indexes to Speed Up SQL Queries</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/using-indexes-to-speed-up-sql-queries.html</link>
			<description>Using indexes to speed up SQL queries is an essential technique in database optimization. Here&amp;rsquo;s a concise guide on how to effectively use indexes:  What Are Indexes?  An index is a database object that improves the speed of data retrieval. Think of it like an index in a book, which allows you to find information quickly without scanning every page.  Types of Indexes   Single-Column Index: I</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/using-indexes-to-speed-up-sql-queries.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>SQL Transactions for Atomic Operations: Ensuring Data Integrity and Consistency</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sql-transactions-for-atomic-operations-ensuring-data-integrity-and-consistency.html</link>
			<description>Implementing transactions for atomic operations is crucial in ensuring data integrity and consistency, especially in databases and concurrent applications.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a high-level overview of how to implement transactions, focusing on the key concepts and techniques involved.  Key Concepts   Atomicity: Ensures that a series of operations either complete entirely or have no effect at all. If any</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 24 Oct 2024 08:47:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sql-transactions-for-atomic-operations-ensuring-data-integrity-and-consistency.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Writing Secure SQL Queries Using Prepared Statements</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/writing-secure-sql-queries-using-prepared-statements.html</link>
			<description>Writing secure SQL queries is crucial to prevent vulnerabilities such as SQL injection. Using prepared statements is one of the best practices to ensure that your SQL queries are safe.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a guide on how to do this effectively.  What are Prepared Statements?  Prepared statements are a feature of many database management systems (DBMS) that allow you to define a SQL query template and the</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 23 Oct 2024 08:17:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/writing-secure-sql-queries-using-prepared-statements.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Implementing One-to-Many and Many-to-Many Relationships</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-one-to-many-and-many-to-many-relationships.html</link>
			<description>Implementing one-to-many and many-to-many relationships in a database is essential for accurately modeling real-world scenarios.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed look at how to set up these relationships in a relational database.  One-to-Many Relationship  A one-to-many relationship occurs when a single record in one table can relate to multiple records in another table.  Example Scenario: Consider a User</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 18:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/implementing-one-to-many-and-many-to-many-relationships.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Wind Vane, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/wind-vane-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple wind vane is a fun and educational science experiment for children that helps them understand wind direction and meteorological concepts. A wind vane, or weather vane, indicates the direction from which the wind is blowing.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to building a basic wind vane using common materials:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Straw or Wooden Dowel: For the central a</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 12:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/wind-vane-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Designing Efficient Schemas for Web Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/designing-efficient-schemas-for-web-applications.html</link>
			<description>The design of an efficient database schema is crucial for the performance, scalability and maintainability of any web application. A well-designed schema ensures that your web application can handle large volumes of data, retrieve information quickly and grow with the increasing needs of your users.  This article explores best practices for designing efficient schemas, focusing on the balance betw</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 22 Oct 2024 08:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/designing-efficient-schemas-for-web-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Basics of Database Design: Normalization, Relationships and ER Diagrams</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/basics-of-database-design-normalization-relationships-and-er-diagrams.html</link>
			<description>Database design is a critical phase in creating a robust, scalable and efficient database system. It involves structuring data in a way that ensures it can be stored, retrieved and managed effectively. Some key concepts fundamental to database design are Normalization, Relationships and Entity-Relationship (ER) Diagrams.  Let&amp;#39;s explore these concepts in detail.  1. Normalization  Normalization</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 12:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/basics-of-database-design-normalization-relationships-and-er-diagrams.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Barometer, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/barometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a homemade barometer is a great science experiment for children to understand how atmospheric pressure is measured and how it changes with weather conditions. A barometer measures air pressure, which can indicate weather changes such as approaching storms or fair weather.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple guide to building a basic barometer using easily available materials:  Materials Needed:   Glas</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 09:51:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/barometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding the SOLID Principles in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</link>
			<description>The SOLID principles are a set of five fundamental design principles in object-oriented programming aimed at improving software design, making it more understandable, flexible and maintainable. These principles are especially relevant for developers working with PHP and similar languages.  Let&amp;#39;s dive into each principle, exploring its meaning and how it can be applied effectively in PHP.  1. S</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to PHP 8 and Key Differences from PHP 7</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-php--and-key-differences-from-php-.html</link>
			<description>PHP 8, released on November 26, 2020, introduces significant improvements and new features that enhance performance, syntax and overall developer experience. This version emphasizes performance optimizations, new language features and better error handling, streamlining the development process and providing developers with more tools to write clean, efficient code.  Key Differences Between PHP 8 a</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 11:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-php--and-key-differences-from-php-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Anemometer, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/anemometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a simple anemometer is a fun and educational science experiment that allows children to measure the wind speed and understand how wind speed is quantified. By defination, an anemometer is a device that measures wind velocity by counting number of times its blades spin in a given time period.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step process for creating a basic anemometer using everyday materials:  Mate</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 07:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/anemometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rainforest in a Jar, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainforest-in-a-jar-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a &amp;quot;Rainforest in a Jar&amp;quot; is a fun science project that helps kids learn about the water cycle and how rainforests work. This mini ecosystem shows how water evaporates, condenses and rains, just like in nature.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple guide to make your own rainforest in a jar:  Materials Needed:   Clear Glass Jar or Large Bowl: This will hold your mini rainforest. Plastic Wrap: To</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainforest-in-a-jar-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cloud in a Bottle, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cloud-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a cloud in a bottle is a fantastic and visually engaging science experiment that demonstrates the basic principles of cloud formation. This simple experiment uses everyday materials to mimic the process of cloud formation in a controlled environment.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to performing the &amp;ldquo;Cloud in a Bottle&amp;rdquo; experiment:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Bottle: A clea</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 08:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cloud-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mini Wind Turbine, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mini-wind-turbine-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a mini wind turbine is a great science experiment for children that demonstrates the principles of wind energy and how it can be converted into electricity.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to creating a simple mini wind turbine using easily available materials:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Bottle: For the turbine&amp;#39;s body. Cardboard or Plastic Sheets: For the turbine blades. Wooden D</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 20:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mini-wind-turbine-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>