<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Sci-Tech - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sci-tech.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>API Docs, Drupal contributed module for your Developer Portal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/api-docs-drupal-contributed-module-for-your-developer-portal.html</link>
			<description>This module will provide API Docs to your Developer Portal, It is powered by Drupal content type, custom field formatters &amp;amp; views.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to help you to download, enable, configure and use the module for your developer portal.  Download &amp;amp; Enable the Module:   Visit the Drupal.org website and navigate to the API Docs module&amp;#39;s page that you want to download, her</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/api-docs-drupal-contributed-module-for-your-developer-portal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Hoop and straw airplane, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hoop-and-straw-airplane-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Hoop and Straw Aeroplane - Exploring Aerodynamics Experiment  Objective: To build and test a hoop and straw aeroplane, investigating the principles of aerodynamics and flight.  Materials:   Drinking straw Lightweight paper (such as construction paper or printer paper) Scissors Tape Hoop or circular object (e.g., a plastic lid, a small hoop made from a pipe cleaner) Optional: Decorative mate</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 10:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hoop-and-straw-airplane-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leaf breathing, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-breathing-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Leaf Breathing - Investigating Transpiration Experiment  Objective: To explore the process of transpiration in plants by observing &amp;quot;leaf breathing&amp;quot; through the movement of water in a plant stem.  Materials:   Freshly cut leafy plant stem (e.g., a leafy branch from a tree or a herbaceous plant) Clear glass or container Water Food coloring (optional) Optional: Plastic wrap or transp</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 18:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-breathing-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Marshmallow catapult, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marshmallow-catapult-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Marshmallow Catapult - Exploring Projectile Motion Experiment  Objective: To build and test a marshmallow catapult, exploring principles of force, motion, and projectile trajectory.  Materials:   Popsicle sticks or craft sticks Rubber bands Plastic spoon Small marshmallows or soft projectiles Tape Optional: Decorative materials (markers, stickers) for customization   Procedure:   Begin by d</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/marshmallow-catapult-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Sticky ice, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sticky-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Sticky Ice - Exploring Surface Tension Experiment  Objective: To investigate surface tension by creating &amp;quot;sticky&amp;quot; ice cubes that can cling to various surfaces.  Materials:   Ice cube tray Water Salt String or thread Various surfaces to test (e.g., plastic, glass, metal, fabric) Optional: Food coloring for visual effect   Procedure:   Fill the ice cube tray with water, leaving some</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sticky-ice-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Paper bridge, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/paper-bridge-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Paper Bridge - Engineering and Structural Strength Experiment  Objective: To design and build a paper bridge that can support the weight of objects and explore the concept of structural strength.  Materials:   Sheets of paper (construction paper or printer paper) Scissors Rulers Books or other small objects to serve as weights Optional: Tape or glue (to reinforce the bridge)   Procedure:   </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 08:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/paper-bridge-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Color changing invisible ink, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-changing-invisible-ink-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Color-Changing Invisible Ink - Chemical Reaction Experiment  Objective: To create and reveal color-changing invisible ink using a simple chemical reaction.  Materials:   Lemon juice or white vinegar Water White paper or a blank sheet of paper Cotton swabs or small paintbrushes Heat source (hairdryer or iron) Optional: Food coloring for additional color effects   Procedure:   Create the invi</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/color-changing-invisible-ink-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Make a compass, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/make-a-compass-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Make Your Own Compass - Magnetism Experiment  Objective: To create a simple compass and explore the principles of magnetism.  Materials:   Small, lightweight magnet (e.g., a bar magnet or a refrigerator magnet) Cork or a small piece of Styrofoam Small bowl or dish filled with water Sewing needle (must be made of steel, not stainless steel) Optional: Tape or glue (to secure the magnet to the</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 17:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/make-a-compass-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Elephant toothpaste, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/elephant-toothpaste-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Elephant Toothpaste - Chemical Reaction Experiment  Objective: To demonstrate an exothermic chemical reaction by creating a foamy eruption known as &amp;quot;elephant toothpaste.&amp;quot;  Materials:   1/2 cup hydrogen peroxide (6% or higher concentration) Dish soap (liquid) Dry yeast Warm water Empty plastic soda bottle (16-ounce or larger) Funnel Safety goggles Tray or large container (to catch </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/elephant-toothpaste-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Milk bottle xylophone, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/milk-bottle-xylophone-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Milk Bottle Xylophone - Sound and Pitch Experiment  Objective: To explore sound and pitch by creating a milk bottle xylophone.  Materials:   Empty glass milk bottles (varying sizes) Water Wooden sticks or metal spoons (for striking the bottles) Optional: Food coloring or colored tape (for visual effect)   Procedure:   Gather a set of empty glass milk bottles. You can use bottles of differen</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/milk-bottle-xylophone-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to improve drupal website performance</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-drupal-website-performance.html</link>
			<description>Improving the performance of a Drupal website involves optimizing various aspects of its configuration and content. Here are some tips to enhance the performance of your Drupal website:   Enable Caching: Enable Drupal&amp;#39;s built-in caching mechanisms to store pre-generated content and reduce the need for repeated processing. Go to Configuration &amp;gt; Performance and enable caching options like pag</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 17:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-drupal-website-performance.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Floating fish, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Floating Fish - Density and Buoyancy Experiment  Objective: To explore the concepts of density and buoyancy by creating a floating fish.  Materials:   Clay or playdough Plasticine or modeling clay Plastic toy fish or small plastic object A basin, tub, or container filled with water   Procedure:   Start by shaping the plasticine or modeling clay into a small ball or disc shape. This will ser</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 07:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/floating-fish-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Craft stick chain reaction, kids science experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/craft-stick-chain-reaction-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Craft Stick Chain Reaction - Potential and Kinetic Energy Experiment  Objective: To explore potential and kinetic energy by creating a chain reaction using craft sticks.  Materials:   Craft sticks (popsicle sticks) Small binder clips or clothespins Optional: Decorative materials (markers, stickers, paint) for customization A wide, flat surface for the experiment (e.g., table, floor)   Proce</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 16:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/craft-stick-chain-reaction-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Grow an avocado tree, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-an-avocado-tree-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Title: Grow an Avocado Tree - Seed Germination Experiment  Objective: To explore the process of seed germination and observe the growth of an avocado tree.  Materials:   An avocado pit (seed) Toothpicks Glass or jar Water Optional: Notebook or journal for recording observations and measurements   Procedure:   Carefully remove the pit (seed) from a ripe avocado. Rinse off any remaining fruit flesh </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 18:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/grow-an-avocado-tree-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to build the engaging digital experience via Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-build-the-engaging-digital-experience-via-drupal.html</link>
			<description>Building an engaging digital experience using Drupal involves combining effective design, user-friendly features, and content that resonates with your audience. Here are some tips to help you create an engaging digital experience using Drupal:   Define Your Target Audience: Understand your target audience and their needs, preferences, and goals. Tailor your digital experience to meet their expecta</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-build-the-engaging-digital-experience-via-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to make your content more Accessible with plain language</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-your-content-more-accessible-with-plain-language.html</link>
			<description>Making your content more accessible with plain language is a valuable practice that ensures your information is easily understood by a wide range of readers. Here are some tips to make your content more accessible and reader-friendly:   Use Clear and Simple Language: Use plain, straightforward language that is easy to understand. Avoid jargon, technical terms, and overly complex vocabulary. Write </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-your-content-more-accessible-with-plain-language.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Watch the Water Rise, Kids Science Experiment</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/watch-the-water-rise-kids-science-experiment.html</link>
			<description>Title: Watch the Water Rise - Absorption Experiment  Objective: To demonstrate the concept of absorption and observe how different materials absorb water.  Materials:   Clear cups or containers Water Various absorbent materials (e.g., paper towels, sponges, cotton balls, fabric scraps, tissue paper) Optional: Food coloring, markers, or colored paper for visual effect   Procedure:   Set up a worksp</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/watch-the-water-rise-kids-science-experiment.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is Drupal the Best Choice for Non-Profit Websites?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-the-best-choice-for-non-profit-websites.html</link>
			<description>Drupal is often considered a great choice for non-profit websites due to several key factors that align with the unique needs and goals of non-profit organizations. Here are some reasons why Drupal is a popular choice for non-profit websites:   Cost-Effectiveness: Drupal is an open-source platform, which means it is free to use and distribute. This can be particularly advantageous for non-profit o</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 11:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-the-best-choice-for-non-profit-websites.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Amplify a Smartphone, Science Experiment for Kids</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/amplify-a-smartphone-science-experiment-for-kids.html</link>
			<description>Amplifying the sound of a smartphone can indeed be turned into a science experiment, allowing kids to explore the principles of acoustics and sound amplification. Here&amp;#39;s a simple science experiment idea:  Title: Investigating Sound Amplification with Everyday Materials  Objective: To explore different materials and their effects on amplifying the sound of a smartphone.  Materials:   Smartphone</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/amplify-a-smartphone-science-experiment-for-kids.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a Mini Baking Soda Rocket?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-mini-baking-soda-rocket.html</link>
			<description>Creating a mini baking soda rocket can be a fun and educational experiment. Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide to making one:  Materials you will need:   A film canister with a tight-fitting lid Baking soda (sodium bicarbonate) Vinegar Tissue or toilet paper Safety goggles (optional but recommended for eye protection)                      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});        Instructio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-mini-baking-soda-rocket.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Security Checklist for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-checklist-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>Securing your Drupal website is crucial to protect your data, users, and overall website integrity. Here&amp;#39;s a security checklist for a Drupal website:   Keep Drupal Core and Modules Up to Date: Regularly update Drupal core and contributed modules to ensure you have the latest security patches. Enable update notifications to stay informed about available updates. Use Strong and Unique Passwords:</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-checklist-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is Drupal Chosen by Large Organizations?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-chosen-by-large-organizations.html</link>
			<description>Drupal is often chosen by large organizations for several reasons. Here are some key factors that make Drupal a popular choice:   Scalability: Drupal is highly scalable, allowing organizations to handle large amounts of content, traffic, and user interactions. Its flexible architecture and robust performance capabilities enable it to accommodate the complex needs of large-scale websites and applic</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-chosen-by-large-organizations.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal LMS Features for Your Education Business</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re running an education business and considering Drupal as the platform for your Learning Management System (LMS), there are several features and capabilities you should look for to ensure a robust and effective solution.  Here are some key Drupal LMS features to consider:   Course Management: A Drupal LMS should provide comprehensive course management capabilities. This includes the ab</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leveraging Content Grouping for Personalized Digital Experiences</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</link>
			<description>Content grouping is a powerful technique that can be leveraged to create personalized digital experiences for users. By grouping content based on specific criteria, such as user preferences, demographics, or behavior, you can deliver targeted and relevant content to individual users. Here are some ways to utilize content grouping for personalized digital experiences:   User Segmentation: Segment y</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What to know before you choose a Drupal Hosting Platform?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-before-you-choose-drupal-hosting-platform.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see a few important notes which will be helpful for people who are looking out to host their Drupal application. When selecting a hosting platform for your Drupal website, there are several key factors to consider.  Here are some important things to know before making a decision:   Compatibility with Drupal: Ensure that the hosting platform is compatible with Drupal&amp;#3</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-before-you-choose-drupal-hosting-platform.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>node_get_recent() is deprecated in Drupal 10.1.x</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/node-get-recent-is-deprecated-in-drupal-ten.html</link>
			<description>node_get_recent() is unused in core and is now deprecated, developers can use views or EntityQuery to get the nodes which are recently modified or added.  Earlier drupal developers used to use the function&amp;nbsp;node_get_recent() to get the recently changed nodes like seen in below example  $latest_updated_nodes = node_get_recent(10);  Now from Drupal 10.1.x onwards, developers need to use entity q</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/node-get-recent-is-deprecated-in-drupal-ten.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best way to add additional estimates upon the original estimate for a Story in a Sprint?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-way-to-add-additional-estimates-upon-the-original-estimate-for-a-story-in-a-sprint.html</link>
			<description>When additional work or requirements are identified for a Story during a Sprint, it is important to ensure that the impact on the Sprint&amp;#39;s scope and timeline is understood and communicated to the team and stakeholders. Here are some steps that can be followed to add additional estimates to a Story in a Sprint:   Review the original estimate: First, review the original estimate for the Story an</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-way-to-add-additional-estimates-upon-the-original-estimate-for-a-story-in-a-sprint.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to generate good revenue from blogging websites?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-generate-good-revenue-from-blogging-websites.html</link>
			<description>To maximize revenue from your blog, it&amp;#39;s important to focus on creating high-quality content, engaging with your audience, and promoting your blog through social media and other marketing channels.  There are several ways to generate revenue from a blogging website:   Advertising: Displaying ads on your blog is one of the most common ways to generate revenue. You can use ad networks like Googl</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-generate-good-revenue-from-blogging-websites.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to improve a website's SEO score and make it searchable on Search Engines like Google?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-websites-seo-score-and-make-it-searchable-on-search-engines-like-google.html</link>
			<description>It is very important for the business to have their web sites to be popular on the search engines and the process of improving the quality and quantity of website traffic to a website or a web page from search engines is search engine optimization.  In this article, we are going to see how one can improve their website&amp;rsquo;s SEO score and make the website popular on search engines.  Improving yo</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-websites-seo-score-and-make-it-searchable-on-search-engines-like-google.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to secure the Passwords of Users in Web Applications?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-secure-the-passwords-of-users-in-web-applications.html</link>
			<description>Generally while working with Web applications, one of the important data related to Users is their passwords, and keeping them secured is one of the important jobs of the Web application.  In this article we gonna see a brief how a developer or admin can make sure the passwords are secure on the web application.  Here are some best practices to secure passwords in web applications:   Use Strong Pa</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-secure-the-passwords-of-users-in-web-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Fix Colima connection refused error: failed to get Info from .lima/colima/ha.sock on Mac</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-colima-connection-refused-error-failed-to-get-info-from-lima-colima-ha-sock-on-mac.html</link>
			<description>This article is about fixing only a single error which you see with Colima on Mac machines. This might be a simple &amp;amp; specific issue, but people who are facing this issue will really feel grateful with the solution provided.  While you are running Colima on your mac machines, generally you get into such issue, when you power off or shut down your mac, without stopping the colima service (and de</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-colima-connection-refused-error-failed-to-get-info-from-lima-colima-ha-sock-on-mac.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Checklist for building an Eco-Friendly Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</link>
			<description>To build a home, which makes low-impact environmentally. And built using materials &amp;amp; technology that lowers its energy needs in future. And also make sure built home is reliable for few decades with minimal energy spent on it.  To do this, you have to consider Energy? what Sustainable materials to be used? how it impacts on our health? And what is costs  Before getting into the details of each</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Multisite Local environment setup with DDEV and Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-ddev-and-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how we can set up a multisite environment with ddev on the local machine. Assuming people are aware of configuring the drupal multiple site from the drupal side of configurations.  As we all know ddev is an open source tool for running local PHP development environments in minutes, which makes developer life easier during the local environment setup process, her</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-ddev-and-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Secure your Web Application's Reset Password flow</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-your-applications-reset-password-flow.html</link>
			<description>Generally any application framework provides users to have a flow to reset the passwords by default, It is more like, use clicking on the Reset Password link and redirects to a page where he will asked for email, and reset link sent to users email, so that user can reset the password on their own.  This is a default or general flow that any application framework provides, but developers or archite</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-your-applications-reset-password-flow.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How does Captcha know that I'm not a Robot?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-captcha-know-that-iam-not-robot.html</link>
			<description>Almost all the developers working on web applications would have come across captcha or re-captcha.  And developers might have also used them on the web pages before authentication of users on web applications or before showing specific content to users.  As developers, we might have got a thought like how will this work behind the scenes, but in most of the cases, we developers would have ignored</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-captcha-know-that-iam-not-robot.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Colima, similar tool like Docker Desktop, for Drupal Development</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</link>
			<description>Colima is a project that is easy to use and fully open source, and it helps in running docker containers on Linux OS and MacOs machines.  We know Docker Desktop is no more a complete open source, if you are not using it personally. So now Colima is a tool which does work similar to Docker Desktop and In this article we are going to see how it works alone or along with Docker Desktop on your Linux </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal 10</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal-ten.html</link>
			<description>We developers always choose to have some tools or setup, which makes our lives easier during the development process whether it might be a local environment or higher environments. Not only will lives be easier with such a setup, even the productivity of the individual or team will be increased. And today we are gonna see how Lando will help the drupal developer or drupal development much quicker </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 12:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal-ten.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal 10 is coming in a few days!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-ten-is-coming-in-a-few-days.html</link>
			<description>Drupal 10 is planned to be released in December 2022. Drupal 10 will be straightforward upgrades like Drupal 8 to 9. Upgrade processes used are more or less similar. Mostly you need to keep your current site up to date with the latest drupal core and contributed projects.  What is new in Drupal 10?  Drupal 10 is a refined version of Drupal 9 with the certain features   Claro administration theme i</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-ten-is-coming-in-a-few-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Project vs Product - Plan and Delivery, Agile Characteristics</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/project-vs-product-plan-and-delivery-agile-characteristics.html</link>
			<description>In the Service Industry, a Technical Lead or Technical Architect or Delivery Manager, one is always looking at the work, either as a Project or a Product, but I say, one should look at it as both, because work would be a Project for us but work would be a Product for the clients.  While working on Agile basis, being at the leading positions one will be seeing the scope of work, then prepare the ba</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/project-vs-product-plan-and-delivery-agile-characteristics.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of Constraints (Validations) on Media Entities in Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-constraints-validations-on-media-entities-in-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how drupal developers can use the Drupal Constraints to Validate the Media entities.  Basically Drupal provides Constraints to do the Validations on the Entities, where Drupal uses the Symfony&amp;rsquo;s validator and extends with Symfony&amp;rsquo;s Typed Data API for validating specific Entity field definitions.  These constraint validators can be used in different w</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-constraints-validations-on-media-entities-in-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>INS Vikrant Delivered to Indian Navy, First Indigenous Aircraft Carrier by India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</link>
			<description>INS Vikrant which is also known as Indigenous Aircraft Carrier 1 (IAC-1). It is the first aircraft carrier to be built in India. This is an Aircraft Carrier constructed by the Cochin Shipyard Limited (CSL) for the Indian Navy.  The name Vikrant means courageous in Sanskrit. The motto of the ship is Jayema Saṁ Yudhi Sprdhah, which means I defeat those who fight against me.  Brief of the backgroun</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of Local Php Security Checker for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how the Local PHP Security Checker library will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated security review. Here comes the Local PHP Security Checker library, which checks for any known vulnerabilities in the package dependencies.  Th</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Complete Guide to Setup and Usage Solar Panels at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Going green is the best of the environment and if you are planning to go green, then we all know Sun is the non-renewable energy and we could use this energy for people&amp;#39;s survival. We have a few articles at PeoplesBLOG related to the Environment and going green, have a check of them.  Using the Electricity from Solar energy is one of the best combinations, because there is not much waste out o</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cooking Food with Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
			<description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Read Data to Paragraph Template in Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/read-data-to-paragraph-template-in-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how to read the dynamic data of the node or entity or field values to the template file, which are specific to the paragraph template.  Generally while the Paragraph module is used, default template suggestions given by the paragraph module or the template suggestions provided by the hooks are used and further template design is done. Here&amp;rsquo;s the article wh</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/read-data-to-paragraph-template-in-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Drupal Paragraphs?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</link>
			<description>Paragraphs can be used as a way for Content Creation in Drupal. It actually allows the site builders to do their stuff a bit cleanly and for the end users this will be pretty easy to manage the content, meaning people get more control on the Editing side.  Paragraphs is one of the&amp;nbsp; popular modules in Drupal, for handling content. It is more or less very similar to the fields and will provide </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PhpStan on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development and code review process. We have a similar helpful article related to Phpcs, have a check of this.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here come</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to charge a Mobile phone with Solar power?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see what all options we have to charge a mobile phone with Solar power.  If you are going on treks which are primarily overnight or a few days of trek in some isolated place. In such cases obviously we won&amp;rsquo;t get any electrical power, In such cases for people Solar energy would be an alternative option to keep your device charged.  And let&amp;rsquo;s see what all</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Twig Templates in Drupal?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how a developer can work with Twig templates, and how to override templates (if needed) and create template suggestions with hooks, so that templates could be easily managed.  Basically drupal allows people to override the existing twig templates, so that people can fully have control on the html generated via the custom theme.  First thing, we need to make sur</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Quick reference of Code Reviews for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how your Drupal team can do code reviews and available tools or libraries which help people in the team to do the code reviews seamlessly.  It&amp;rsquo;s pretty important to follow a few guidelines as well, so that all people or developers in the team are on the same page.  Firstly, for the code reviews to be at their best, the committed code should be more organis</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>