<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Sci-Tech - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sci-tech.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Security Checklist for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-checklist-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>Securing your Drupal website is crucial to protect your data, users, and overall website integrity. Here&amp;#39;s a security checklist for a Drupal website:   Keep Drupal Core and Modules Up to Date: Regularly update Drupal core and contributed modules to ensure you have the latest security patches. Enable update notifications to stay informed about available updates. Use Strong and Unique Passwords:</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-checklist-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is Drupal Chosen by Large Organizations?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-chosen-by-large-organizations.html</link>
			<description>Drupal is often chosen by large organizations for several reasons. Here are some key factors that make Drupal a popular choice:   Scalability: Drupal is highly scalable, allowing organizations to handle large amounts of content, traffic, and user interactions. Its flexible architecture and robust performance capabilities enable it to accommodate the complex needs of large-scale websites and applic</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-chosen-by-large-organizations.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal LMS Features for Your Education Business</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re running an education business and considering Drupal as the platform for your Learning Management System (LMS), there are several features and capabilities you should look for to ensure a robust and effective solution.  Here are some key Drupal LMS features to consider:   Course Management: A Drupal LMS should provide comprehensive course management capabilities. This includes the ab</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leveraging Content Grouping for Personalized Digital Experiences</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</link>
			<description>Content grouping is a powerful technique that can be leveraged to create personalized digital experiences for users. By grouping content based on specific criteria, such as user preferences, demographics, or behavior, you can deliver targeted and relevant content to individual users. Here are some ways to utilize content grouping for personalized digital experiences:   User Segmentation: Segment y</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What to know before you choose a Drupal Hosting Platform?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-before-you-choose-drupal-hosting-platform.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see a few important notes which will be helpful for people who are looking out to host their Drupal application. When selecting a hosting platform for your Drupal website, there are several key factors to consider.  Here are some important things to know before making a decision:   Compatibility with Drupal: Ensure that the hosting platform is compatible with Drupal&amp;#3</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2023 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-before-you-choose-drupal-hosting-platform.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>node_get_recent() is deprecated in Drupal 10.1.x</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/node-get-recent-is-deprecated-in-drupal-ten.html</link>
			<description>node_get_recent() is unused in core and is now deprecated, developers can use views or EntityQuery to get the nodes which are recently modified or added.  Earlier drupal developers used to use the function&amp;nbsp;node_get_recent() to get the recently changed nodes like seen in below example  $latest_updated_nodes = node_get_recent(10);  Now from Drupal 10.1.x onwards, developers need to use entity q</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 09 May 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/node-get-recent-is-deprecated-in-drupal-ten.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best way to add additional estimates upon the original estimate for a Story in a Sprint?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-way-to-add-additional-estimates-upon-the-original-estimate-for-a-story-in-a-sprint.html</link>
			<description>When additional work or requirements are identified for a Story during a Sprint, it is important to ensure that the impact on the Sprint&amp;#39;s scope and timeline is understood and communicated to the team and stakeholders. Here are some steps that can be followed to add additional estimates to a Story in a Sprint:   Review the original estimate: First, review the original estimate for the Story an</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 15:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-way-to-add-additional-estimates-upon-the-original-estimate-for-a-story-in-a-sprint.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to generate good revenue from blogging websites?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-generate-good-revenue-from-blogging-websites.html</link>
			<description>To maximize revenue from your blog, it&amp;#39;s important to focus on creating high-quality content, engaging with your audience, and promoting your blog through social media and other marketing channels.  There are several ways to generate revenue from a blogging website:   Advertising: Displaying ads on your blog is one of the most common ways to generate revenue. You can use ad networks like Googl</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 07 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-generate-good-revenue-from-blogging-websites.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to improve a website's SEO score and make it searchable on Search Engines like Google?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-websites-seo-score-and-make-it-searchable-on-search-engines-like-google.html</link>
			<description>It is very important for the business to have their web sites to be popular on the search engines and the process of improving the quality and quantity of website traffic to a website or a web page from search engines is search engine optimization.  In this article, we are going to see how one can improve their website&amp;rsquo;s SEO score and make the website popular on search engines.  Improving yo</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-websites-seo-score-and-make-it-searchable-on-search-engines-like-google.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to secure the Passwords of Users in Web Applications?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-secure-the-passwords-of-users-in-web-applications.html</link>
			<description>Generally while working with Web applications, one of the important data related to Users is their passwords, and keeping them secured is one of the important jobs of the Web application.  In this article we gonna see a brief how a developer or admin can make sure the passwords are secure on the web application.  Here are some best practices to secure passwords in web applications:   Use Strong Pa</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-secure-the-passwords-of-users-in-web-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Fix Colima connection refused error: failed to get Info from .lima/colima/ha.sock on Mac</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-colima-connection-refused-error-failed-to-get-info-from-lima-colima-ha-sock-on-mac.html</link>
			<description>This article is about fixing only a single error which you see with Colima on Mac machines. This might be a simple &amp;amp; specific issue, but people who are facing this issue will really feel grateful with the solution provided.  While you are running Colima on your mac machines, generally you get into such issue, when you power off or shut down your mac, without stopping the colima service (and de</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-colima-connection-refused-error-failed-to-get-info-from-lima-colima-ha-sock-on-mac.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Checklist for building an Eco-Friendly Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</link>
			<description>To build a home, which makes low-impact environmentally. And built using materials &amp;amp; technology that lowers its energy needs in future. And also make sure built home is reliable for few decades with minimal energy spent on it.  To do this, you have to consider Energy? what Sustainable materials to be used? how it impacts on our health? And what is costs  Before getting into the details of each</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/checklist-for-building-an-eco-friendly-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Multisite Local environment setup with DDEV and Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-ddev-and-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how we can set up a multisite environment with ddev on the local machine. Assuming people are aware of configuring the drupal multiple site from the drupal side of configurations.  As we all know ddev is an open source tool for running local PHP development environments in minutes, which makes developer life easier during the local environment setup process, her</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-ddev-and-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Secure your Web Application's Reset Password flow</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-your-applications-reset-password-flow.html</link>
			<description>Generally any application framework provides users to have a flow to reset the passwords by default, It is more like, use clicking on the Reset Password link and redirects to a page where he will asked for email, and reset link sent to users email, so that user can reset the password on their own.  This is a default or general flow that any application framework provides, but developers or archite</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 22 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/secure-your-applications-reset-password-flow.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How does Captcha know that I'm not a Robot?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-captcha-know-that-iam-not-robot.html</link>
			<description>Almost all the developers working on web applications would have come across captcha or re-captcha.  And developers might have also used them on the web pages before authentication of users on web applications or before showing specific content to users.  As developers, we might have got a thought like how will this work behind the scenes, but in most of the cases, we developers would have ignored</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Jan 2023 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-does-captcha-know-that-iam-not-robot.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Colima, similar tool like Docker Desktop, for Drupal Development</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</link>
			<description>Colima is a project that is easy to use and fully open source, and it helps in running docker containers on Linux OS and MacOs machines.  We know Docker Desktop is no more a complete open source, if you are not using it personally. So now Colima is a tool which does work similar to Docker Desktop and In this article we are going to see how it works alone or along with Docker Desktop on your Linux </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal 10</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal-ten.html</link>
			<description>We developers always choose to have some tools or setup, which makes our lives easier during the development process whether it might be a local environment or higher environments. Not only will lives be easier with such a setup, even the productivity of the individual or team will be increased. And today we are gonna see how Lando will help the drupal developer or drupal development much quicker </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 18 Dec 2022 12:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal-ten.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal 10 is coming in a few days!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-ten-is-coming-in-a-few-days.html</link>
			<description>Drupal 10 is planned to be released in December 2022. Drupal 10 will be straightforward upgrades like Drupal 8 to 9. Upgrade processes used are more or less similar. Mostly you need to keep your current site up to date with the latest drupal core and contributed projects.  What is new in Drupal 10?  Drupal 10 is a refined version of Drupal 9 with the certain features   Claro administration theme i</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 08 Dec 2022 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-ten-is-coming-in-a-few-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Project vs Product - Plan and Delivery, Agile Characteristics</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/project-vs-product-plan-and-delivery-agile-characteristics.html</link>
			<description>In the Service Industry, a Technical Lead or Technical Architect or Delivery Manager, one is always looking at the work, either as a Project or a Product, but I say, one should look at it as both, because work would be a Project for us but work would be a Product for the clients.  While working on Agile basis, being at the leading positions one will be seeing the scope of work, then prepare the ba</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/project-vs-product-plan-and-delivery-agile-characteristics.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of Constraints (Validations) on Media Entities in Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-constraints-validations-on-media-entities-in-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how drupal developers can use the Drupal Constraints to Validate the Media entities.  Basically Drupal provides Constraints to do the Validations on the Entities, where Drupal uses the Symfony&amp;rsquo;s validator and extends with Symfony&amp;rsquo;s Typed Data API for validating specific Entity field definitions.  These constraint validators can be used in different w</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-constraints-validations-on-media-entities-in-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>INS Vikrant Delivered to Indian Navy, First Indigenous Aircraft Carrier by India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</link>
			<description>INS Vikrant which is also known as Indigenous Aircraft Carrier 1 (IAC-1). It is the first aircraft carrier to be built in India. This is an Aircraft Carrier constructed by the Cochin Shipyard Limited (CSL) for the Indian Navy.  The name Vikrant means courageous in Sanskrit. The motto of the ship is Jayema Saṁ Yudhi Sprdhah, which means I defeat those who fight against me.  Brief of the backgroun</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ins-vikrant-delivered-to-indian-navy-first-indigenous-aircraft-carrier-by-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of Local Php Security Checker for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how the Local PHP Security Checker library will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated security review. Here comes the Local PHP Security Checker library, which checks for any known vulnerabilities in the package dependencies.  Th</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-local-php-security-checker-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Complete Guide to Setup and Usage Solar Panels at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Going green is the best of the environment and if you are planning to go green, then we all know Sun is the non-renewable energy and we could use this energy for people&amp;#39;s survival. We have a few articles at PeoplesBLOG related to the Environment and going green, have a check of them.  Using the Electricity from Solar energy is one of the best combinations, because there is not much waste out o</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cooking Food with Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
			<description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Read Data to Paragraph Template in Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/read-data-to-paragraph-template-in-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how to read the dynamic data of the node or entity or field values to the template file, which are specific to the paragraph template.  Generally while the Paragraph module is used, default template suggestions given by the paragraph module or the template suggestions provided by the hooks are used and further template design is done. Here&amp;rsquo;s the article wh</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/read-data-to-paragraph-template-in-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Drupal Paragraphs?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</link>
			<description>Paragraphs can be used as a way for Content Creation in Drupal. It actually allows the site builders to do their stuff a bit cleanly and for the end users this will be pretty easy to manage the content, meaning people get more control on the Editing side.  Paragraphs is one of the&amp;nbsp; popular modules in Drupal, for handling content. It is more or less very similar to the fields and will provide </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-drupal-paragraphs.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PhpStan on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development and code review process. We have a similar helpful article related to Phpcs, have a check of this.  To make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here come</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpstan-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to charge a Mobile phone with Solar power?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see what all options we have to charge a mobile phone with Solar power.  If you are going on treks which are primarily overnight or a few days of trek in some isolated place. In such cases obviously we won&amp;rsquo;t get any electrical power, In such cases for people Solar energy would be an alternative option to keep your device charged.  And let&amp;rsquo;s see what all</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to work with Twig Templates in Drupal?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how a developer can work with Twig templates, and how to override templates (if needed) and create template suggestions with hooks, so that templates could be easily managed.  Basically drupal allows people to override the existing twig templates, so that people can fully have control on the html generated via the custom theme.  First thing, we need to make sur</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Quick reference of Code Reviews for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how your Drupal team can do code reviews and available tools or libraries which help people in the team to do the code reviews seamlessly.  It&amp;rsquo;s pretty important to follow a few guidelines as well, so that all people or developers in the team are on the same page.  Firstly, for the code reviews to be at their best, the committed code should be more organis</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PHPCS on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  And to make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here comes the PHP codesniffer and Drupal coder module.  If you are maintaini</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Store Secrets Securely on Pantheon for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-secrets-securely-on-pantheon-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how people can store access keys and tokens securely, in the case of your drupal application that is managed on pantheon.  Generally, all the Access keys or Tokens or any Secret third party auth information should not be stored in the database or within the project web root, Its safe to store it encrypted and within a file, and keep the file outside of the proj</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-secrets-securely-on-pantheon-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Configuration management via Quicksilver on Pantheon</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuration-management-via-quicksilver-on-pantheon.html</link>
			<description>As we saw in the earlier article, like how we manage the configuration across the environments.  In this article we are going to see how Drupal configurations can be deployed or imported across the environments with the help of Quicksilver which hooks into platform workflows to automate your Pantheon WebOps workflow across the environments.  In the pantheon environment&amp;rsquo;s drupal code base, yo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuration-management-via-quicksilver-on-pantheon.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal Configuration management (Local, Dev, Test and Live)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-configuration-management-local-dev-test-and-live.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how Drupal serves configurations across the environments, which can be well maintained with help of some contributed modules and version control.  Drupal 8 onwards configuration has been saved in the yml files in a consistent manner, which includes all the enabled modules, all the content types, vocabularies, fields &amp;amp; views.  Making the configurations direct</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-configuration-management-local-dev-test-and-live.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Improve Drupal Search with Solr, Locally configured via Lando</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/improve-drupal-search-with-solr-locally-configured-via-lando.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn how Drupal search can be improved with Solr which provides great performance, and is suitable even for use on large commercial websites. And along with this using the search_api &amp; search_api_solr modules, helps to configure the Facets &amp; Multilingual content can be handled in an improved manner. And let's see how we can configure this locally with the help of </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/improve-drupal-search-with-solr-locally-configured-via-lando.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>When to use hook_update_N &amp; hook_post_update_NAME?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-to-use-hook_update_n-and-hook_post_update_name.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn when to use hook_update_N and hook_post_update_NAME. In general, I was using hook_update_N for any database-related changes or with any configuration additions or updates. And I was using hook_post_update_NAME for any content creation or updating or for the creation or updating any taxonomy terms etc, sometimes for clearing site caches as well. But, let’s h</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-to-use-hook_update_n-and-hook_post_update_name.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Improvements for Editor Experience in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/improvements-for-editor-experience-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn what Drupal offers for text editors or content managers as a content management framework within Drupal Core &amp; Contributed modules. Earlier versions of Drupal have several useful features to help content editors to manage their content on a daily basis. And in the newer versions of Drupal (from when Symfony was introduced), there are a few more improvements i</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/improvements-for-editor-experience-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Core</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-drupal-offers-as-responsive-web-design-within-core.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we gonna see What Drupal offers as Responsive Web Design within Drupal Core for developers. While Drupal 8 was out and it had a buzz of being responsive, mobile friendly. And yes, the Internet is on the verge of being dominated by smartphones &amp; Drupal needs to be prepared.Mobile friendly will also mean the content is first. From a big screen to a little screen, elements would look</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-drupal-offers-as-responsive-web-design-within-core.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Know why Symfony framework was picked by Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/know-why-symfony-framework-was-picked-by-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we gonna see why Symfony was picked for Drupal and what it changes for developers. As we all know PHP evolved rapidly in the past years, and unfortunately, Drupal adjustment to this development was not satisfying, especially in the case of software engineering patterns adoption. And that is one of the reasons why Drupal Developers had to come up with creative ways to deal with suc</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/know-why-symfony-framework-was-picked-by-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understand why Twig is replacing PHP Template in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understand-why-twig-is-replacing-php-template-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>A completely new template engine is introduced in Drupal. The templating system in all previous versions of Drupal is using theme_* functions and PHP-based *.tpl.php files. Now, this has been completely replaced in Drupal 8. Instead of using theme functions and theme template files, Drupal is now using the Twig templating system.
                            Twig is a PHP-based compiled templating </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understand-why-twig-is-replacing-php-template-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>In layman's terms, Services &amp; Dependency Injection in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/in-laymans-terms-services-and-dependency-injection-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>If we look into the basis of Software engineering, Dependency Injection is an approach in which one object get another object that it depends on. And these other objects are called dependencies. And Injection refers to the passing of a dependency (as a service) into the client object that would use it.
                            With Dependency Injection, the class is no longer responsible for in</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/in-laymans-terms-services-and-dependency-injection-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal Cache Clear &amp; Cache Rebuild</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-cache-clear-and-cache-rebuild.html</link>
			<description>In order to render a page via Drupal, Drupal will need to make several database queries and get the data to render. This process of making queries can be reduced by storing the web pages in a cache, which is what Drupal does.
                            And developers during developments may use this cache clear or cache rebuild quite often, like after installing a new module or theme. The site wo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-cache-clear-and-cache-rebuild.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Multisite Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</link>
			<description>As we have seen in the earlier article to setup the Local environment with Lando &amp; Drupal, Now let's see how we set up the multisite with the lando.
                            And hope you are already aware of Drupal Multisite. If not, It is a feature of Drupal that allows you to run multiple Drupal installs off of a common codebase. This allows you to share themes and modules between a collectio</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/multisite-local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Studies estimate long COVID-19 has over two hundred Symptoms</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</link>
			<description>According to a Lancet's journal EClinicalMedicine, In the Coronavirus (Covid-19) patients who are facing prolonged symptoms have reported more than 200 symptoms across 10 organ systems.
                            They have analysed the responses of 3,762 peoples from 56 different countries with confirmed or suspected Covid-19. And the data were collected from September 6, 2020, to November 25, 20</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/studies-estimate-long-covid-has-over-two-hundred-symptoms.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Local environment setup with Lando &amp; Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</link>
			<description>We developers always choose to have some tools or setup, which makes our lives easier during the development process whether it might be a local environment or higher environments. Not only will lives be easier with such a setup, even the productivity of the individual or team will be increased. And today we are gonna see how Lando will help the drupal developer or drupal development much more qui</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/local-environment-setup-with-lando-and-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Fix SSL error 61 in Citrix Web Receiver on Ubuntu</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-ssl-error-in-citrix-web-receiver-on-ubuntu.html</link>
			<description>This article is about fixing only a single error which you see with Citrix Web Receiver on the Ubuntu machines. This might be a simple &amp; specific issue, but people who are facing this issue will really feel grateful with the solution provided.
                                After you install the Citrix web receiver on Ubuntu machine &amp; while you try to connect, in some cases no connection to syste</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fix-ssl-error-in-citrix-web-receiver-on-ubuntu.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why to have a Green Roof or Eco Friendly Roof on a Building</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-to-have-a-green-roof-or-eco-friendly-roof-on-a-building.html</link>
			<description>A roof of a building that is partially or completely covered with vegetation, that is planted over a waterproofing membrane. It may also include additional layers such as a root barrier and drainage and irrigation systems. Rooftop ponds are another form of green roofs which are used to treat greywater.
                                Vegetation, soil, drainage layer, roof barrier and irrigation sy</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-to-have-a-green-roof-or-eco-friendly-roof-on-a-building.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Security Hardening - Nginx Response Headers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-hardening-nginx-response-headers.html</link>
			<description>Now-a-days, web based attacks are one of the most common types of cybercrime, and in most cases, the attacked protocol is the HTTP, while the component that receives the attacks is the web server. Hardening Nginx HTTP headers becomes necessary for reducing any attacks to the web server.
                                And how to harden Nginx response HTTP headers? - HTTP headers are pieces of info</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-hardening-nginx-response-headers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Black Fungus - Detected in Coronavirus Patients</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</link>
			<description>Black fungus is an infection caused by a fungus named mucormycosis. This fungal infection is being reported in a few Corona-affected patients during or post-recovery.
                                People catch mucormycosis when they come in contact with the fungal spores in the environment. It can also be contacted through skin contact through a cut, burn, or any other form of skin trauma.
     </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Leela Vasundhara</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/black-fungus-detected-in-coronavirus-patients.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal 7 to Drupal 8/9 Audits</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal--to-drupalaudits.html</link>
			<description>Migration from Drupal 7 to Drupal 8/9 is more of a re-build than a simple upgrade. We can move the content. users and other configuration with the help of core system, But still their will be a need to re-write custom modules or themes and some times contrib ones as well. By having a list which helps us to Audit any D7 Project to Drupal 8/9 migration would help start quick.
                       </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal--to-drupalaudits.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>