<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Sci-Tech - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sci-tech.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Basics of Database Design: Normalization, Relationships, and ER Diagrams</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/basics-of-database-design-normalization-relationships-and-er-diagrams.html</link>
			<description>Database design is a critical phase in creating a robust, scalable, and efficient database system. It involves structuring data in a way that ensures it can be stored, retrieved, and managed effectively. Some key concepts fundamental to database design are Normalization, Relationships, and Entity-Relationship (ER) Diagrams.  Let&amp;#39;s explore these concepts in detail.  1. Normalization  Normalizat</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Oct 2024 12:26:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/basics-of-database-design-normalization-relationships-and-er-diagrams.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Barometer, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/barometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a homemade barometer is a great science experiment for children to understand how atmospheric pressure is measured and how it changes with weather conditions. A barometer measures air pressure, which can indicate weather changes such as approaching storms or fair weather.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple guide to building a basic barometer using easily available materials:  Materials Needed:   Glas</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 09:51:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/barometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding the SOLID Principles in PHP</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</link>
			<description>The SOLID principles are a set of five fundamental design principles in object-oriented programming aimed at improving software design, making it more understandable, flexible, and maintainable. These principles are especially relevant for developers working with PHP and similar languages.  Let&amp;#39;s dive into each principle, exploring its meaning and how it can be applied effectively in PHP.  1. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 10:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-solid-principles-in-php.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to PHP 8 and Key Differences from PHP 7</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-php--and-key-differences-from-php-.html</link>
			<description>PHP 8, released on November 26, 2020, introduces significant improvements and new features that enhance performance, syntax, and overall developer experience. This version emphasizes performance optimizations, new language features, and better error handling, streamlining the development process and providing developers with more tools to write clean, efficient code.  Key Differences Between PHP 8</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2024 11:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-php--and-key-differences-from-php-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Anemometer, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/anemometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a simple anemometer is a fun and educational science experiment that allows children to measure the wind speed and understand how wind speed is quantified. By defination, an anemometer is a device that measures wind velocity by counting number of times its blades spin in a given time period.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step process for creating a basic anemometer using everyday materials:  Mate</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2024 07:01:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/anemometer-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rainforest in a Jar, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainforest-in-a-jar-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a &amp;quot;Rainforest in a Jar&amp;quot; is a fun science project that helps kids learn about the water cycle and how rainforests work. This mini ecosystem shows how water evaporates, condenses, and rains, just like in nature.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a simple guide to make your own rainforest in a jar:  Materials Needed:   Clear Glass Jar or Large Bowl: This will hold your mini rainforest. Plastic Wrap: T</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Sep 2024 19:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainforest-in-a-jar-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cloud in a Bottle, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cloud-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a cloud in a bottle is a fantastic and visually engaging science experiment that demonstrates the basic principles of cloud formation. This simple experiment uses everyday materials to mimic the process of cloud formation in a controlled environment.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to performing the &amp;ldquo;Cloud in a Bottle&amp;rdquo; experiment:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Bottle: A clea</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 08:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cloud-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mini Wind Turbine, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mini-wind-turbine-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a mini wind turbine is a great science experiment for children that demonstrates the principles of wind energy and how it can be converted into electricity.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to creating a simple mini wind turbine using easily available materials:  Materials Needed:   Plastic Bottle: For the turbine&amp;#39;s body. Cardboard or Plastic Sheets: For the turbine blades. Wooden D</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2024 07:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mini-wind-turbine-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solar Oven Cooking, science experiment for children </title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-oven-cooking-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building and using a DIY solar oven is a fantastic way to explore solar energy and understand the principles of cooking with sunlight. A solar oven harnesses solar energy to heat and cook food, providing a practical demonstration of renewable energy in action.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a step-by-step guide to creating and using a simple solar oven:  Materials Needed:   Cardboard Box: A large, clean cardboard </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 23 Aug 2024 07:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-oven-cooking-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Hydropower Experiment, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hydropower-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple water wheel is an excellent hands-on experiment to understand the principles of hydropower. A waterwheel converts the kinetic energy of flowing water into mechanical energy, which can then be used to perform work or generate electricity.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to building a basic waterwheel to explore the fundamentals of hydropower:  Materials Needed:   Plastic or Cardb</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2024 06:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/hydropower-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Potato Battery, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-potato-battery-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a DIY potato battery is a fascinating and educational experiment that demonstrates the basics of electrochemical cells and how chemical energy can be converted into electrical energy.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to building a potato battery using zinc and copper electrodes:  Materials Needed:   Potatoes: 2-3 medium-sized potatoes (or more if you want to create a battery with higher v</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 11 Aug 2024 10:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/diy-potato-battery-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solar Still Experiment, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-still-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Solar still is a simple yet effective device for purifying water using solar energy. It works on the principle of evaporation and condensation to separate clean water from impurities.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to conducting a solar still experiment to demonstrate the process of water purification:  Materials Needed:   Clear Plastic Sheet: To cover the solar still and capture the evaporated </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 07:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-still-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rheumatoid Arthritis - Symptoms, Causes, Diagnosis, Treatment, Recovery</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rheumatoid-arthritis-symptoms-causes-diagnosis-treatment-recovery.html</link>
			<description>Rheumatoid arthritis (RA) is a chronic inflammatory disorder that primarily affects the joints. It is an autoimmune condition, meaning the immune system mistakenly attacks the body&amp;#39;s own tissues.  Symptoms:   Joint pain and swelling: Commonly affects small joints in the hands, wrists, and feet. Stiffness: Particularly pronounced in the morning or after periods of inactivity. Fatigue: Persisten</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 31 Jul 2024 08:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rheumatoid-arthritis-symptoms-causes-diagnosis-treatment-recovery.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Borax Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/borax-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating Borax slime is a classic and fun science experiment that helps children understand the properties of polymers and cross-linking.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to making Borax slime:  Materials:   White school glue (PVA glue) Borax powder (sodium borate) Water Food coloring (optional) Mixing bowls Measuring cups and spoons Mixing spoon or spatula    Google Ad 1   Procedure:   Prepare th</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 06 Jul 2024 10:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/borax-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Magnetic Slime, science experiment for childrens</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-childrens.html</link>
			<description>Creating magnetic slime is an exciting and educational science experiment that combines chemistry and physics to demonstrate magnetism and polymer properties.  Here&amp;rsquo;s how to make magnetic slime step-by-step:  Materials:   White school glue (PVA glue) Liquid starch Iron oxide powder (can be found online or at some craft stores) Water Strong neodymium magnets Mixing bowl Mixing spoon or spatul</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Jun 2024 12:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-childrens.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Fluffy Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fluffy-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating fluffy slime is a fun and educational science experiment that engages children with hands-on learning about chemistry and the properties of materials.  Here&amp;#39;s how to make fluffy slime step-by-step:  Materials:   White school glue (PVA glue) Shaving cream (foam, not gel) Baking soda Contact lens solution (containing boric acid and sodium borate) Food coloring (optional) Mixing bowl Mix</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 17 Jun 2024 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/fluffy-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Edible Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/edible-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating edible slime is a fun and safe science experiment for children, combining sensory play with a touch of culinary creativity.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to making edible slime using simple ingredients:  Materials:   Marshmallows (large or mini) Cornstarch Vegetable oil Food coloring (optional) Microwave-safe bowl Mixing spoons    Google Ad 1   Procedure:   Melt the Marshmallows:  Plac</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2024 11:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/edible-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rainbow Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainbow-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating rainbow slime is a fun and colorful science experiment that helps children learn about chemistry, specifically the concepts of polymers and non-Newtonian fluids.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Clear school glue (PVA glue) Liquid starch Food coloring (red, orange, yellow, green, blue, purple) Small mixing bowls (one for each color) Mixing spoons Measuring cups and spoons  </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 May 2024 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rainbow-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Salt Crystal Garden, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/salt-crystal-garden-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a salt crystal garden is a fascinating and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about solubility, saturation, and crystallization.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Wide-mouthed glass or plastic container (such as a jar or bowl) String, yarn, or pipe cleaners Scissors Salt (Epsom salt or table salt) Water Food coloring (o</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/salt-crystal-garden-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Borax Crystal Snowflakes, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/borax-crystal-snowflakes-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating Borax crystal snowflakes is a captivating and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about solubility, saturation, and crystallization. Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Borax powder (available in the laundry aisle of most supermarkets) Pipe cleaners (white or blue works well for snowflakes) String or yarn Pencil or stick Sc</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 May 2024 09:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/borax-crystal-snowflakes-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Alum Crystal Geodes, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/alum-crystal-geodes-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating alum crystal geodes is a captivating and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about solubility, saturation, and crystallization.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Alum powder (aluminum potassium sulfate) Eggshells or small hollow egg-shaped molds Water Food coloring (optional) String or fishing line Scissors Stirring spoo</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 15 May 2024 08:37:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/alum-crystal-geodes-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Rock Candy Crystal Sticks, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rock-candy-crystal-sticks-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating rock candy crystal sticks is a fun and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about solubility and saturation.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Granulated sugar Water Glass or plastic jars or cups Wooden skewers or bamboo sticks Clothespins Food coloring (optional) Flavor extracts (optional) Saucepan Stirring spoon Scissor</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 May 2024 13:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rock-candy-crystal-sticks-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Epsom Salt Crystal Shapes, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/epsom-salt-crystal-shapes-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating Epsom salt crystal shapes is a captivating and educational science experiment that allows children to observe crystal formation and learn about crystal structures.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Epsom salt (magnesium sulfate) Water Heat source (stove or microwave) Glass or plastic containers (jars, bowls, or cups) String or pipe cleaners Pencil or stick Food coloring (opt</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 06 May 2024 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/epsom-salt-crystal-shapes-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Balloon and Bottle Experiment, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-and-bottle-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The balloon and bottle experiment is a simple yet effective way to demonstrate the effects of air pressure.  Here&amp;#39;s how to conduct the experiment:  Materials Needed:   Empty plastic bottle with a narrow neck (such as a soda bottle) Balloon Scissors Tape (optional)    Google Ad 1   Instructions:   Start by removing the cap from the plastic bottle. If the bottle has any labels or stickers on it,</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 01 May 2024 09:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-and-bottle-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Crushing Can Experiment, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/crushing-can-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The crushing can experiment is a fascinating demonstration of air pressure in action.  Here&amp;#39;s how to conduct the experiment:  Materials Needed:   Empty aluminum soda can Heat-resistant tongs or a pair of pliers Stovetop or hot plate Bowl or container of cold water Safety goggles (optional but recommended)    Google Ad 1   Instructions:    Prepare the Can:   Begin by rinsing out the empty alumi</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 28 Apr 2024 16:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/crushing-can-experiment-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cartesian Diver, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cartesian-diver-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a Cartesian diver is a simple and fun science experiment that allows children to explore the concepts of buoyancy and pressure.  Here&amp;#39;s how to make one:  Materials Needed:   Clear plastic bottle with a screw-on cap Small plastic eye dropper or pipette Water Optional: Food coloring    Google Ad 1   Instructions:   Fill the plastic bottle with water almost to the top. Leave a small air </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 25 Apr 2024 19:46:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cartesian-diver-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ping Pong Ball Hovercraft, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ping-pong-ball-hovercraft-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a ping pong ball hovercraft is a fun and educational science experiment that children can enjoy while learning about the principles of air pressure and friction.  Here&amp;#39;s how to make a simple ping pong ball hovercraft:  Materials Needed:   A sturdy, smooth-surfaced CD or DVD A large balloon (preferably round) A hot glue gun and glue sticks A bottle cap (with a flat bottom) A ping pong </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Apr 2024 08:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ping-pong-ball-hovercraft-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a water fountain using air pressure, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-water-fountain-using-air-pressure-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a water fountain using air pressure can be an engaging and educational project.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple way to make a small-scale water fountain using air pressure:  Materials Needed:   Plastic bottle Drinking straw Hot glue gun and glue sticks Scissors Tape Water Optional: Food coloring (for colored water)    Google Ad 1   Instructions:   Prepare the Bottle:   Take a plastic bottle and remo</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 13 Apr 2024 09:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-water-fountain-using-air-pressure-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Build a Worm Farm, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-a-worm-farm-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Building a worm farm is a fantastic way to teach children about ecology, decomposition, and the importance of worms in soil health.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide to creating a worm farm:  Materials:   Large, clear plastic container with a lid Small container for drainage (with holes) Soil Sand Vegetable scraps (fruit and vegetable peels, coffee grounds, etc.) Red wiggler worms (available at garden ce</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 08 Apr 2024 08:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-a-worm-farm-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Gummy Bear Osmosis, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gummy-bear-osmosis-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The Gummy Bear Osmosis experiment is a simple and engaging way to demonstrate the concept of osmosis, which is the movement of water across a selectively permeable membrane.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Gummy bears (different colors if possible) Water Salt Clear cups or containers Tablespoon Timer or clock Paper and pen for recording observations      (adsbygoogle = window.adsby</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 03 Apr 2024 19:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/gummy-bear-osmosis-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Egg in a Bottle, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The Egg in a Bottle experiment is a classic demonstration of the principles of air pressure.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide for conducting this experiment:  Materials:   Hard-boiled egg (peeled) Glass bottle with a narrow neck (a milk bottle works well) Sheet of paper Matches or lighter      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    Procedure:   Peel the hard-boiled egg so that it easily f</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 18:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/egg-in-a-bottle-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leaf Chromatography, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-chromatography-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Leaf chromatography is a simple and fascinating experiment that introduces children to the concept of chromatography, which separates different pigments in leaves.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Fresh green leaves (different types if possible) Coffee filters or chromatography paper Pencil Small glasses or jars Rubbing alcohol or isopropyl alcohol Water Tape Small weights or paperc</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leaf-chromatography-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Seed Germination science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/seed-germination-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Germination experiment is a wonderful way to teach children about plant life cycles and the process of seed germination.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple experiment that can be done at home:  Materials:   Seeds (e.g., bean seeds, sunflower seeds, or radish seeds) Small containers or pots Potting soil Water Plastic wrap or a clear plastic bag Labels or markers for labeling      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogl</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Mar 2024 17:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/seed-germination-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Simple Circuits, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/simple-circuits-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple circuit is an excellent way to introduce children to the basics of electricity and electronics.  Here&amp;#39;s a straightforward experiment for making a simple circuit:  Materials:   AA batteries (1 or 2, depending on the circuit) Battery holder LED (Light Emitting Diode) Copper tape or aluminum foil Cardboard or paper Insulating tape or masking tape      (adsbygoogle = window.adsby</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Mar 2024 10:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/simple-circuits-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to maintain solar panel setup at your home to get the best results?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-maintain-solar-panel-setup-at-your-home-to-get-the-best-results.html</link>
			<description>Maintaining your solar panel setup is important to ensure it continues to operate efficiently and generate the maximum amount of energy.  Here are some steps you can take to maintain your home solar panel system:  Regular Cleaning:   Frequency: Depending on your location and climate, aim to clean your solar panels 2-4 times a year. More frequent cleaning may be needed in areas with high dust, poll</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 11:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-maintain-solar-panel-setup-at-your-home-to-get-the-best-results.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a custom Drupal Service and Use as a Helper</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-custom-drupal-service-and-use-as-a-helper.html</link>
			<description>Creating a custom Drupal service allows you to encapsulate functionality and access it wherever needed, promoting modularity and reusability within your codebase as a Helper.  In this article we are sharing an example of how to create a custom Drupal service and use it as a helper.  Step 1: Define the Service  Create a new custom module or use an existing one. Define your service in the module&amp;rsq</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-custom-drupal-service-and-use-as-a-helper.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to set up a Monitoring System for the Solar panel at your home?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-set-up-a-monitoring-system-for-the-solar-panel-at-your-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a monitoring system for your solar panel system allows you to track its performance and ensure it&amp;#39;s operating at its best.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can do it:  1. Choose a Monitoring System:  There are various monitoring options available, ranging from basic to advanced:   Manufacturer&amp;#39;s Monitoring: Many solar panel and inverter manufacturers offer their own monitoring platforms or a</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-set-up-a-monitoring-system-for-the-solar-panel-at-your-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Magnetic Slime, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating magnetic slime is a fun and educational science experiment that combines elements of chemistry and physics.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple guide for making magnetic slime:  Materials:   White school glue (like Elmer&amp;#39;s glue) Liquid starch Iron oxide powder (magnetic powder) Disposable mixing bowl Stirring stick or spoon Strong neodymium magnets (optional, for interactive play) Ziplock bag or air</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Dec 2023 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/magnetic-slime-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What is Charge Controller &amp; how to use it with a Solar panel setup at home?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-charge-controller-and-how-to-use-it-with-a-solar-panel-setup-at-home.html</link>
			<description>A charge controller, also known as a charge regulator, is a crucial component in a solar panel system. Its primary function is to regulate the voltage and current coming from the solar panels and going to the battery bank.  Here&amp;#39;s how to use a charge controller in a home solar panel setup:  Purpose of a Charge Controller:   Prevents Overcharging: Charge controllers prevent overcharging of batt</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-charge-controller-and-how-to-use-it-with-a-solar-panel-setup-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best Batteries to use with the Solar panels for home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-batteries-to-use-with-the-solar-panels-for-home.html</link>
			<description>When it comes to choosing batteries for a solar panel system, several options are available. The best battery for your home will depend on factors like budget, energy requirements, available space, and desired lifespan.  Here are some of the most common types:   Lithium-Ion Batteries:  Advantages:  High energy density, which means they can store a lot of energy in a relatively small space. Long li</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-batteries-to-use-with-the-solar-panels-for-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>DIY Pulley System, science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-it-yourself-pulley-system-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>Creating a simple DIY pulley system is a great way to introduce children to basic physics concepts like force and mechanical advantage.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can conduct a pulley system science experiment for children:  Materials:   Two sturdy hooks or fixed points (e.g., a door frame, tree branches, or any secure anchor points) String or rope Small bucket or container Objects with varying weights (</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-it-yourself-pulley-system-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Balloon Rocket science experiment for children</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</link>
			<description>The balloon rocket experiment is a simple and exciting way to explore the principles of action and reaction, or Newton&amp;#39;s Third Law of Motion.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can conduct the balloon rocket science experiment for children:  Materials:   Balloon String or thread (about 10-15 feet) Drinking straw Tape Scissors      (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});    Procedure:   Prepare the</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Nov 2023 11:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/balloon-rocket-science-experiment-for-children.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Optimal placement of solar panels for better observation of solar energy</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimal-placement-of-solar-panels-for-better-observation-of-solar-energy.html</link>
			<description>Optimal panel placement is crucial for maximizing energy production from your solar panel system. Here are some key considerations:   Orientation: In the Northern Hemisphere, panels should face true south to capture the maximum amount of sunlight throughout the day. In the Southern Hemisphere, panels should face true north. Tilt Angle: The tilt angle of the panels should be approximately equal to </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimal-placement-of-solar-panels-for-better-observation-of-solar-energy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a volcanic eruption with baking soda and vinegar</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-volcanic-eruption-with-baking-soda-and-vinegar.html</link>
			<description>Creating a volcanic eruption with baking soda and vinegar is a classic and safe science experiment that demonstrates the reaction between an acid (vinegar) and a base (baking soda) to produce carbon dioxide gas.  Here&amp;#39;s a simple step-by-step guide:  Materials:   Baking soda Vinegar Dish soap (optional) Red food coloring (optional) Container or plastic bottle Modeling clay or playdough Tray or </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Nov 2023 12:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-volcanic-eruption-with-baking-soda-and-vinegar.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Imagefield Slideshow module to render Slideshow on Drupal website</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/imagefield-slideshow-module-to-render-slideshow-on-drupal-website.html</link>
			<description>If you want to show images as a slideshow on your drupal website and want to do it quickly. Here&amp;rsquo;s the module which solves your purpose. Imagefield Slideshow is the simple module which will allow images to render as a slideshow on the drupal website at the field level.  This module will provide a Slideshow formatter for Image fields, so that multiple images are uploaded to that particular im</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Nov 2023 16:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/imagefield-slideshow-module-to-render-slideshow-on-drupal-website.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Choose the Inverters which are more efficient to work with Solar panels?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/choose-the-inverters-which-are-more-efficient-to-work-with-solar-panels.html</link>
			<description>Selecting an efficient inverter is crucial for maximizing the energy production of your solar panel system.  Here are key considerations for choosing an efficient solar inverter:   Type of Inverter:   String Inverters: These are connected to multiple solar panels in a series. They are cost-effective but the performance of the whole string can be affected if one panel is shaded or underperforming. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/choose-the-inverters-which-are-more-efficient-to-work-with-solar-panels.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to choose solar panels which are more efficient?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-choose-solar-panels-which-are-more-efficient.html</link>
			<description>Choosing efficient solar panels is crucial for maximizing the energy production of your solar system.  Here are some key factors to consider when selecting high-efficiency solar panels:   Conversion Efficiency:   Look for panels with a high conversion efficiency. This indicates the percentage of sunlight that the panel can convert into electricity. Higher efficiency panels will generate more power</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 13:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-choose-solar-panels-which-are-more-efficient.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Technical information to know about the Solar energy setup for your home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/technical-information-to-know-about-the-solar-energy-setup-for-your-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a solar power system for your home is a sustainable and environmentally-friendly way to generate electricity  Here are some key technical details to understand when setting up a solar energy system for your home:   Solar Panels (Photovoltaic Modules):   Capacity (Wattage): The power output of each panel, typically ranging from 250 to 400 watts. Efficiency: The percentage of sunlight tha</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/technical-information-to-know-about-the-solar-energy-setup-for-your-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to setup solar power for you home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-setup-solar-power-for-you-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a solar power system for a family of four in India involves several steps. Please note that the costs provided are approximate and can vary based on factors like location, system size, quality of components, and labor costs.  Additionally, government incentives and rebates can affect the final cost.  Step-by-Step Guide:  Step 1: Assess Your Energy Needs   Determine Your Energy Consumpti</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-setup-solar-power-for-you-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Unable to install Update Manager, update.settings already exists in active configuration</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unable-to-install-update-manager-update-settings-already-exists-in-active-configuration.html</link>
			<description>Generally you see this error while you try to install the update manager module via UI or via Drush command.  Not really sure how you came up with this issue. But if you are seeing this issue, you have an entry in your site&amp;#39;s configuration saying that the update module is already installed.  1. You can simply delete this configuration with the below command  $ drush cdel update.settings  Which</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unable-to-install-update-manager-update-settings-already-exists-in-active-configuration.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>