<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Sci-Tech - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Sci-Tech.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to work with Twig Templates in Drupal?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how a developer can work with Twig templates, and how to override templates (if needed) and create template suggestions with hooks, so that templates could be easily managed.  Basically drupal allows people to override the existing twig templates, so that people can fully have control on the html generated via the custom theme.  First thing, we need to make sur</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Jun 2022 19:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-work-with-twig-templates-in-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Quick reference of Code Reviews for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how your Drupal team can do code reviews and available tools or libraries which help people in the team to do the code reviews seamlessly.  It&amp;rsquo;s pretty important to follow a few guidelines as well, so that all people or developers in the team are on the same page.  Firstly, for the code reviews to be at their best, the committed code should be more organis</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 21:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/quick-reference-of-code-reviews-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Usage of PHPCS on Github via Pull Request for Drupal Applications</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how some tools &amp;amp; libraries will make people&amp;#39;s lives easier during the development &amp;amp; code review process.  And to make developer life easier, developers look for tools or libraries which can automated code review and if needed make any corrections in the code automatically. Here comes the PHP codesniffer and Drupal coder module.  If you are maintaini</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/usage-of-phpcs-on-github-via-pull-request-for-drupal-applications.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Store Secrets Securely on Pantheon for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-secrets-securely-on-pantheon-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see how people can store access keys and tokens securely, in the case of your drupal application that is managed on pantheon.  Generally, all the Access keys or Tokens or any Secret third party auth information should not be stored in the database or within the project web root, Its safe to store it encrypted and within a file, and keep the file outside of the proj</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/store-secrets-securely-on-pantheon-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Configuration management via Quicksilver on Pantheon</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuration-management-via-quicksilver-on-pantheon.html</link>
			<description>As we saw in the earlier article, like how we manage the configuration across the environments.  In this article we are going to see how Drupal configurations can be deployed or imported across the environments with the help of Quicksilver which hooks into platform workflows to automate your Pantheon WebOps workflow across the environments.  In the pantheon environment&amp;rsquo;s drupal code base, yo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 20:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/configuration-management-via-quicksilver-on-pantheon.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal Configuration management (Local, Dev, Test and Live)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-configuration-management-local-dev-test-and-live.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are going to see how Drupal serves configurations across the environments, which can be well maintained with help of some contributed modules and version control.  Drupal 8 onwards configuration has been saved in the yml files in a consistent manner, which includes all the enabled modules, all the content types, vocabularies, fields &amp;amp; views.  Making the configurations direct</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Jun 2022 15:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-configuration-management-local-dev-test-and-live.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Improve Drupal Search with Solr, Locally configured via Lando</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Improve-Drupal-Search-with-Solr-Locally-configured-via-Lando.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn how Drupal search can be improved with Solr which provides great performance, and is suitable even for use on large commercial websites. And along with this using the search_api &amp; search_api_solr modules, helps to configure the Facets &amp; Multilingual content can be handled in an improved manner. And let's see how we can configure this locally with the help of </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 19:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Improve-Drupal-Search-with-Solr-Locally-configured-via-Lando.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>When to use hook_update_N &amp; hook_post_update_NAME?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/When-to-use-hook_update_N-and-hook_post_update_NAME.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn when to use hook_update_N and hook_post_update_NAME. In general, I was using hook_update_N for any database-related changes or with any configuration additions or updates. And I was using hook_post_update_NAME for any content creation or updating or for the creation or updating any taxonomy terms etc, sometimes for clearing site caches as well. But, let’s h</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 08 Feb 2022 12:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/When-to-use-hook_update_N-and-hook_post_update_NAME.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Improvements for Editor Experience in Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Improvements-for-Editor-Experience-in-Drupal.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to learn what Drupal offers for text editors or content managers as a content management framework within Drupal Core &amp; Contributed modules. Earlier versions of Drupal have several useful features to help content editors to manage their content on a daily basis. And in the newer versions of Drupal (from when Symfony was introduced), there are a few more improvements i</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Dec 2021 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Improvements-for-Editor-Experience-in-Drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why do dentists suggest Clear aligners (invisalign)?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Why-do-dentists-suggest-Clear-aligners-invisalign.html</link>
			<description>Every patient wants their teeth to be in the proper correct position. In young patients they go for orthodontist braces treatment for the correction of their teeth. Patients demand for esthetic orthodontic appliances as made for clear aligners into mainstream modern orthodontics. Clear aligners actually began in 1926, by Orrin Remensydre’s Flex-o-Tite, the gum massage appliance which has side ef</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 16:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi S N</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Why-do-dentists-suggest-Clear-aligners-invisalign.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>