<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Self - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/self.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>The Journey from Self to Soul</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-journey-from-self-to-soul.html</link>
			<description>Beloved seekers of truth,  Life is not merely the rising and setting of the sun, nor the endless pursuit of worldly desires. Life is a sacred pilgrimage &amp;mdash; a journey from the self that clings to the body and mind, to the soul that is eternal, pure, and boundless. To walk this path is to awaken to the truth of who we are and why we are here.  The Nature of the Self  The self, as most understan</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-journey-from-self-to-soul.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to prevent morning breath?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prevent-morning-breath.html</link>
			<description>Morning breath, also known as halitosis, is a common issue caused by the natural decrease in saliva production while you sleep. Without adequate saliva to rinse away bacteria, odor-causing microbes can flourish, leading to unpleasant breath upon waking.  While it&amp;rsquo;s a natural occurrence, there are several steps you can take to minimize or prevent morning breath.  Understanding the Causes of M</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 08:59:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-prevent-morning-breath.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Reasons to Hang Eucalyptus in Your Shower</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reasons-to-hang-eucalyptus-in-your-shower.html</link>
			<description>Hanging eucalyptus in your shower has become a popular practice, not only because it adds a touch of natural beauty but because it offers a wide range of health and wellness benefits. Eucalyptus, a plant known for its distinctive aroma and healing properties, has been used for centuries in traditional medicine to relieve respiratory issues, promote relaxation, and improve overall well-being.  Here</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 08:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reasons-to-hang-eucalyptus-in-your-shower.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to tackle Emotional Resilience</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-tackle-emotional-resilience.html</link>
			<description>Tackling emotional resilience involves developing the skills and mindset to effectively cope with adversity, stress and challenges while maintaining a sense of well-being and inner strength.  Here are some strategies to help you build emotional resilience:   Cultivate Self-Awareness: Start by becoming aware of your thoughts, emotions and reactions to different situations. Pay attention to your tri</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 May 2024 14:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-tackle-emotional-resilience.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How can people approach unconscious bias towards other people?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-people-approach-unconscious-bias-towards-other-people.html</link>
			<description>Addressing unconscious bias is a complex but important task. It involves self-reflection, education and ongoing effort to challenge and change ingrained thought patterns.  Here are some approaches individuals can take to address unconscious bias:   Self-Reflection: Start by reflecting on your own beliefs, values and attitudes. Consider whether you might hold any biases and how they may influence y</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Mar 2024 18:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-people-approach-unconscious-bias-towards-other-people.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are the types of unconscious bias that people make?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-types-of-unconscious-bias-that-people-make.html</link>
			<description>Unconscious biases are automatic and unintentional judgments and attitudes that people hold about others based on characteristics such as race, gender, age, or other social categories. These biases can influence decision-making and behavior in subtle ways.  There are various types of unconscious biases and individuals may harbor multiple biases simultaneously.  Here are some common types:   Affini</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Mar 2024 13:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-types-of-unconscious-bias-that-people-make.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Build self awareness about unconscious bias and why it is needed?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-self-awareness-about-unconscious-bias-and-why-it-is-needed.html</link>
			<description>Self-awareness about unconscious bias is crucial for personal and professional development. Unconscious biases are automatic judgments and stereotypes that we hold about people based on characteristics such as race, gender, age, or other social categories. These biases can affect our perceptions, decisions and behaviors in subtle and unintended ways.  Building self-awareness about unconscious bias</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 11 Dec 2023 20:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-self-awareness-about-unconscious-bias-and-why-it-is-needed.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to be selfish and focus more on self?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-be-selfish-and-focus-more-on-self.html</link>
			<description>It&amp;#39;s important to clarify that while self-care and prioritizing your own well-being are important, actively seeking to harm others, such as cheating or being intentionally selfish in a harmful way, can lead to negative consequences for both you and those around you. It&amp;#39;s generally better to seek win-win situations where your needs are met without causing harm to others.  Focusing more on y</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 09 Oct 2023 18:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-be-selfish-and-focus-more-on-self.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>