<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Self - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/self.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to tackle Emotional Resilience</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-tackle-emotional-resilience.html</link>
			<description>Tackling emotional resilience involves developing the skills and mindset to effectively cope with adversity, stress, and challenges while maintaining a sense of well-being and inner strength.  Here are some strategies to help you build emotional resilience:   Cultivate Self-Awareness: Start by becoming aware of your thoughts, emotions, and reactions to different situations. Pay attention to your t</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:05:49 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-tackle-emotional-resilience.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How can people approach unconscious bias towards other people?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-people-approach-unconscious-bias-towards-other-people.html</link>
			<description>Addressing unconscious bias is a complex but important task. It involves self-reflection, education, and ongoing effort to challenge and change ingrained thought patterns.  Here are some approaches individuals can take to address unconscious bias:   Self-Reflection: Start by reflecting on your own beliefs, values, and attitudes. Consider whether you might hold any biases and how they may influence</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:05:49 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-people-approach-unconscious-bias-towards-other-people.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are the types of unconscious bias that people make?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-types-of-unconscious-bias-that-people-make.html</link>
			<description>Unconscious biases are automatic and unintentional judgments and attitudes that people hold about others based on characteristics such as race, gender, age, or other social categories. These biases can influence decision-making and behavior in subtle ways.  There are various types of unconscious biases, and individuals may harbor multiple biases simultaneously.  Here are some common types:   Affin</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:05:49 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-types-of-unconscious-bias-that-people-make.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Build self awareness about unconscious bias and why it is needed?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-self-awareness-about-unconscious-bias-and-why-it-is-needed.html</link>
			<description>Self-awareness about unconscious bias is crucial for personal and professional development. Unconscious biases are automatic judgments and stereotypes that we hold about people based on characteristics such as race, gender, age, or other social categories. These biases can affect our perceptions, decisions, and behaviors in subtle and unintended ways.  Building self-awareness about unconscious bia</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:05:49 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/build-self-awareness-about-unconscious-bias-and-why-it-is-needed.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to be selfish and focus more on self?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-be-selfish-and-focus-more-on-self.html</link>
			<description>It&amp;#39;s important to clarify that while self-care and prioritizing your own well-being are important, actively seeking to harm others, such as cheating or being intentionally selfish in a harmful way, can lead to negative consequences for both you and those around you. It&amp;#39;s generally better to seek win-win situations where your needs are met without causing harm to others.  Focusing more on y</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Oct 2024 08:05:49 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-be-selfish-and-focus-more-on-self.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>