<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Sexual Health - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/sexual-health.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to increase breast size naturally</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-increase-breast-size-naturally.html</link>
			<description>Increasing breast size naturally is a common concern, but it&amp;#39;s important to note that there are no guaranteed methods to significantly increase breast size without surgery.  However, some natural methods may help enhance breast appearance or promote overall breast health:  Exercises:   Push-Ups:   Strengthen the chest muscles (pectorals) which can make breasts appear firmer. Lie face down with</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-increase-breast-size-naturally.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Five exercises to naturally increase penis size</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/five-exercises-to-naturally-increase-penis-size.html</link>
			<description>There is no scientific evidence to support that exercises can significantly increase penis size. However, certain exercises can improve erectile function and overall penile health by increasing blood flow and strengthening the pelvic floor muscles.  Here are five exercises that may help:  Kegel Exercises:   Purpose: Strengthen the pelvic floor muscles, which support erectile function. How to Perfo</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Aug 2024 06:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/five-exercises-to-naturally-increase-penis-size.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How Do I Deal with Anxiety During Sex?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-i-deal-with-anxiety-during-sex.html</link>
			<description>Experiencing anxiety during sex can be a common issue and it is important to address the root cause of the anxiety and find ways to manage it.  Here are some tips for dealing with anxiety during sex:   Communicate with your partner: Let your partner know how you&amp;#39;re feeling and what you need to feel comfortable. Communication is key to a healthy and satisfying sexual experience.                </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-do-i-deal-with-anxiety-during-sex.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>BDSM Role Play: How Does It Work?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bdsm-role-play-how-does-it-work.html</link>
			<description>BDSM (bondage and discipline, dominance and submission, sadism and masochism) role play is a consensual sexual activity that involves one partner taking on a dominant role and the other partner taking on a submissive role. This can include activities such as power exchange, restraint and impact play.                     (adsbygoogle = window.adsbygoogle || []).push({});        In BDSM role play, p</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bdsm-role-play-how-does-it-work.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Different ways to get more out of 69 position</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-ways-to-get-more-out-of-six-nine-position.html</link>
			<description>The 69 position is a popular sexual position that involves mutual oral sex. Here are some tips to get more out of the 69 position:  1. Change positions: Try changing positions to mix things up. You can start with one person on top, then switch to the other person on top, or try a side-by-side position.  2. Use your hands: Incorporate your hands into the mix by touching your partner&amp;#39;s erogenous</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Mar 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/different-ways-to-get-more-out-of-six-nine-position.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Get more Pleasure from Lotus position!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-more-pleasure-from-lotus-position.html</link>
			<description>People have coitus in different positions, generally what they most like. And Lotus position is one of the such positions where you get to see and talk to your partner in a relaxed manner during your intimate intercourse.  So what is the Lotus position? - having an&amp;nbsp;intimate&amp;nbsp;intercourse by facing the partner by sitting as close as you both can, wrap your legs around their body and partner</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/get-more-pleasure-from-lotus-position.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to Have a Better Sex?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-have-a-better-sex.html</link>
			<description>For all people to have a healthy relationship, people need to have healthy communication. Many of us might have ended up with an unsatisfied sex, but did you really communicate this with your partner?  Actually one should not be silent though, ideally should speak about it, but how and when, I would leave it to the people, anyways they have their own ways of presentations and explanations.  Genera</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-have-a-better-sex.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>People still say yes to Condoms, instead of Birth Control</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-still-say-yes-to-condoms-instead-of-birth-control.html</link>
			<description>Generally when you don&amp;rsquo;t want to get any&amp;nbsp;byproduct out of your pleasure, then you tend to have birth control or an IUD, Intrauterine device or an Implant. But many people will still prefer to&amp;nbsp;use condoms instead&amp;nbsp;of other stuff. I think there are many good reasons behind that, let&amp;#39;s see what are those.   Easy available method to avoid Pregnancy or any STIs No need of a Pres</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/people-still-say-yes-to-condoms-instead-of-birth-control.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Do you know? Your Brain is the biggest Sex organ!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-you-know-your-brain-is-the-biggest-sex-organ.html</link>
			<description>Experiencing our sexuality has a lot to do with bodies, like how we like to touch and be touched by our partner. And when we think of the sex organs,&amp;nbsp;our minds think toward&amp;nbsp;the naughty parts between our legs, but our minds should be doing this right.  The&amp;nbsp;real catalyst for sexual activity&amp;nbsp;is the brain, actually not entirty brain, but specific parts of the brain and it&amp;rsquo;s n</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/do-you-know-your-brain-is-the-biggest-sex-organ.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Having Good Sex at any Age! Is it Really Possible?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/having-good-sex-at-any-age-is-it-really-possible.html</link>
			<description>No matter what is your gender, you can always enjoy sex for as long as you wish. And naturally sex at age of 70 or 80&amp;nbsp;may not be same&amp;nbsp;like it is at would be at 20 or 30, but It would be better in some ways.  Sex can be one of the powerful emotional experience and one of the great tool for protecting or improving your health, And it doesn&amp;rsquo;t mean, you can have it only at young age. Y</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/having-good-sex-at-any-age-is-it-really-possible.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>