<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Social Media - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/social-media.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Droupadi Murmu, New President of India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</link>
			<description>Droupadi Murmu was nominated to President elections and on 21st of July 2022 elections counting was finished and Droupadi Murmu won the elections and will be the New President of India, Murmu is likely to take oath on July 25 as President of India.  A few highlights of 15th President of India   Droupadi Murmu will be the first person belonging to a Scheduled Tribe (ST) community to be elected as t</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>President of India nominated Veerendra Heggade, P.T. Usha, Ilaiyaraaja and V. Vijayendra Prasad to the Rajya Sabha</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</link>
			<description>According to the Fourth Schedule (Articles 4(1) and 80(2)) of the Constitution of India, The President of India can nominate 12 members to Rajya Sabha for a term of six-years for their contributions towards Arts, Literature, Sciences, and Social Services.  Maybe earlier most of the South Indian peoples, for this matter all the Indian people might not be aware that The President of India can nomina</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why Madanapalle should be headquarters of proposed Annamayya District?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-madanapalle-should-be-the-headquarters-of-the-proposed-annamayya-district.html</link>
			<description>There are many reasons for Madanapalle to be the headquarters of the proposed Annamayya district in almost all aspects. Madanapalle is a city in the Chittoor district of the Indian state of Andhra Pradesh. Madanapalli was founded by Sri Maadanna in 1618 AD. One of the oldest towns. In 1850, Madanapalle was developed as Sub Division and had the First Sub Collector. Rabindranath Tagore translated Ja</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-madanapalle-should-be-the-headquarters-of-the-proposed-annamayya-district.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>For Indian Youth..! What should you know about Nambi Narayanan?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-indian-youth-what-should-you-know-about-nambi-narayanan.html</link>
			<description>Lets see the background,
                                In 1992, India signed an agreement with Russia..
                                
                                    Aggrement was for transfer of technology to develop cryogenic fuel-based engines and procurement of two such engines for ₹ 235 crore.
                                    However, Russia did not materialize after the US pres</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-indian-youth-what-should-you-know-about-nambi-narayanan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Things to Know before you go for Registration of a Plot or Property in Bangalore</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-before-you-go-for-registration-of-a-plot-in-bangalore.html</link>
			<description>When you decide to buy a property or land than a normal business deal where you get a plot of land in exchange of money. Before going into details of plot registration, there are a few terms you must know.
                                Registration fee - It's a small percentage of total cost of plot paid by buyer to state government for registering property on his name.
                         </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-before-you-go-for-registration-of-a-plot-in-bangalore.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>When Police doesnot register your FIR? Contact Judge!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-police-doesnot-register-your-fir-contact-judge.html</link>
			<description>If you are reporting a cognisable crime and Police refuse to register your FIR, you can make a complaint to a higher ranking officer such as the Superintendent of Police (SP), the Deputy Inspector General (DIG) or the Inspector General of Police (IGP). You can also complain to the nearest Judicial Magistrate, who will order the police to register the FIR if deemed necessary.
                      </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-police-doesnot-register-your-fir-contact-judge.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Privatisation of Public Sector Banks &amp; Banks Strike in March 2021</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/privatisation-of-public-sector-banks-banks-strike-march-.html</link>
			<description>The Finance Minister has announced in Union Budget of India for 2021-22, that two Public Sector Banks (PSBs) will be Privatised. The policy of government in last three decades of economic reforms was to sell a part of shares in Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) including PSBs to public while retaining the controlling share in its own hands.
                                Privatisation of PSBs is </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/privatisation-of-public-sector-banks-banks-strike-march-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World Wildlife Day</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-wildlife-day.html</link>
			<description>On 20 December 2013, United Nations General Assembly (UNGA), in its resolution UN 68/205, decided to proclaim 3 March, the international day of the adoption of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Wild Fauna and Flora (CITES) on the planet raise awareness and benefits fauna and flora in 1973, as World Wildlife Day, which was proposed by Thailand, to celebrate and raise aw</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-wildlife-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>International Mother Language Day</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/international-mother-language-day.html</link>
			<description>International Mother Language Day is a worldwide annual observance held on 21st February to promote awareness of linguistic and cultural diversity and to promote multilingualism. First announced by UNESCO on 17 November 1999, it was formally recognized by the United Nations General Assembly with the adoption of UN resolution 56/262 in 2002.
                                Mother Language Day is pa</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/international-mother-language-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>If farmers have greater choice to sell to whoever &amp; wherever! Why still Farmers are protesting?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/if-farmers-have-greater-choice-to-sell-to-whoever-and-wherever.html</link>
			<description>The Rajya Sabha passed two out of the three Bills being referred to as the Farm Bills. These two Bills are the Farmers Produce Trade and Commerce (Promotion and Facilitation) Bill, 2020, and the Farmers (Empowerment and Protection) Agreement on Price Assurance and Farm Services Bill, 2020. The Lok Sabha had already passed these Bills. There was some ruckus in the Rajya Sabha where the Bill was pas</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/if-farmers-have-greater-choice-to-sell-to-whoever-and-wherever.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World Cancer Day, February 4th - Early detection of Cancer can lead to Improved outcomes &amp; Cure.</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</link>
			<description>Cancer is a large group of diseases that can start in almost any organ or tissue of the body when abnormal cells grow uncontrollably, go beyond their usual boundaries to invade adjoining parts of the body and/or spread to other organs. The latter process is called metastasizing which is a major cause of death from cancer. A neoplasm and malignant tumour are other common names for cancer.
         </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian Farms Reforms of 2020</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-farms-reforms-of-.html</link>
			<description>The Indian Farms Reforms of 2020 refer to the agricultural bills passed by the Lok Sabha on 17th September 2020 and by the Rajya Sabha on 20th September 2020. The bills collectively seek to provide farmers with multiple marketing channels and provide a legal framework for farmers to enter into pre-arranged contracts among other things.
                                The President of India gave hi</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-farms-reforms-of-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>National Education Policy 2020, Government of India (NEP 2020)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/national-education-policy-nep.html</link>
			<description>National Education Policy (NEP 2020) has been approved by Union Cabinet on 29 July 2020. Its major aim is to introduce changes in the Indian Education System right from the school to the college level of education. Making India a Global Knowledge Superpower is the ultimate objective of the NEP 2020. It is the third major change in education systems in India since independence in 1947. Earlier two </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/national-education-policy-nep.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World's Fastest Anti-Ship Cruise Missile in Operation</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/worlds-fastest-anti-ship-cruise-missile-in-operation.html</link>
			<description>BrahMos is a medium-range ramjet supersonic cruise missile that can be launched from submarine, ships, aircraft, or land. It is the fastest supersonic cruise missile in the world. It is a joint venture between the Russian Federation's NPO Mashinostroyeniya and India's Defence Research and Development Organisation (DRDO), who together have formed BrahMos Aerospace. The name BrahMos is formed from t</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 16 Dec 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/worlds-fastest-anti-ship-cruise-missile-in-operation.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Scientists Have Created Hexagonal Salt, For First Time Ever</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/scientists-have-created-hexagonal-salt.html</link>
			<description>While it probably won't make it to your dining table, a new scientific achievement might be able to help in everything from radar equipment to electric cars: scientists have been able to form salt, aka sodium chloride (NaCl), in a hexagonal shapeThis is work done at the smallest of scales, with researchers able to get a thin film of hexagonal salt to form on top of a layer of diamond, due to the c</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/scientists-have-created-hexagonal-salt.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>'PigeonBot' is the first robot that can bend its wings like a real bird</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pigeonbot-is-the-first-robot-that-can-bend-its-wings.html</link>
			<description>Pigeons may be considered rats of the sky, but some scientists have found greater value in these urban birds: the blueprint for a new generation of flying machines.Birds can modify the shape of their wings by fanning out their feathers or shuffling them closer together. Those adjustments allow birds to cut through the sky more nimbly than rigid drones. Now, using new insights into exactly how pige</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pigeonbot-is-the-first-robot-that-can-bend-its-wings.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>