<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Social Media - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/social-media.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Burial Case: SIT Granted Police Station Status, Investigation Gains Legal Edge</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-granted-police-station-status-investigation-gains-legal-edge.html</link>
			<description>Bengaluru/Mangaluru  The Special Investigation Team (SIT) probing the alleged Dharmasthala mass burial and murder case has now been officially granted the status of a police station, a move expected to significantly strengthen the investigation and prevent legal hurdles during trial proceedings.  Empowered Status  According to Home Ministry sources, the order was issued on Thursday (August 7, 2025</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Aug 2025 13:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-burial-case-sit-granted-police-station-status-investigation-gains-legal-edge.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dharmasthala Mass Murder Case Escalates to Delhi: Grievance Seeks NIA Probe, Alleges State Government Obstruction</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-murder-case-escalates-to-delhi-grievance-seeks-nia-probe-alleges-state-government-obstruction.html</link>
			<description>Dharmasthala / New Delhi &amp;mdash; A formal grievance submitted through the Central Government&amp;rsquo;s CPGRAMS portal has raised serious concerns about the handling of the Dharmasthala mass murder case. The petitioner has urged the Ministry of Home Affairs to transfer the case to the National Investigation Agency (NIA), citing international dimensions and obstruction by senior Karnataka political fi</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dharmasthala-mass-murder-case-escalates-to-delhi-grievance-seeks-nia-probe-alleges-state-government-obstruction.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>YouTubers Attacked by Alleged Dharmasthala D-Gang: A Blow to Press Freedom</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/youtubers-attacked-by-alleged-dharmasthala-d-gang-a-blow-to-press-freedom.html</link>
			<description>Dharmasthala, Karnataka &amp;ndash; 6th August 2025  In a shocking incident that has sparked widespread outrage, two independent YouTubers were reportedly attacked while covering ongoing developments around the mysterious deaths and criminal allegations in and around the Dharmasthala region. The attack, allegedly carried out by what locals and media sources are calling the &amp;quot;Dharmasthala D-Gang&amp;qu</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Aug 2025 08:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/youtubers-attacked-by-alleged-dharmasthala-d-gang-a-blow-to-press-freedom.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>India Stands Tall: Navigating Geopolitical Tensions Without Bowing to Pressure</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/india-stands-tall-navigating-geopolitical-tensions-without-bowing-to-pressure.html</link>
			<description>In today&amp;rsquo;s complex and volatile global environment, India is emerging not just as a regional power, but as a nation capable of making sovereign choices amidst growing international scrutiny. With Prime Minister Narendra Modi at the helm, India has demonstrated that it will not bend under external pressure&amp;mdash;be it from the West, the East, or any geopolitical bloc. At the heart of this sta</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/india-stands-tall-navigating-geopolitical-tensions-without-bowing-to-pressure.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The MiG-21: India’s First Supersonic Jet Retires After 62 Years of Glorious Service</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-mig--india-s-first-supersonic-jet-retires-after--years-of-glorious-service.html</link>
			<description>India&amp;rsquo;s journey toward becoming a modern air power took flight with the MiG‑21, a supersonic fighter aircraft that served the nation with distinction for over six decades. As the Indian Air Force prepares to bid farewell to this iconic aircraft in September 2025, it is a moment of reflection and pride for every Indian.  A Historic Induction  The MiG-21 was inducted into the Indian Air Forc</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jul 2025 18:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-mig--india-s-first-supersonic-jet-retires-after--years-of-glorious-service.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Maulana Masood Azhar, The Terror Mastermind and Most Wanted by India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/maulana-masood-azhar-the-terror-mastermind-and-most-wanted-by-india.html</link>
			<description>Maulana Masood Azhar is one of the world&amp;rsquo;s most dangerous and most wanted terrorists, known for orchestrating multiple deadly attacks against India. As the founder of Jaish-e-Mohammed (JeM), a UN-designated terrorist organization, Azhar has spent decades fueling jihadist violence, especially in the Indian region of Jammu and Kashmir. His name is synonymous with some of the worst terror incid</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:14:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/maulana-masood-azhar-the-terror-mastermind-and-most-wanted-by-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Donald Trump and the Elusive Nobel Peace Prize: Past Attempts, Present Claims, and Persistent Barriers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/donald-trump-and-the-elusive-nobel-peace-prize-past-attempts-present-claims-and-persistent-barriers.html</link>
			<description>Few honors in the world carry as much symbolic and moral weight as the Nobel Peace Prize. It&amp;rsquo;s not just a medal&amp;mdash;it&amp;rsquo;s a historic recognition of an individual&amp;#39;s contribution to peace and human progress. Donald Trump, former U.S. President, has openly expressed his desire to receive this prestigious award.  Despite multiple nominations and public claims of deserving it, he remai</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/donald-trump-and-the-elusive-nobel-peace-prize-past-attempts-present-claims-and-persistent-barriers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>RCB, Alcohol Ownership, and the Public Spectacle: A Modern-Colosseum Distraction?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rcb-alcohol-ownership-and-the-public-spectacle-a-modern-colosseum-distraction.html</link>
			<description>Every April&amp;ndash;May from past 18 years, Bengaluru transforms into a sea of red and black as fans don RCB jerseys and pour into pubs, chanting their team&amp;rsquo;s praises. For many, RCB (Royal Challengers Bengaluru) isn&amp;rsquo;t just a cricket franchise&amp;mdash;it&amp;rsquo;s Karnataka pride incarnate. 🏏 But beneath the enthusiasm lies a deeper truth: RCB is owned by United Spirits, a subsidiary of Di</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 24 Jun 2025 10:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/rcb-alcohol-ownership-and-the-public-spectacle-a-modern-colosseum-distraction.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Should people really vote in democracy?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</link>
			<description>Yes, voting is a crucial aspect of a democratic society and it plays a fundamental role in shaping the governance and policies of a nation.  Here are some reasons why voting is important:   Representation: Voting allows individuals to have a say in choosing representatives who will make decisions on their behalf. By participating in elections, citizens can help ensure that their interests and conc</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/should-people-really-vote-in-democracy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Droupadi Murmu, New President of India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</link>
			<description>Droupadi Murmu was nominated to President elections and on 21st of July 2022 elections counting was finished and Droupadi Murmu won the elections and will be the New President of India, Murmu is likely to take oath on July 25 as President of India.  A few highlights of 15th President of India   Droupadi Murmu will be the first person belonging to a Scheduled Tribe (ST) community to be elected as t</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/droupadi-murmu-new-president-of-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>President of India nominated Veerendra Heggade, P.T. Usha, Ilaiyaraaja and V. Vijayendra Prasad to the Rajya Sabha</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</link>
			<description>According to the Fourth Schedule (Articles 4(1) and 80(2)) of the Constitution of India, The President of India can nominate 12 members to Rajya Sabha for a term of six-years for their contributions towards Arts, Literature, Sciences and Social Services.  Maybe earlier most of the South Indian peoples, for this matter all the Indian people might not be aware that The President of India can nominat</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/president-of-india-nominated-veerendra-heggade-pt-usha-ilaiyaraaja-and-vijayendra-prasad-to-the-rajya-sabha.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why Madanapalle should be headquarters of proposed Annamayya District?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-madanapalle-should-be-the-headquarters-of-the-proposed-annamayya-district.html</link>
			<description>There are many reasons for Madanapalle to be the headquarters of the proposed Annamayya district in almost all aspects. Madanapalle is a city in the Chittoor district of the Indian state of Andhra Pradesh. Madanapalli was founded by Sri Maadanna in 1618 AD. One of the oldest towns. In 1850, Madanapalle was developed as Sub Division and had the First Sub Collector. Rabindranath Tagore translated Ja</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-madanapalle-should-be-the-headquarters-of-the-proposed-annamayya-district.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>For Indian Youth..! What should you know about Nambi Narayanan?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-indian-youth-what-should-you-know-about-nambi-narayanan.html</link>
			<description>Lets see the background,                                In 1992, India signed an agreement with Russia..                                                                    Aggrement was for transfer of technology to develop cryogenic fuel-based engines and procurement of two such engines for ₹ 235 crore.                                    However, Russia did not materialize after the US presiden</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/for-indian-youth-what-should-you-know-about-nambi-narayanan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Things to Know before you go for Registration of a Plot or Property in Bangalore</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-before-you-go-for-registration-of-a-plot-in-bangalore.html</link>
			<description>When you decide to buy a property or land than a normal business deal where you get a plot of land in exchange of money. Before going into details of plot registration, there are a few terms you must know.                                Registration fee - It's a small percentage of total cost of plot paid by buyer to state government for registering property on his name.                           </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/things-to-know-before-you-go-for-registration-of-a-plot-in-bangalore.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>When Police doesnot register your FIR? Contact Judge!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-police-doesnot-register-your-fir-contact-judge.html</link>
			<description>If you are reporting a cognisable crime and Police refuse to register your FIR, you can make a complaint to a higher ranking officer such as the Superintendent of Police (SP), the Deputy Inspector General (DIG) or the Inspector General of Police (IGP). You can also complain to the nearest Judicial Magistrate, who will order the police to register the FIR if deemed necessary.                       </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/when-police-doesnot-register-your-fir-contact-judge.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Privatisation of Public Sector Banks &amp; Banks Strike in March 2021</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/privatisation-of-public-sector-banks-banks-strike-march-.html</link>
			<description>The Finance Minister has announced in Union Budget of India for 2021-22, that two Public Sector Banks (PSBs) will be Privatised. The policy of government in last three decades of economic reforms was to sell a part of shares in Public Sector Undertakings (PSUs) including PSBs to public while retaining the controlling share in its own hands.                                Privatisation of PSBs is i</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/privatisation-of-public-sector-banks-banks-strike-march-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World Wildlife Day</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-wildlife-day.html</link>
			<description>On 20 December 2013, United Nations General Assembly (UNGA), in its resolution UN 68/205, decided to proclaim 3 March, the international day of the adoption of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Wild Fauna and Flora (CITES) on the planet raise awareness and benefits fauna and flora in 1973, as World Wildlife Day, which was proposed by Thailand, to celebrate and raise aw</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-wildlife-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>International Mother Language Day</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/international-mother-language-day.html</link>
			<description>International Mother Language Day is a worldwide annual observance held on 21st February to promote awareness of linguistic and cultural diversity and to promote multilingualism. First announced by UNESCO on 17 November 1999, it was formally recognized by the United Nations General Assembly with the adoption of UN resolution 56/262 in 2002.                                Mother Language Day is par</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/international-mother-language-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>If farmers have greater choice to sell to whoever &amp; wherever! Why still Farmers are protesting?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/if-farmers-have-greater-choice-to-sell-to-whoever-and-wherever.html</link>
			<description>The Rajya Sabha passed two out of the three Bills being referred to as the Farm Bills. These two Bills are the Farmers Produce Trade and Commerce (Promotion and Facilitation) Bill, 2020 and the Farmers (Empowerment and Protection) Agreement on Price Assurance and Farm Services Bill, 2020. The Lok Sabha had already passed these Bills. There was some ruckus in the Rajya Sabha where the Bill was pass</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/if-farmers-have-greater-choice-to-sell-to-whoever-and-wherever.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World Cancer Day, February 4th - Early detection of Cancer can lead to Improved outcomes &amp; Cure.</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</link>
			<description>Cancer is a large group of diseases that can start in almost any organ or tissue of the body when abnormal cells grow uncontrollably, go beyond their usual boundaries to invade adjoining parts of the body and/or spread to other organs. The latter process is called metastasizing which is a major cause of death from cancer. A neoplasm and malignant tumour are other common names for cancer.          </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-cancer-day-february-th.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Indian Farms Reforms of 2020</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-farms-reforms-of-.html</link>
			<description>The Indian Farms Reforms of 2020 refer to the agricultural bills passed by the Lok Sabha on 17th September 2020 and by the Rajya Sabha on 20th September 2020. The bills collectively seek to provide farmers with multiple marketing channels and provide a legal framework for farmers to enter into pre-arranged contracts among other things.                                The President of India gave his</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 16 Dec 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/indian-farms-reforms-of-.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>National Education Policy 2020, Government of India (NEP 2020)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/national-education-policy-nep.html</link>
			<description>National Education Policy (NEP 2020) has been approved by Union Cabinet on 29 July 2020. Its major aim is to introduce changes in the Indian Education System right from the school to the college level of education. Making India a Global Knowledge Superpower is the ultimate objective of the NEP 2020. It is the third major change in education systems in India since independence in 1947. Earlier two </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/national-education-policy-nep.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World's Fastest Anti-Ship Cruise Missile in Operation</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/worlds-fastest-anti-ship-cruise-missile-in-operation.html</link>
			<description>BrahMos is a medium-range ramjet supersonic cruise missile that stands as the fastest supersonic cruise missile in the world. Designed for versatile deployment, it can be launched from submarines, ships, aircraft, or land-based platforms. Developed as a joint venture between the Russian Federation&amp;rsquo;s NPO Mashinostroyeniya and India&amp;rsquo;s Defence Research and Development Organisation (DRDO),</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 11:23:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/worlds-fastest-anti-ship-cruise-missile-in-operation.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Scientists Have Created Hexagonal Salt, For First Time Ever</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/scientists-have-created-hexagonal-salt.html</link>
			<description>While it probably won't make it to your dining table, a new scientific achievement might be able to help in everything from radar equipment to electric cars: scientists have been able to form salt, aka sodium chloride (NaCl), in a hexagonal shapeThis is work done at the smallest of scales, with researchers able to get a thin film of hexagonal salt to form on top of a layer of diamond, due to the c</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/scientists-have-created-hexagonal-salt.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>'PigeonBot' is the first robot that can bend its wings like a real bird</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pigeonbot-is-the-first-robot-that-can-bend-its-wings.html</link>
			<description>Pigeons may be considered rats of the sky, but some scientists have found greater value in these urban birds: the blueprint for a new generation of flying machines.  Birds can modify the shape of their wings by fanning out their feathers or shuffling them closer together. Those adjustments allow birds to cut through the sky more nimbly than rigid drones. Now, using new insights into exactly how pi</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 17:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/pigeonbot-is-the-first-robot-that-can-bend-its-wings.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>