<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Software - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/software.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to Create a Document Library in SharePoint and Configure Content Types, Terms, User Groups, and Permissions</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-create-a-document-library-in-sharepoint-and-configure-content-types-terms-user-groups-and-permissions.html</link>
			<description>SharePoint is a robust collaboration platform that helps organizations manage and share documents and other content. One of the key features of SharePoint is the ability to create Document Libraries, which serve as centralized repositories for storing, organizing, and managing documents. These libraries can be highly customized with features like Content Types, Managed Metadata (Terms), User Group</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 08:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-create-a-document-library-in-sharepoint-and-configure-content-types-terms-user-groups-and-permissions.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding SharePoint Document Libraries, Content Types, Terms, User Groups and Permissions</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sharepoint-document-libraries-content-types-terms-user-groups-and-permissions.html</link>
			<description>SharePoint is a powerful collaboration platform that allows organizations to store, manage, and share content efficiently. One of the core features of SharePoint is the Document Library, which provides a centralized location for storing files and documents. To enhance document management, SharePoint allows for a range of customization options, including Content Types, Managed Metadata (Terms), Use</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sharepoint-document-libraries-content-types-terms-user-groups-and-permissions.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding SharePoint Documents vs. Document Sets: Key Differences and Use Cases</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sharepoint-documents-vs-document-sets-key-differences-and-use-cases.html</link>
			<description>When working with SharePoint, a robust collaboration and document management platform, it&amp;#39;s important to understand the different ways you can organize and manage your files. Two key features for managing files in SharePoint are Documents and Document Sets. Although they may seem similar at first glance, they serve different purposes and offer distinct features to help you manage your content </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2024 07:12:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-sharepoint-documents-vs-document-sets-key-differences-and-use-cases.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Create a custom Drupal Service and Use as a Helper</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-custom-drupal-service-and-use-as-a-helper.html</link>
			<description>Creating a custom Drupal service allows you to encapsulate functionality and access it wherever needed, promoting modularity and reusability within your codebase as a Helper.  In this article we are sharing an example of how to create a custom Drupal service and use it as a helper.  Step 1: Define the Service  Create a new custom module or use an existing one. Define your service in the module&amp;rsq</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 22 Mar 2024 15:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/create-a-custom-drupal-service-and-use-as-a-helper.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Unable to install Update Manager, update.settings already exists in active configuration</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unable-to-install-update-manager-update-settings-already-exists-in-active-configuration.html</link>
			<description>Generally you see this error while you try to install the update manager module via UI or via Drush command.  Not really sure how you came up with this issue. But if you are seeing this issue, you have an entry in your site&amp;#39;s configuration saying that the update module is already installed.  1. You can simply delete this configuration with the below command  $ drush cdel update.settings  Which</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 08 Sep 2023 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unable-to-install-update-manager-update-settings-already-exists-in-active-configuration.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What is a Customer Data Platform and which one is best for your Business?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-a-customer-data-platform-and-which-one-is-best-for-your-business.html</link>
			<description>Customer Data Platform (CDP) is a sophisticated software system that aggregates and manages customer data across various touchpoints and channels. Its primary purpose is to create a unified and comprehensive view of individual customers or segments of customers. This centralized data is then made accessible to other systems and tools for marketing, analytics and customer engagement.  Key features </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Sep 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-a-customer-data-platform-and-which-one-is-best-for-your-business.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>API Docs, Drupal contributed module for your Developer Portal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/api-docs-drupal-contributed-module-for-your-developer-portal.html</link>
			<description>This module will provide API Docs to your Developer Portal, It is powered by Drupal content type, custom field formatters &amp;amp; views.  Here&amp;#39;s a step-by-step guide to help you to download, enable, configure and use the module for your developer portal.  Download &amp;amp; Enable the Module:   Visit the Drupal.org website and navigate to the API Docs module&amp;#39;s page that you want to download, her</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/api-docs-drupal-contributed-module-for-your-developer-portal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to improve drupal website performance</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-drupal-website-performance.html</link>
			<description>Improving the performance of a Drupal website involves optimizing various aspects of its configuration and content. There are several ways to overall complex performance related problems and improve Drupal website performance to load it quicker.  Here are some tips to enhance the performance of your Drupal website:  Enable Caching:   Enable Drupal&amp;#39;s built-in caching mechanisms to store pre-gen</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 14:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-drupal-website-performance.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to build the engaging digital experience via Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-build-the-engaging-digital-experience-via-drupal.html</link>
			<description>Building an engaging digital experience using Drupal involves combining effective design, user-friendly features and content that resonates with your audience. Here are some tips to help you create an engaging digital experience using Drupal:   Define Your Target Audience: Understand your target audience and their needs, preferences and goals. Tailor your digital experience to meet their expectati</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-build-the-engaging-digital-experience-via-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Security Checklist for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-checklist-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>Securing your Drupal website is crucial to protect your data, users and overall website integrity. Here&amp;#39;s a security checklist for a Drupal website:   Keep Drupal Core and Modules Up to Date: Regularly update Drupal core and contributed modules to ensure you have the latest security patches. Enable update notifications to stay informed about available updates. Use Strong and Unique Passwords: </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-checklist-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is Drupal Chosen by Large Organizations?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-chosen-by-large-organizations.html</link>
			<description>Drupal is often chosen by large organizations for several reasons. Here are some key factors that make Drupal a popular choice:   Scalability: Drupal is highly scalable, allowing organizations to handle large amounts of content, traffic and user interactions. Its flexible architecture and robust performance capabilities enable it to accommodate the complex needs of large-scale websites and applica</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-chosen-by-large-organizations.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal LMS Features for Your Education Business</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re running an education business and considering Drupal as the platform for your Learning Management System (LMS), there are several features and capabilities you should look for to ensure a robust and effective solution.  Here are some key Drupal LMS features to consider:   Course Management: A Drupal LMS should provide comprehensive course management capabilities. This includes the ab</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leveraging Content Grouping for Personalized Digital Experiences</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</link>
			<description>Content grouping is a powerful technique that can be leveraged to create personalized digital experiences for users. By grouping content based on specific criteria, such as user preferences, demographics, or behavior, you can deliver targeted and relevant content to individual users. Here are some ways to utilize content grouping for personalized digital experiences:   User Segmentation: Segment y</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Colima, similar tool like Docker Desktop, for Drupal Development</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</link>
			<description>Colima is a project that is easy to use and fully open source and it helps in running docker containers on Linux OS and MacOs machines.  We know Docker Desktop is no more a complete open source, if you are not using it personally. So now Colima is a tool which does work similar to Docker Desktop and In this article we are going to see how it works alone or along with Docker Desktop on your Linux m</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 14:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What to Know for Estimating Projects</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-for-estimating-projects.html</link>
			<description>Estimating projects is part of project management. And we can’t always estimate a project with 100% accuracy. There will be learning from the failed attempts at estimating projects, maybe with running overtime, or with budget, or with resources etc.                            If one needs to deliver a project successfully then one must estimate the project as better as possible.                 </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-for-estimating-projects.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>