<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Software - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/software.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to improve drupal website performance</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-drupal-website-performance.html</link>
			<description>Improving the performance of a Drupal website involves optimizing various aspects of its configuration and content. Here are some tips to enhance the performance of your Drupal website:   Enable Caching: Enable Drupal&amp;#39;s built-in caching mechanisms to store pre-generated content and reduce the need for repeated processing. Go to Configuration &amp;gt; Performance and enable caching options like pag</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 17:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-improve-drupal-website-performance.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to build the engaging digital experience via Drupal</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-build-the-engaging-digital-experience-via-drupal.html</link>
			<description>Building an engaging digital experience using Drupal involves combining effective design, user-friendly features, and content that resonates with your audience. Here are some tips to help you create an engaging digital experience using Drupal:   Define Your Target Audience: Understand your target audience and their needs, preferences, and goals. Tailor your digital experience to meet their expecta</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-build-the-engaging-digital-experience-via-drupal.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Security Checklist for Drupal Application</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-checklist-for-drupal-application.html</link>
			<description>Securing your Drupal website is crucial to protect your data, users, and overall website integrity. Here&amp;#39;s a security checklist for a Drupal website:   Keep Drupal Core and Modules Up to Date: Regularly update Drupal core and contributed modules to ensure you have the latest security patches. Enable update notifications to stay informed about available updates. Use Strong and Unique Passwords:</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jun 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/security-checklist-for-drupal-application.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is Drupal Chosen by Large Organizations?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-chosen-by-large-organizations.html</link>
			<description>Drupal is often chosen by large organizations for several reasons. Here are some key factors that make Drupal a popular choice:   Scalability: Drupal is highly scalable, allowing organizations to handle large amounts of content, traffic, and user interactions. Its flexible architecture and robust performance capabilities enable it to accommodate the complex needs of large-scale websites and applic</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 05 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-drupal-chosen-by-large-organizations.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Drupal LMS Features for Your Education Business</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re running an education business and considering Drupal as the platform for your Learning Management System (LMS), there are several features and capabilities you should look for to ensure a robust and effective solution.  Here are some key Drupal LMS features to consider:   Course Management: A Drupal LMS should provide comprehensive course management capabilities. This includes the ab</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 May 2023 09:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/drupal-lms-features-for-your-education-business.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Leveraging Content Grouping for Personalized Digital Experiences</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</link>
			<description>Content grouping is a powerful technique that can be leveraged to create personalized digital experiences for users. By grouping content based on specific criteria, such as user preferences, demographics, or behavior, you can deliver targeted and relevant content to individual users. Here are some ways to utilize content grouping for personalized digital experiences:   User Segmentation: Segment y</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Colima, similar tool like Docker Desktop, for Drupal Development</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</link>
			<description>Colima is a project that is easy to use and fully open source, and it helps in running docker containers on Linux OS and MacOs machines.  We know Docker Desktop is no more a complete open source, if you are not using it personally. So now Colima is a tool which does work similar to Docker Desktop and In this article we are going to see how it works alone or along with Docker Desktop on your Linux </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What to Know for Estimating Projects</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-for-estimating-projects.html</link>
			<description>Estimating projects is part of project management. And we can’t always estimate a project with 100% accuracy. There will be learning from the failed attempts at estimating projects, maybe with running overtime, or with budget, or with resources etc.
                            If one needs to deliver a project successfully then one must estimate the project as better as possible.
               </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-for-estimating-projects.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>