<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Software - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/software.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Leveraging Content Grouping for Personalized Digital Experiences</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</link>
			<description>Content grouping is a powerful technique that can be leveraged to create personalized digital experiences for users. By grouping content based on specific criteria, such as user preferences, demographics, or behavior, you can deliver targeted and relevant content to individual users. Here are some ways to utilize content grouping for personalized digital experiences:   User Segmentation: Segment y</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/leveraging-content-grouping-for-personalized-digital-experiences.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Colima, similar tool like Docker Desktop, for Drupal Development</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</link>
			<description>Colima is a project that is easy to use and fully open source, and it helps in running docker containers on Linux OS and MacOs machines.  We know Docker Desktop is no more a complete open source, if you are not using it personally. So now Colima is a tool which does work similar to Docker Desktop and In this article we are going to see how it works alone or along with Docker Desktop on your Linux </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 31 Dec 2022 14:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/colima-similar-tool-like-docker-desktop-for-drupal-development.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What to Know for Estimating Projects</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-for-estimating-projects.html</link>
			<description>Estimating projects is part of project management. And we can’t always estimate a project with 100% accuracy. There will be learning from the failed attempts at estimating projects, maybe with running overtime, or with budget, or with resources etc.
                            If one needs to deliver a project successfully then one must estimate the project as better as possible.
               </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-to-know-for-estimating-projects.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>