<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Solar Energy - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar-energy.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Optimal placement of solar panels for better observation of solar energy</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimal-placement-of-solar-panels-for-better-observation-of-solar-energy.html</link>
			<description>Optimal panel placement is crucial for maximizing energy production from your solar panel system. Here are some key considerations:   Orientation: In the Northern Hemisphere, panels should face true south to capture the maximum amount of sunlight throughout the day. In the Southern Hemisphere, panels should face true north. Tilt Angle: The tilt angle of the panels should be approximately equal to </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 17:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/optimal-placement-of-solar-panels-for-better-observation-of-solar-energy.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Choose the Inverters which are more efficient to work with Solar panels?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/choose-the-inverters-which-are-more-efficient-to-work-with-solar-panels.html</link>
			<description>Selecting an efficient inverter is crucial for maximizing the energy production of your solar panel system.  Here are key considerations for choosing an efficient solar inverter:   Type of Inverter:   String Inverters: These are connected to multiple solar panels in a series. They are cost-effective but the performance of the whole string can be affected if one panel is shaded or underperforming. </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Nov 2023 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/choose-the-inverters-which-are-more-efficient-to-work-with-solar-panels.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to choose solar panels which are more efficient?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-choose-solar-panels-which-are-more-efficient.html</link>
			<description>Choosing efficient solar panels is crucial for maximizing the energy production of your solar system.  Here are some key factors to consider when selecting high-efficiency solar panels:   Conversion Efficiency:   Look for panels with a high conversion efficiency. This indicates the percentage of sunlight that the panel can convert into electricity. Higher efficiency panels will generate more power</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 13:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-choose-solar-panels-which-are-more-efficient.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Technical information to know about the Solar energy setup for your home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/technical-information-to-know-about-the-solar-energy-setup-for-your-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a solar power system for your home is a sustainable and environmentally-friendly way to generate electricity  Here are some key technical details to understand when setting up a solar energy system for your home:   Solar Panels (Photovoltaic Modules):   Capacity (Wattage): The power output of each panel, typically ranging from 250 to 400 watts. Efficiency: The percentage of sunlight tha</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 23 Oct 2023 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/technical-information-to-know-about-the-solar-energy-setup-for-your-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to setup solar power for you home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-setup-solar-power-for-you-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a solar power system for a family of four in India involves several steps. Please note that the costs provided are approximate and can vary based on factors like location, system size, quality of components and labor costs.  Additionally, government incentives and rebates can affect the final cost.  Step-by-Step Guide:  Step 1: Assess Your Energy Needs   Determine Your Energy Consumptio</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2023 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-setup-solar-power-for-you-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Complete Guide to Setup and Usage Solar Panels at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Going green is the best of the environment and if you are planning to go green, then we all know Sun is the non-renewable energy and we could use this energy for people&amp;#39;s survival. We have a few articles at PeoplesBLOG related to the Environment and going green, have a check of them.  Using the Electricity from Solar energy is one of the best combinations, because there is not much waste out o</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cooking Food with Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
			<description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to charge a Mobile phone with Solar power?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>As the world shifts toward renewable energy, solar power is becoming an increasingly practical and eco-friendly way to charge everyday devices&amp;mdash;especially mobile phones. Whether you&amp;#39;re off the grid, on a camping trip, or simply looking to reduce your environmental impact, solar charging offers a convenient solution.  This article will walk you through how to charge your phone using solar </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>