<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Solar Energy - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Solar-Energy.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Complete Guide to Setup and Usage Solar Panels at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</link>
			<description>Going green is the best of the environment and if you are planning to go green, then we all know Sun is the non-renewable energy and we could use this energy for people&amp;#39;s survival. We have a few articles at PeoplesBLOG related to the Environment and going green, have a check of them.  Using the Electricity from Solar energy is one of the best combinations, because there is not much waste out o</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2022 17:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/complete-guide-to-setup-and-usage-solar-panels-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cooking Food with Solar Power at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</link>
			<description>On PeoplesBLOG, we were writing articles related to Eco friendly homes and how to use Solar energy and along the same lines, in this article we are going to see how people can cook their food with Solar energy.  Generally majority of the people nowadays use Gas stoves for Cooking at home and Solar is one of the best case of the replacement for this. People can make a major change on the Environmen</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cooking-food-with-solar-power-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to charge a Mobile phone with Solar power?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see what all options we have to charge a mobile phone with Solar power.  If you are going on treks which are primarily overnight or a few days of trek in some isolated place. In such cases obviously we won&amp;rsquo;t get any electrical power, In such cases for people Solar energy would be an alternative option to keep your device charged.  And let&amp;rsquo;s see what all</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>