<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Solar - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solar.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>How to maintain solar panel setup at your home to get the best results?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-maintain-solar-panel-setup-at-your-home-to-get-the-best-results.html</link>
			<description>Maintaining your solar panel setup is important to ensure it continues to operate efficiently and generate the maximum amount of energy.  Here are some steps you can take to maintain your home solar panel system:  Regular Cleaning:   Frequency: Depending on your location and climate, aim to clean your solar panels 2-4 times a year. More frequent cleaning may be needed in areas with high dust, poll</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 11:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-maintain-solar-panel-setup-at-your-home-to-get-the-best-results.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to set up a Monitoring System for the Solar panel at your home?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-set-up-a-monitoring-system-for-the-solar-panel-at-your-home.html</link>
			<description>Setting up a monitoring system for your solar panel system allows you to track its performance and ensure it&amp;#39;s operating at its best.  Here&amp;#39;s how you can do it:  1. Choose a Monitoring System:  There are various monitoring options available, ranging from basic to advanced:   Manufacturer&amp;#39;s Monitoring: Many solar panel and inverter manufacturers offer their own monitoring platforms or a</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 2024 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-set-up-a-monitoring-system-for-the-solar-panel-at-your-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What is Charge Controller &amp; how to use it with a Solar panel setup at home?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-charge-controller-and-how-to-use-it-with-a-solar-panel-setup-at-home.html</link>
			<description>A charge controller, also known as a charge regulator, is a crucial component in a solar panel system. Its primary function is to regulate the voltage and current coming from the solar panels and going to the battery bank.  Here&amp;#39;s how to use a charge controller in a home solar panel setup:  Purpose of a Charge Controller:   Prevents Overcharging: Charge controllers prevent overcharging of batt</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 10:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-charge-controller-and-how-to-use-it-with-a-solar-panel-setup-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best Batteries to use with the Solar panels for home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-batteries-to-use-with-the-solar-panels-for-home.html</link>
			<description>When it comes to choosing batteries for a solar panel system, several options are available. The best battery for your home will depend on factors like budget, energy requirements, available space and desired lifespan.  Here are some of the most common types:   Lithium-Ion Batteries:  Advantages:  High energy density, which means they can store a lot of energy in a relatively small space. Long lif</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2023 10:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-batteries-to-use-with-the-solar-panels-for-home.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>