<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Solo - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Bangalore to Munnar Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-munnar-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Munnar can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the picturesque tea plantations, misty hills, and serene lakes of this charming hill station in Kerala. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey,  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Dindigul -&amp;gt; Munnar -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Salem -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Munnar   Start your trip early i</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-munnar-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kodaikanal Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kodaikanal-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Kodaikanal can be a wonderful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the misty hills, scenic landscapes, and serene lakes of this charming hill station.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Dindigul -&amp;gt; Kodaikanal -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Salem -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Kodaikanal   Start your trip early in the m</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 17:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kodaikanal-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Wayanad Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-wayanad-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>A solo trip from Bangalore to Wayanad can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the natural beauty and tranquility of this hill station in Kerala. Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your journey:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Mysuru -&amp;gt; Gundlupete -&amp;gt; Wayanad -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Mysuru -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Wayanad   Start your journey early in the morning from Bangal</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-wayanad-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Hyderabad Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hyderabad-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Planning a trip from Bangalore to Hyderabad can be an exciting adventure! One day trip or Two day trip from Bengaluru to Hyderabad, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in Hyderabad.  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Anantapur -&amp;gt; Kurnool -&amp;gt; Hyderabad -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-hyderabad-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kukke-subramanya-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Planning a trip from Bangalore to Kukke Subramanya? That&amp;#39;s a great choice! One day trip or Two day trip from Bengaluru to Kukke Subramanya, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in Kukke Subramanya.  Kukke Subramanya is a popular pilgrimage destination in Karnataka known for its ancient templ</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 18 May 2023 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kukke-subramanya-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bengaluru to BR Hills and KGudi Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bengaluru-to-br-hills-and-kgudi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One day trip or Two day trip from Bengaluru to BR Hills and KGudi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover places in BR Hills and KGudi.  BR Hills is a Hill range, also a tiger reserve, also a temple of Lord Ranganathaswamy which attracts people to visit BR Hills. Once in two years, the Soliga Tribals pre</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Feb 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bengaluru-to-br-hills-and-kgudi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mysore Solo Trip plan (2 Days + 1 Night)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</link>
			<description>Two days Ride from&amp;nbsp;Bangalore to Mysore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for two days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Chamundeshwari</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kochi Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from&amp;nbsp;Bangalore&amp;nbsp;to Kochi, If you are&amp;nbsp;Solo&amp;nbsp;riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Kochi and one couple more quick visits in Mysore, Ooty and Coimbatore on the way.  Kochi, called as&amp;nbsp;Queen of the Arabian Sea, is one of the major port cities in the coast of India and also has </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jun 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kochi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Srisailam Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Srisailam, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well to cover Srisailam and one more Shakti Peethas on the way.  Srisailam is one of the places where people get to visit Lord Mallikarjuna (one of the Jyotirlinga) and Goddess Bhramaramba (one of the Ashtadasa Shakti Peetha) in</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2022 13:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srisailam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Pondicherry Solo Trip plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-pondicherry-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two to Three days trip from Bangalore to Pondicherry, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this two to three days plan works very well.  Among the touristers Pondicherry is famous for its rich French essence of architecture of buildings in the White town area. Also it&amp;#39;s famous for beaches and it&amp;#39;s one of the good places for Solo travelers. Let&amp;#3</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 04 Dec 2022 16:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-pondicherry-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Lepakshi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One day trip from Bangalore to Lepakshi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this one day plan works very well.  Lepakshi is a small village located in Anantapur district, Andhra Pradesh. It is around 120 KM from Bangalore. It is famous for Veerabhadra temple, one of the oldest temples in India. The temple has Ganesha, Nandi, Veerabhadra, Shiva, Bhadrak</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Everest Base Camp Trek, Start Trekking from Salleri and back to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of where you can start your trek. I have read through many articles &amp;amp; videos and found the best route for trekking.  Generally people all over the world will reach Kathmandu and then take a flight to Lukla and start the trek to Everest base camp from Lukla.  In case you are n</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, Bangalore to Kathmandu then to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to trek Solo to Everest Base Camp by yourself from Bangalore, then this article will help you to get a picture of how to reach Salleri from Bangalore, where Salleri will be the starting point of Trek to Everest Base Camp.  There are many possible routes to reach Kathmandu from Bangalore.   Flight  There are direct flights from Bangalore to Kathmandu and vice versa. You also hav</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Travel to Gokarna for Three Nights and Four Days</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</link>
			<description>You are planning to visit Gokarna solo then here is the article which will help you to plan your trip. And this plan in this article is for three days and four nights and for a person who wants to travel solo.  If you are traveling from Bangalore, overnight bus or a train will be the best option for travel to Gokarna. And if you wish to travel via flight, the nearest airport for people will be eit</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tips for Night Driving on Motorcycle on Roads and Highways</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-for-night-driving-on-motorcycle-on-roads-and-highways.html</link>
			<description>Driving during night will have few advantages and yes it comes with being very careful and prepared as well. And sharing this article particularly for the Motorcycle riders.  Night driving will have few advantages for people, like no need to worry about the huge traffic because most of the people will be sleeping, And you will not get tired like you get tired in the daytime, And most of the night </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-for-night-driving-on-motorcycle-on-roads-and-highways.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, What to pack?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of what you might need to pack in your backpack. Packing proper equipment, clothing &amp;amp; quick energy foods will help you to do your trek bit smoothly.  One more important thing, is this plan would fit for the people who are willing to trek solo (without a porter), so what you a</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2022 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>