<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Spiritual - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/spiritual.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>The Journey from Self to Soul</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-journey-from-self-to-soul.html</link>
			<description>Beloved seekers of truth,  Life is not merely the rising and setting of the sun, nor the endless pursuit of worldly desires. Life is a sacred pilgrimage &amp;mdash; a journey from the self that clings to the body and mind, to the soul that is eternal, pure, and boundless. To walk this path is to awaken to the truth of who we are and why we are here.  The Nature of the Self  The self, as most understan</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 26 Sep 2025 13:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-journey-from-self-to-soul.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Karma and Dharma: Balancing Duty and Destiny</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/karma-and-dharma-balancing-duty-and-destiny.html</link>
			<description>Beloved seekers of truth,  In this journey of life, two great forces silently shape our every step &amp;mdash; Karma and Dharma. These are not just words from our sacred scriptures; they are eternal principles woven into the fabric of existence. To understand them is to understand the dance of destiny and duty, action and consequence, the seen and the unseen.  The Law of Karma  Karma is the echo of ou</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 18 Aug 2025 12:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/karma-and-dharma-balancing-duty-and-destiny.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vedic Philosophy: The Foundation of Indian Thought</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vedic-philosophy-the-foundation-of-indian-thought.html</link>
			<description>Vedic philosophy comes from the ancient Vedas, which are some of the oldest Hindu scriptures. These texts, written between 1500 and 500 BCE, explore deep ideas about life, the universe, and human purpose. This article explains the key ideas of Vedic philosophy and how they continue to influence Indian thought and spirituality.  The Vedas: The Base of Vedic Philosophy  What Are the Vedas?   The Ved</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 20 Mar 2025 17:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vedic-philosophy-the-foundation-of-indian-thought.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Comparing the Vedas with Other Ancient Scriptures</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/comparing-the-vedas-with-other-ancient-scriptures.html</link>
			<description>The Vedas are among the oldest and most respected religious texts, forming the foundation of Hinduism and influencing Indian culture. However, many other ancient scriptures also played key roles in shaping different civilizations. This article compares the Vedas with texts from Mesopotamia, Egypt, Greece, China, and Israel, highlighting their similarities and differences.  Understanding the Vedas </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 13 Mar 2025 18:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/comparing-the-vedas-with-other-ancient-scriptures.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Mantras and Chants: Their Role in Vedic Rituals</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mantras-and-chants-their-role-in-vedic-rituals.html</link>
			<description>Mantras and chants hold a central place in Vedic rituals, embodying the profound spiritual and symbolic dimensions of ancient Hindu practices. These sacred utterances, derived from the Vedic texts, are more than mere sounds; they are considered powerful tools for invoking divine energies, maintaining cosmic order and achieving spiritual goals.  This article explores the significance of mantras and</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2025 07:32:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/mantras-and-chants-their-role-in-vedic-rituals.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Vedas and the Development of Yoga</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-vedas-and-the-development-of-yoga.html</link>
			<description>Yoga, a spiritual and physical discipline, has deep roots in the ancient Vedic texts of Hinduism. Originating in the early Vedic period, yoga has evolved significantly over millennia, intertwining with various philosophical and religious traditions.  This article explores the connection between the Vedas and the development of yoga, tracing its origins, evolution and enduring significance.  Origin</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2025 07:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-vedas-and-the-development-of-yoga.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Importance of the Vedas in Modern Hinduism</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-importance-of-the-vedas-in-modern-hinduism.html</link>
			<description>The Vedas are ancient sacred texts of Hinduism that form the foundation of Hindu religion and philosophy. Written in early Sanskrit more than 3,000 years ago, these texts are not just historical artifacts but living sources of spiritual wisdom. They continue to influence Hindu beliefs, practices, and culture today. This article explores how the Vedas shape modern Hinduism, impacting rituals, philo</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-importance-of-the-vedas-in-modern-hinduism.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Cosmology and Creation in the Vedas</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cosmology-and-creation-in-the-vedas.html</link>
			<description>The Vedic gods are central to the ancient Indian texts called the Vedas. These deities symbolize natural forces, cosmic laws, and divine qualities. They are deeply connected to rituals and hymns, highlighting the relationship between the divine and the natural world.  Here&amp;#39;s a breakdown of major Vedic gods, their roles, and their significance:  Key Vedic Gods and Their Roles  Agni (God of Fire</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2024 08:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/cosmology-and-creation-in-the-vedas.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Vedic Gods and Their Attributes</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-vedic-gods-and-their-attributes.html</link>
			<description>The Vedic gods, who come from the ancient religious texts called the Vedas, represent different natural forces, cosmic principles and divine qualities. These gods are very important in Vedic rituals, hymns and beliefs, showing a close link between the divine world and nature.  This article introduces some major Vedic gods, their characteristics and their roles in Vedic beliefs.  Main Vedic Gods an</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-vedic-gods-and-their-attributes.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vedic Rituals and Sacrifices: An Overview</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vedic-rituals-and-sacrifices-an-overview.html</link>
			<description>Vedic rituals and sacrifices, also called yajnas, are key practices in Vedic religion and Hinduism. They have their roots in ancient Vedic texts and involve elaborate ceremonies intended to honor gods, keep the universe in balance and achieve both spiritual and worldly goals. This article explains what Vedic rituals are, their purposes, how they are performed and why they are important in Vedic tr</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vedic-rituals-and-sacrifices-an-overview.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Concept of Dharma in the Vedas</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-concept-of-dharma-in-the-vedas.html</link>
			<description>The concept of dharma is central to Hindu philosophy and is rooted in the ancient texts called the Vedas. Dharma is a term that holds many meanings, ranging from the cosmic order of the universe to an individual&amp;#39;s personal duties in life. It is a principle that guides people to live righteously, follow moral codes and maintain ethical behavior. Dharma also plays an essential role in shaping th</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:45:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-concept-of-dharma-in-the-vedas.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vedic Hymns and their Significance</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vedic-hymns-and-their-significance.html</link>
			<description>Vedic hymns, also called &amp;quot;suktas&amp;quot; are important parts of the Vedas, which are ancient scriptures of Hinduism. Written in early Sanskrit, these hymns are not just poems; they represent the spiritual, philosophical and ritual aspects of Vedic traditions.  This article looks at the nature of Vedic hymns, how they are composed and their significance in rituals, philosophy and culture.  Compo</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:47:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vedic-hymns-and-their-significance.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Understanding the four Vedas - Rigveda, Samaveda, Yajurveda and Atharvaveda</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-four-vedas-rigveda-samaveda-yajurveda-and-atharvaveda.html</link>
			<description>The Vedas are the most ancient and revered texts in Hinduism, foundational to its rituals, philosophy and cosmology. Composed in early Sanskrit, these texts were transmitted orally for centuries before being written down. The Vedas are traditionally categorized into four distinct collections: the Rigveda, Samaveda, Yajurveda and Atharvaveda. Each Veda serves a unique purpose and contributes to the</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/understanding-the-four-vedas-rigveda-samaveda-yajurveda-and-atharvaveda.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vedic Sanskrit, Language and Structure</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vedic-sanskrit-language-and-structure.html</link>
			<description>Vedic Sanskrit is the ancient form of the Sanskrit language used primarily in the Vedic texts, including the four Vedas: the Rigveda, Samaveda, Yajurveda and Atharvaveda. It represents one of the earliest attested stages of the Indo-European language family and holds significant importance in the study of ancient Indian history, linguistics and religious traditions.  This article explores the lang</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:51:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vedic-sanskrit-language-and-structure.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Historical Context of the Vedas</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-historical-context-of-the-vedas.html</link>
			<description>The Vedas, the sacred texts of ancient Hinduism, are considered some of the oldest religious writings in human history. To fully understand their significance, it is crucial to explore their historical context, the era in which they were composed, the socio-political environment of ancient India and their impact on subsequent cultures and religious practices.  Vedic Period  The Vedic period, durin</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:52:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-historical-context-of-the-vedas.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Introduction to the Vedas: The Oldest Sacred Texts</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-the-vedas-the-oldest-sacred-texts.html</link>
			<description>Introduction  The Vedas are revered as the oldest &amp;amp; most foundational sacred texts of Hinduism, forming the bedrock of Vedic tradition and Indian philosophy. Composed in ancient Sanskrit, these texts offer profound insights into the spiritual, philosophical and ritualistic aspects of early Indian civilization. This article delves into the Vedas origins, structure, significance and impact on Hi</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2024 08:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Krishna D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/introduction-to-the-vedas-the-oldest-sacred-texts.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>