<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Temple - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/temple.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Defiance of Gravity at Lepakshi Temple, Andhra Pradesh</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/defiance-of-gravity-at-lepakshi-temple-andhra-pradesh.html</link>
			<description>Nestled in the small town of Lepakshi in Andhra Pradesh lies one of India&amp;rsquo;s most intriguing architectural enigmas&amp;mdash;the Veerabhadra Temple, a masterpiece of the Vijayanagara period. Built in the 16th century by the brothers Viranna and Virupanna, this temple is renowned not only for its exquisite carvings and mural paintings but also for its mystifying hanging pillar&amp;mdash;a stone column</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 10:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/defiance-of-gravity-at-lepakshi-temple-andhra-pradesh.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Enigma of the Unfinished Kailasa Temple, Ellora</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-enigma-of-the-unfinished-kailasa-temple-ellora.html</link>
			<description>The Kailasa Temple at Ellora, carved from a single massive rock in Maharashtra, India, stands as one of the greatest architectural and engineering marvels of the ancient world. Dedicated to Lord Shiva, the temple forms part of the Ellora Caves, a UNESCO World Heritage Site. Unlike most temples that were built by adding material, this one was created through monolithic excavation&amp;mdash;workers remo</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-enigma-of-the-unfinished-kailasa-temple-ellora.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tiruttani Solo Travel Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruttani-solo-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Tiruttani is a significant pilgrimage destination in Tamil Nadu, known for its ancient temple dedicated to Lord Murugan. As a solo traveler, you&amp;#39;ll have the opportunity to immerse yourself in the spiritual ambiance of the temple town, explore its cultural heritage and witness the rituals and traditions firsthand.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested solo travel plan:  Arrival in Tiruttani   Depart from Ban</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 07:39:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruttani-solo-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>