<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Travel - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/travel.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Bangalore to Lepakshi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One day trip from Bangalore to Lepakshi, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in a Car, then this one day plan works very well.  Lepakshi is a small village located in Anantapur district, Andhra Pradesh. It is around 120 KM from Bangalore. It is famous for Veerabhadra temple, one of the oldest temples in India. The temple has Ganesha, Nandi, Veerabhadra, Shiva, Bhadrak</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 14 Nov 2022 13:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-lepakshi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Everest Base Camp Trek, Start Trekking from Salleri and back to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of where you can start your trek. I have read through many articles &amp;amp; videos and found the best route for trekking.  Generally people all over the world will reach Kathmandu and then take a flight to Lukla and start the trek to Everest base camp from Lukla.  In case you are n</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 11 Nov 2022 15:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dharmasthala Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>One or Two days Trip from Bangalore to Dharmasthala to Bangalore, If you are Solo riding on a MotorBike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this one or two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.  Dharmasthala is a small Hindu </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 07 Nov 2022 18:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dharmasthala-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, Bangalore to Kathmandu then to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to trek Solo to Everest Base Camp by yourself from Bangalore, then this article will help you to get a picture of how to reach Salleri from Bangalore, where Salleri will be the starting point of Trek to Everest Base Camp.  There are many possible routes to reach Kathmandu from Bangalore.   Flight  There are direct flights from Bangalore to Kathmandu and vice versa. You also hav</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Travel to Gokarna for Three Nights and Four Days</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</link>
			<description>You are planning to visit Gokarna solo then here is the article which will help you to plan your trip. And this plan in this article is for three days and four nights and for a person who wants to travel solo.  If you are traveling from Bangalore, overnight bus or a train will be the best option for travel to Gokarna. And if you wish to travel via flight, the nearest airport for people will be eit</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 19:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Tips for Night Driving on Motorcycle on Roads and Highways</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-for-night-driving-on-motorcycle-on-roads-and-highways.html</link>
			<description>Driving during night will have few advantages and yes it comes with being very careful and prepared as well. And sharing this article particularly for the Motorcycle riders.  Night driving will have few advantages for people, like no need to worry about the huge traffic because most of the people will be sleeping, And you will not get tired like you get tired in the daytime, And most of the night </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 14:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/tips-for-night-driving-on-motorcycle-on-roads-and-highways.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, What to pack?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of what you might need to pack in your backpack. Packing proper equipment, clothing &amp;amp; quick energy foods will help you to do your trek bit smoothly.  One more important thing, is this plan would fit for the people who are willing to trek solo (without a porter), so what you a</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to charge a Mobile phone with Solar power?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see what all options we have to charge a mobile phone with Solar power.  If you are going on treks which are primarily overnight or a few days of trek in some isolated place. In such cases obviously we won&amp;rsquo;t get any electrical power, In such cases for people Solar energy would be an alternative option to keep your device charged.  And let&amp;rsquo;s see what all</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Makalidurga - Trekking</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</link>
			<description>One-day trek from Bangalore to Makalidurga to Bangalore. If you are a couple riding on a Bike or you are a Family driving in a Car, then this trek plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. Makalidurga is a hill fort situated 60 km north of Bangalore. The fort at the summit has an old temple of Shiva with Nandi and in legend, Markandeya Rishi performed penan</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Gandikota (Two Days and One Night, Trip Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-gandikota-two-days-one-night-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Two Days Trip from Bangalore to Gandikota to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on a Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly.
                            A couple of the best places you can visit on the way or around are Lakshmi Narasimha Swamy temple in Kadiri &amp; Belum Caves in Kolimigundla.
  </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jul 2022 12:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-gandikota-two-days-one-night-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Precautions while travelling during Coronavirus times</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/precautions-while-travelling-during-coronavirus-times.html</link>
			<description>It is not completely safe to travel during the Coronavirus times. Although the mortality rate of the people affected with COVID appears to be quite low, there is always a chance with the data which we get in our country. I see one should avoid travelling as much as possible so that we reduce the chances of spreading the virus.
                                Following are some of the things to be </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/precautions-while-travelling-during-coronavirus-times.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tirumala (2 Days + 1 Night)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tirumala-two-days-trip.html</link>
			<description>Two days Trip from Bangalore to Tirumala to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on bike or you are a family driving in car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. You can book the Dharshna Tickets &amp; Stay via Online Booking or you can get it once you reach their based on the Crowd on Tirumala.
                                Tirumala </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tirumala-two-days-trip.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Rameswaram (3 Days + 2 Nights, Trip Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Three days Trip from Bangalore to Rameswaram to Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Rameshwaram is a small Hindu pilgrimage town a</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 14:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Ooty (3 Days + 2 Nights, Trip Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</link>
			<description>Three days Trip from Bangalore  Ooty  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Ooty known as the Queen of the hill stations in South In</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/three-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-ooty.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore -> Murdeshwar -> Gokarna -> Goa -> Dandeli -> Bangalore</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-murdeshwar-gokarna-goa-dandeli.html</link>
			<description>Ten days Ride from Bangalore  Murdeshwar  Gokarna  Goa  Dandeli  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for ten days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.
       </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-murdeshwar-gokarna-goa-dandeli.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Ghati Subramanya (Morning Ride Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/short-trip-from-bangalore-to-ghati.html</link>
			<description>Ghati Subramanya is an ancient Hindu temple, 50 kms away from Bangalore towards Doddaballapur situated on the outskirts of Bangalore. Ghati Subramanya has a recorded history of more than 600 years. Ghati Subramanya Temple was first developed by the Ghorpade rulers of Sandur who ruled parts of Bellary.
                                The uniqueness of this temple is the prime deity "Lord Karthikeya</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/short-trip-from-bangalore-to-ghati.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mysore (2 Days + 1 Night, Ride Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</link>
			<description>Two days Ride from Bangalore  Mysore  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for two days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.
                                Ro</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/two-days-trip-from-bangalore-to-mysore.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>