<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Travel - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/travel.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Bangalore to Talakadu Historical Site – A Couple Motorcycle Ride Travel Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-talakadu-historical-site-a-couple-motorcycle-ride-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Talakadu, on the banks of the river Kaveri, is a fascinating blend of history, mythology, and natural beauty. Once a flourishing city with more than 30 temples, Talakadu is today partly buried under shifting sand dunes, earning it the name &amp;ldquo;The Desert of Karnataka.&amp;rdquo; For a couple riding out of Bangalore on a motorcycle, this trip is the perfect mix of adventure, romance, and heritage. T</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Sep 2025 09:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-talakadu-historical-site-a-couple-motorcycle-ride-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kanipakam Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanipakam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Kanipakam, located in Chittoor district of Andhra Pradesh, is a renowned pilgrimage destination famous for the Sri Varasiddhi Vinayaka Temple. Known for its divine atmosphere and spiritual significance, the temple attracts devotees from across South India. A solo trip from Bangalore to Kanipakam is perfect for those seeking peace, devotion, and personal reflection.  Route from Bangalore to Kanipak</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 23 Aug 2025 11:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanipakam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Kadri Manjunatha Temple vs Dharmasthala Manjunatha Temple – History, Spiritual Importance, and Travel Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/kadri-manjunatha-temple-vs-dharmasthala-manjunatha-temple-history-spiritual-importance-and-travel-guide.html</link>
			<description>Historical Background  When it comes to Lord Manjunatha worship in Karnataka, two major temples often come to mind: Kadri Manjunatha Temple in Mangaluru and Dharmasthala Manjunatha Temple in Dakshina Kannada district.   Kadri Manjunatha Temple is historically older, dating back to at least the 10th&amp;ndash;11th century CE. Its roots are linked to early Buddhist and Nath traditions before evolving in</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Aug 2025 12:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/kadri-manjunatha-temple-vs-dharmasthala-manjunatha-temple-history-spiritual-importance-and-travel-guide.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tiruvannamalai Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruvannamalai-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Tiruvannamalai, a sacred town in Tamil Nadu, is renowned for the Arunachaleswarar Temple and the spiritual aura that surrounds the holy Arunachala hill. Just 200 km from Bangalore, it makes for a serene solo getaway&amp;mdash;whether you&amp;rsquo;re seeking divine connection, introspection, or a peaceful retreat in nature. Here&amp;rsquo;s your complete solo travel guide from Bangalore to Tiruvannamalai.  Ro</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 11 Jul 2025 17:02:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruvannamalai-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Savandurga Rock Trek – Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-savandurga-rock-trek-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Savandurga, known as one of the largest monolith hills in Asia, is a popular trekking destination located just 60 km from Bangalore. With its rugged trails, panoramic views, and historical ruins, it offers an ideal solo trekking experience for adventure lovers and nature enthusiasts alike. Whether you&amp;#39;re seeking a quick escape or a physical challenge, this guide will help you plan your solo ad</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 14:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-savandurga-rock-trek-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mekedatu Gorge Adventure Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mekedatu-gorge-adventure-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Mekedatu, meaning &amp;ldquo;Goat&amp;rsquo;s Leap&amp;rdquo; in Kannada, is a breathtaking gorge where the Cauvery River flows through narrow rock formations. Located about 100 km from Bangalore, it is an excellent destination for a solo adventure, offering stunning landscapes, river views, and an exciting trek. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for an escape into nature, this guide will help you plan a seamless journ</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 24 Mar 2025 09:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mekedatu-gorge-adventure-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Time Travel Possibilities in Quantum Physics</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/time-travel-possibilities-in-quantum-physics.html</link>
			<description>Time travel has long been a fascination in science fiction, but could it actually be possible? While classical physics suggests that time flows in a straight line from past to future, quantum physics introduces concepts that challenge our understanding of time. Some physicists believe that time travel might not only be possible but may already be happening at a microscopic level. In this article, </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/time-travel-possibilities-in-quantum-physics.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Chennai to Vedanthangal Bird Sanctuary Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/chennai-to-vedanthangal-bird-sanctuary-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Vedanthangal Bird Sanctuary, located in Tamil Nadu, is one of the oldest bird sanctuaries in India. Just 80 kilometers from Chennai, it is a paradise for bird watchers and nature enthusiasts. This sanctuary is home to a variety of migratory birds and provides a tranquil escape from the city&amp;rsquo;s hustle and bustle.  If you&amp;rsquo;re planning a solo trip, here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed guide to help you </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 19 Jan 2025 07:25:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/chennai-to-vedanthangal-bird-sanctuary-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ahmedabad to Shamlaji: Temple Pilgrimage</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ahmedabad-to-shamlaji-temple-pilgrimage.html</link>
			<description>The Shamlaji Temple, also known as the Shamlaji Vishnu Mandir, is one of Gujarat&amp;#39;s most revered pilgrimage sites. Nestled amidst the picturesque Aravalli Hills, the temple is dedicated to Lord Vishnu and attracts thousands of devotees each year. Located about 120 kilometers from Ahmedabad, Shamlaji Temple is a perfect destination for a peaceful spiritual retreat.  Here&amp;rsquo;s a detailed artic</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 13 Jan 2025 09:31:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ahmedabad-to-shamlaji-temple-pilgrimage.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Jaipur to Tonk: Exploring the City of Havelis</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jaipur-to-tonk-exploring-the-city-of-havelis.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re in Jaipur and looking for a short, historical getaway, Tonk, known as the &amp;quot;City of Havelis,&amp;quot; is an ideal destination. This quaint town, just 96 kilometers from Jaipur, is rich in cultural heritage and showcases the grandeur of Rajasthani architecture. Whether you&amp;#39;re a history enthusiast, an architecture lover, or someone looking for a peaceful retreat, Tonk has somethin</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 07:38:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/jaipur-to-tonk-exploring-the-city-of-havelis.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kanakapura, Kayaking Spot: A Perfect Day Trip Guide</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanakapura-kayaking-spot-a-perfect-day-trip-guide.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re looking for an adventurous escape from Bangalore, Kanakapura is an ideal destination. Located just 55 kilometers from the city, this serene spot offers exciting kayaking experiences amid lush greenery and scenic landscapes.  In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll go over everything you need to know about making the most out of a day trip from Bangalore to Kanakapura, including the route, itine</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 15:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kanakapura-kayaking-spot-a-perfect-day-trip-guide.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How can I meet new people when traveling alone?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-meet-new-people-when-traveling-alone.html</link>
			<description>Meeting new people while traveling alone can make your trip more exciting and create wonderful memories.  Here are some great ways to connect with others during your solo travels:  1. Stay in Social Places   Hostels:   Hostels are perfect for solo travelers. They often have shared spaces like lounges or kitchens where guests can hang out. Join in on hostel activities, group outings, or simply chat</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 26 Sep 2024 09:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-meet-new-people-when-traveling-alone.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are the positives of traveling alone?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-positives-of-traveling-alone.html</link>
			<description>Traveling alone can be a transformative and enriching experience, offering a range of positives that contribute to personal growth, self-discovery and independence.  Here are some of the key benefits of traveling alone:  1. Self-Discovery and Personal Growth   Freedom to Explore: Traveling alone allows you to set your own pace, make your own decisions and explore places that genuinely interest you</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 11 Sep 2024 08:16:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-positives-of-traveling-alone.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are some inexpensive methods of traveling?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-inexpensive-methods-of-traveling.html</link>
			<description>Traveling on a budget can be a fulfilling and exciting experience.  Here are some inexpensive methods and tips to help you travel affordably:  1. Transportation  Flights   Flight Comparison Websites: Use sites like Skyscanner, Kayak&amp;nbsp;and Google Flights to compare prices and find the best deals. Budget Airlines: Consider flying with budget carriers like Ryanair, EasyJet&amp;nbsp;and Southwest Airli</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2024 06:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-inexpensive-methods-of-traveling.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why do people travel so much?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-travel-so-much.html</link>
			<description>People travel for a multitude of reasons, driven by various motivations and desires.  Here are some common reasons why people are passionate about traveling:  Exploration and Adventure   Curiosity: Many people have an innate curiosity about the world and a desire to explore new places, cultures and experiences. Adventure: Traveling offers opportunities for adventure, whether it&amp;#39;s hiking in rem</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 24 Aug 2024 14:11:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-do-people-travel-so-much.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How can I travel around the world with little money?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-travel-around-the-world-with-little-money.html</link>
			<description>Traveling around the world with little money requires careful planning, resourcefulness and a willingness to adapt to different circumstances.  Here are some strategies and tips to help you make the most of your budget:  1. Plan and Research Thoroughly   Budgeting: Set a realistic budget for your trip, including daily expenses, transportation, accommodation, food and activities. Destination Resear</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 17 Aug 2024 17:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-can-i-travel-around-the-world-with-little-money.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What is some good advice and tips for traveling alone?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-some-good-advice-and-tips-for-traveling-alone.html</link>
			<description>Traveling alone can be an incredibly rewarding experience, offering freedom, self-discovery and adventure.  Here are some tips and advice to ensure a safe, enjoyable and fulfilling solo travel experience:  Preparation and Planning   Research Your Destination:   Learn about the culture, customs and local laws. Identify safe neighborhoods and areas to avoid. Understand the local transportation syste</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2024 07:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-some-good-advice-and-tips-for-traveling-alone.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are the best jobs for traveling around the world?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-best-jobs-for-traveling-around-the-world.html</link>
			<description>If you&amp;#39;re looking to travel the world while earning an income, there are various jobs that offer the flexibility and opportunities to do so.  Here are some of the best jobs for travelers:  Remote and Freelance Jobs   Freelance Writing:   Pros: High demand for content creation, flexibility and ability to write about diverse topics including travel. Platforms: Upwork, Freelancer, Fiverr, Contena</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 07:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-best-jobs-for-traveling-around-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are some good tips and tricks to travel cheap?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-good-tips-and-tricks-to-travel-cheap.html</link>
			<description>Traveling on a budget can be both rewarding and challenging.  Here are some tips and tricks to help you travel cheaply while still having an enriching and enjoyable experience:  Planning and Preparation   Flexible Travel Dates:   Being flexible with your travel dates can help you find cheaper flights and accommodations. Use tools like Google Flights or Skyscanner to compare prices over a range of </description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2024 20:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-some-good-tips-and-tricks-to-travel-cheap.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What is it like to quit your job and travel the world?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-it-like-to-quit-your-job-and-travel-the-world.html</link>
			<description>Quitting your job to travel the world is a life-changing decision that can be both exhilarating and challenging.  Here&amp;#39;s an overview of what it might be like, based on the experiences of those who have taken the plunge:  The Initial Stages   Excitement and Anticipation:   The decision to quit your job and travel is often accompanied by a rush of excitement and anticipation. The idea of explori</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 29 Jul 2024 21:04:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-it-like-to-quit-your-job-and-travel-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are the best ways to earn money while traveling around the world?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-best-ways-to-earn-money-while-traveling-around-the-world.html</link>
			<description>Earning money while traveling around the world can be an exciting and fulfilling way to sustain your travel lifestyle.  Here are some of the best ways to earn money while on the road:  Remote Work   Freelancing:   Platforms: Freelancing involves working independently rather than being employed by a company, offering services to clients on a contract or project basis. It provides flexibility and th</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jun 2024 07:34:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-the-best-ways-to-earn-money-while-traveling-around-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Why is traveling so important in life?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-traveling-so-important-in-life.html</link>
			<description>Traveling is often considered a vital aspect of life for numerous reasons, encompassing personal growth, cultural understanding and overall well-being.  Here are some compelling reasons why traveling is so important:  Personal Growth and Development   Self-Discovery: Traveling provides opportunities for self-reflection and discovery. Being in new environments challenges you to step out of your com</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 23 Jun 2024 19:19:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/why-is-traveling-so-important-in-life.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten best hill stations to Travel Solo in North East of India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-north-east-of-india.html</link>
			<description>The North East of India is a treasure trove of natural beauty, cultural diversity and serene hill stations perfect for solo travelers.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in North East India for solo travel:   Shillong, Meghalaya   Known as the &amp;quot;Scotland of the East&amp;quot; Shillong offers lush green landscapes, waterfalls and a pleasant climate. Popular spots include Elephant Falls, Shillo</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 16:21:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-north-east-of-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten best hill stations to Travel Solo in North India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-north-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in North India can be an exhilarating experience with the stunning landscapes, rich culture and adventurous activities.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in North India for solo travelers:   Manali, Himachal Pradesh   Manali is a well-known destination for its breathtaking landscapes, adventure sports and vibrant culture. The Solang Valley and Rohtang Pass are</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 May 2024 13:47:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-north-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten best hill stations to Travel Solo in South India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in South India offers a unique blend of tranquility, adventure and scenic beauty.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in South India for solo travelers:   Munnar, Kerala   Known for its tea gardens, rolling hills and pleasant weather, Munnar is a great destination for solo travelers. The serene environment and numerous trekking trails make it ideal for exploring</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 May 2024 08:54:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten best beaches to Travel Solo in India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-beaches-to-travel-solo-in-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo can be a rewarding experience, offering freedom and the opportunity for self-discovery.  Here are ten of the best beaches in India for solo travelers:   Palolem Beach, Goa   Known for its stunning crescent shape and calm waters, Palolem is perfect for a peaceful solo retreat. The friendly vibe and numerous cafes make it easy to meet other travelers.   Varkala Beach, Kerala  Varkala </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2024 09:27:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-beaches-to-travel-solo-in-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Trivandrum Solo Travel Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-trivandrum-solo-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo from Bangalore to Trivandrum offers a wonderful opportunity to explore the cultural richness, natural beauty and vibrant atmosphere of Kerala&amp;#39;s capital city.  Here&amp;#39;s a solo travel plan for your trip:   Day 1: Arrival in Trivandrum   Arrive in Trivandrum by flight, train, or bus. Check into your accommodation and freshen up. Explore local attractions like Padmanabhaswamy Temp</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 May 2024 09:27:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-trivandrum-solo-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Dandeli Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dandeli-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Dandeli promises an exciting adventure amidst nature, wildlife and thrilling activities.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Day 1: Bangalore to Dandeli   Morning: Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Dandeli is approximately 460 kilometers and the drive tak</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 05 May 2024 12:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-dandeli-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Sakleshpur Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-sakleshpur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Sakleshpur offers an ideal getaway amidst the serene Western Ghats, lush greenery and pleasant weather.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Sakleshpur   Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to avoid traffic and make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Sakleshpur is approximately 220 kilom</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-sakleshpur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Chikmagalur Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chikmagalur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Chikmagalur promises a perfect blend of natural beauty, serene landscapes and rejuvenating experiences.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Chikmagalur   Start your journey early in the morning to avoid traffic and reach Chikmagalur with ample time. The distance between Bangalore and Chikmagalur is approximately 240 kilometers and the dri</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 27 Apr 2024 12:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chikmagalur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kovalam Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kovalam-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kovalam offers a perfect blend of relaxation, beach vibes and cultural experiences.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Salem -&amp;gt; Madurai -&amp;gt; Tirunelveli -&amp;gt; Nagercoil -&amp;gt; Kovalam  Bangalore to Kovalam   Departure from Bangalore   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between </description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 24 Apr 2024 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kovalam-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Travel to Rishikesh - Yoga Capital of the World</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-rishikesh-yoga-capital-of-the-world.html</link>
			<description>Solo travel to Rishikesh, known as the &amp;quot;Yoga Capital of the World,&amp;quot; can be a transformative journey offering opportunities for self-discovery, spiritual growth and adventure.  Here&amp;#39;s why, how and when to plan a solo trip to Rishikesh:  Why Solo Travel to Rishikesh:   Yoga and Meditation: Rishikesh is renowned for its numerous yoga schools, ashrams and meditation centers, making it an</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-rishikesh-yoga-capital-of-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten best places to Travel Solo in North India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-places-to-travel-solo-in-north-india.html</link>
			<description>Here are ten of the best places to travel solo in North India, along with suggestions on when to visit and why they are ideal for solo travelers:   Leh-Ladakh, Jammu and Kashmir   When: May to September (summer months) Why: During this time, the weather is favorable and most roads and passes are open, allowing solo travelers to explore the stunning landscapes, serene monasteries and adventurous ac</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 Apr 2024 10:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-places-to-travel-solo-in-north-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in Karnataka to travel solo in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-karnataka-to-travel-solo-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo in Karnataka during hot summers can be a delightful experience, especially when you explore destinations with cooler climates or indoor attractions. Karnataka offers a diverse range of destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers.  Here are some of the best places to visit in Karnataka during the hot summer months:   Coorg (Kodagu):   Known as the &amp;quot;Scotland of</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Apr 2024 18:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-karnataka-to-travel-solo-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tiruttani Solo Travel Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruttani-solo-travel-plan.html</link>
			<description>Tiruttani is a significant pilgrimage destination in Tamil Nadu, known for its ancient temple dedicated to Lord Murugan. As a solo traveler, you&amp;#39;ll have the opportunity to immerse yourself in the spiritual ambiance of the temple town, explore its cultural heritage and witness the rituals and traditions firsthand.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested solo travel plan:  Arrival in Tiruttani   Depart from Ban</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 31 Mar 2024 07:39:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-tiruttani-solo-travel-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Jog Falls Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-jog-falls-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Jog Falls can be a refreshing experience, especially for nature lovers. Jog Falls, located in the Shimoga district of Karnataka, is one of the highest plunge waterfalls in India.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Jog Falls   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of the day. The distance between Bangalore and Jog Falls</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 26 Mar 2024 14:09:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-jog-falls-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Best places in South India to travel in Hot Summer?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</link>
			<description>South India offers several destinations that are perfect for traveling during hot summers due to their cooler climates, hill stations and coastal areas.  Here are some of the best places to visit in South India during the hot summer months, along with reasons, ways to travel and the best time to visit:    Ooty, Tamil Nadu:   Why: Ooty, also known as the &amp;quot;Queen of Hill Stations,&amp;quot; offers c</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 19 Mar 2024 08:58:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/best-places-in-south-india-to-travel-in-hot-summer.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kollur Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kollur-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kollur can be a serene and spiritually enriching experience, as Kollur is home to the famous Mookambika Temple.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Kollur   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Kollur is approximately 400 kilometers and the drive takes around 8-9 hours. R</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 19:42:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kollur-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Anamudi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-anamudi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Anamudi, standing as the highest peak in the Western Ghats and South India, is a wonderful destination for nature lovers and trekkers. It&amp;#39;s situated in the Eravikulam National Park near Munnar, Kerala.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip from Bangalore to Anamudi:  Bangalore to Munnar   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between </description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 04 Mar 2024 12:22:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-anamudi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Chitradurga Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chitradurga-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Chitradurga can be a rewarding experience, with Chitradurga being known for its historical fort and scenic landscapes.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Chitradurga   Start your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Bangalore and Chitradurga is approximately 200 kilometers and it takes around 4-</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 13 Jan 2024 11:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-chitradurga-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Madurai Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-madurai-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Madurai can be a fascinating journey, rich in history, culture and spirituality. Madurai, often referred to as the Athens of the East, is famous for its Meenakshi Amman Temple and vibrant street life.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Madurai   Begin your journey early in the morning to make the most of your day. The distance between Ba</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 14 Dec 2023 17:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-madurai-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten hill stations to travel solo in south of India</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-of-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo to hill stations in South India can be a delightful experience, offering scenic beauty, tranquility and a chance for self-reflection.  Here are ten of the best hill stations in South India for solo travel:   Ooty, Tamil Nadu: Known as the &amp;quot;Queen of Hill Stations,&amp;quot; Ooty is famous for its lush tea gardens, serene lakes and pleasant weather. The Nilgiri Mountain Railway adds </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2023 09:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-hill-stations-to-travel-solo-in-south-of-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Nagarahole Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-nagarahole-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Nagarahole promises an exciting adventure amidst the wildlife and natural beauty of the national park. Nagarahole, also known as Rajiv Gandhi National Park, is renowned for its diverse flora and fauna.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your solo trip:  Bangalore to Nagarahole   Begin your journey early in the morning to allow ample time for exploration. The distance</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 25 Nov 2023 09:40:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-nagarahole-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Kudremukh Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kudremukh-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Kudremukh promises an adventurous and nature-filled experience. Kudremukh is known for its scenic beauty, trekking trails and lush green landscapes.  The name&amp;nbsp;Kuduremukha&amp;nbsp;literally means &amp;quot;horse-faced&amp;quot; in&amp;nbsp;Kannada&amp;nbsp;and refers to a particular picturesque view of a side of the mountain that resembles a horse&amp;#39;s face. It was also referred to a</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2023 07:50:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-kudremukh-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Ten best places to Travel Solo in South India?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-places-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</link>
			<description>Traveling solo in South India can be a remarkable experience, offering a diverse range of landscapes, cultures and experiences.  Here are ten of the best places to explore, along with reasons why they are great for solo travelers and the best times to visit:   Pondicherry, Tamil Nadu:  Why: Pondicherry offers a unique blend of French and Indian cultures, serene beaches and a peaceful ambiance. It&amp;</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 09:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ten-best-places-to-travel-solo-in-south-india.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Srikalahasti Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srikalahasti-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Srikalahasti can be a spiritually enriching experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to visit the famous Srikalahasti Temple and explore the cultural heritage of this ancient town in Andhra Pradesh.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Chittoor -&amp;gt; Tirupati -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Srikalahasti -&amp;gt; Tirupati -&amp;gt; Chittoor -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2023 19:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-srikalahasti-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Horanadu Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-horanadu-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Horanadu can be a serene and spiritual experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to visit the famous Horanadu Annapoorneshwari Temple and explore the natural beauty of the Western Ghats in Karnataka.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Belur -&amp;gt;&amp;nbsp;Mudigere -&amp;gt; Kalasa -&amp;gt; Horanadu -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalo</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 09:55:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-horanadu-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Agumbe Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-agumbe-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Agumbe can be a thrilling adventure, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the rainforests, waterfalls and scenic beauty of the Western Ghats in Karnataka. Agumbe is also known as the &amp;quot;Cherrapunji of South India&amp;quot; due to its high rainfall and lush greenery.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Belur -&amp;gt; Sringeri -&amp;gt; A</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 12 Sep 2023 09:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-agumbe-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Mangalore Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mangalore-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Mangalore can be an exciting journey, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the pristine beaches, ancient temples and vibrant culture of this coastal city in Karnataka.  Here&amp;#39;s a suggested itinerary for your trip:  Route  Bangalore -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Belur -&amp;gt; Charmady Ghat -&amp;gt; Mangaluru -&amp;gt; Sakleshpura -&amp;gt; Hassan -&amp;gt; Bangalore  Day 1: Bangalore to Mangalore   Star</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-mangalore-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Udupi Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-udupi-solo-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Solo trip from Bangalore to Udupi can be a delightful experience, as you&amp;#39;ll get to explore the pristine beaches, ancient temples and delicious cuisine of this coastal town in Karnataka.  Udupi is one of the top tourist attractions in Karnataka and has various educational institutions. It is notable for the&amp;nbsp;Krishna Temple&amp;nbsp;and is also known as the temple city.[3]&amp;nbsp;It also lends its</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 20:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-udupi-solo-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>