<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Travel - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Travel.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Bangalore to Makalidurga - Trekking</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Makalidurga-Trekking.html</link>
			<description>One-day trek from Bangalore to Makalidurga to Bangalore. If you are a couple riding on a Bike or you are a Family driving in a Car, then this trek plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. Makalidurga is a hill fort situated 60 km north of Bangalore. The fort at the summit has an old temple of Shiva with Nandi and in legend, Markandeya Rishi performed penan</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Makalidurga-Trekking.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Gandikota (2 Days + 1 Nights, Trip Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Gandikota-two-Days-one-Night-Trip-Plan.html</link>
			<description>Two Days Trip from Bangalore to Gandikota to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on a Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly.
                            A couple of the best places you can visit on the way or around are Lakshmi Narasimha Swamy temple in Kadiri &amp; Belum Caves in Kolimigundla.
  </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 08 Aug 2021 13:20:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Gandikota-two-Days-one-Night-Trip-Plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Precautions while travelling during Coronavirus times</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Precautions-while-travelling-during-Coronavirus-times.html</link>
			<description>It is not completely safe to travel during the Coronavirus times. Although the mortality rate of the people affected with COVID appears to be quite low, there is always a chance with the data which we get in our country. I see one should avoid travelling as much as possible so that we reduce the chances of spreading the virus.
                                Following are some of the things to be </description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 14:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Precautions-while-travelling-during-Coronavirus-times.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Tirumala (2 Days + 1 Night)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Tirumala-two-days-trip.html</link>
			<description>Two days Trip from Bangalore to Tirumala to Bangalore, If you are a couple riding on bike or you are a family driving in car, then this two days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. You can book the Dharshna Tickets &amp; Stay via Online Booking or you can get it once you reach their based on the Crowd on Tirumala.
                                Tirumala </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 24 Apr 2021 08:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Tirumala-two-days-trip.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Rameswaram (3 Days + 2 Nights, Trip Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</link>
			<description>Three days Trip from Bangalore to Rameswaram to Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Rameshwaram is a small Hindu pilgrimage town a</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 10 Feb 2021 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Rameswaram--days--nights-trip-plan.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore <=> Ooty (3 Days + 2 Nights, Trip Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Three-Days-Trip-from-Bangalore-to-Ooty.html</link>
			<description>Three days Trip from Bangalore  Ooty  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are a Family driving in Car, then this three days plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route. Ooty known as the Queen of the hill stations in South In</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 02 Dec 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Three-Days-Trip-from-Bangalore-to-Ooty.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore -> Murdeshwar -> Gokarna -> Goa -> Dandeli -> Bangalore</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-Murdeshwar-Gokarna-Goa-Dandeli.html</link>
			<description>Ten days Ride from Bangalore  Murdeshwar  Gokarna  Goa  Dandeli  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for ten days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.
       </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 23 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-Murdeshwar-Gokarna-Goa-Dandeli.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore <=> Ghati Subramanya (Morning Ride Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Short-trip-from-Bangalore-to-Ghati.html</link>
			<description>Ghati Subramanya is an ancient Hindu temple, 50 kms away from Bangalore towards Doddaballapur situated on the outskirts of Bangalore. Ghati Subramanya has a recorded history of more than 600 years. Ghati Subramanya Temple was first developed by the Ghorpade rulers of Sandur who ruled parts of Bellary.
                                The uniqueness of this temple is the prime deity "Lord Karthikeya</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Short-trip-from-Bangalore-to-Ghati.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore <=> Mysore (2 Days + 1 Night, Ride Plan)</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Two-days-trip-from-Bangalore-to-Mysore.html</link>
			<description>Two days Ride from Bangalore  Mysore  Bangalore, If you are a Couple riding on Bike or You are riding with a Friend in two different Bikes, then this plan for two days works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly, if at all you need to spend some more time in some place in the list, you can skip the next place in the planned route.
                                Ro</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 04 Jun 2020 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Two-days-trip-from-Bangalore-to-Mysore.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>