<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Trekking - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Trekking.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Solo Travel to Gokarna for Three Nights and Four Days</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</link>
			<description>You are planning to visit Gokarna solo then here is the article which will help you to plan your trip. And this plan in this article is for three days and four nights and for a person who wants to travel solo.  If you are traveling from Bangalore, overnight bus or a train will be the best option for travel to Gokarna. And if you wish to travel via flight, the nearest airport for people will be eit</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 21 Jul 2022 19:15:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, What to pack?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of what you might need to pack in your backpack. Packing proper equipment, clothing &amp;amp; quick energy foods will help you to do your trek bit smoothly.  One more important thing, is this plan would fit for the people who are willing to trek solo (without a porter), so what you a</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 11:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to charge a Mobile phone with Solar power?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>In this article, we are going to see what all options we have to charge a mobile phone with Solar power.  If you are going on treks which are primarily overnight or a few days of trek in some isolated place. In such cases obviously we won&amp;rsquo;t get any electrical power, In such cases for people Solar energy would be an alternative option to keep your device charged.  And let&amp;rsquo;s see what all</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Jul 2022 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
			<description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Makalidurga - Trekking</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Makalidurga-Trekking.html</link>
			<description>One-day trek from Bangalore to Makalidurga to Bangalore. If you are a couple riding on a Bike or you are a Family driving in a Car, then this trek plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. Makalidurga is a hill fort situated 60 km north of Bangalore. The fort at the summit has an old temple of Shiva with Nandi and in legend, Markandeya Rishi performed penan</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 30 Oct 2021 15:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/Bangalore-to-Makalidurga-Trekking.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>