<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Trekking - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/trekking.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>Everest Base Camp Trek - What should you know before you start?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-what-should-you-know-before-you-start.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of what to know before you proceed further.  The Everest Base Camp Trek is a challenging and rewarding adventure that takes you to the base of the highest mountain in the world.  Here are some things you should know before you start:   Physical Fitness: The Everest Base Camp Trek</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-what-should-you-know-before-you-start.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Everest Base Camp Trek, Start Trekking from Salleri and back to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of where you can start your trek. I have read through many articles &amp;amp; videos and found the best route for trekking.  Generally people all over the world will reach Kathmandu and then take a flight to Lukla and start the trek to Everest base camp from Lukla.  In case you are n</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/everest-base-camp-trek-start-trekking-from-salleri-and-back-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, Bangalore to Kathmandu then to Salleri</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to trek Solo to Everest Base Camp by yourself from Bangalore, then this article will help you to get a picture of how to reach Salleri from Bangalore, where Salleri will be the starting point of Trek to Everest Base Camp.  There are many possible routes to reach Kathmandu from Bangalore.   Flight  There are direct flights from Bangalore to Kathmandu and vice versa. You also hav</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-bangalore-to-kathmandu-then-to-salleri.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Gokarna Solo Trip Plan</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</link>
			<description>You are planning to visit Gokarna solo then here is the article which will help you to plan your trip. And this plan in this article is for three days and four nights and for a person who wants to travel solo.  If you are traveling from Bangalore, overnight bus or a train will be the best option for travel to Gokarna. And if you wish to travel via flight, the nearest airport for people will be eit</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Nov 2023 09:30:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-gokarna-for-three-nights-and-four-days.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Everest Base Camp Trek, What to pack?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</link>
			<description>If you are planning to prepare to trek Everest Base Camp by yourself, then this article would help you to get a picture of what you might need to pack in your backpack. Packing proper equipment, clothing &amp;amp; quick energy foods will help you to do your trek bit smoothly.  One more important thing, is this plan would fit for the people who are willing to trek solo (without a porter), so what you a</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-everest-base-camp-trek-what-to-pack.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to charge a Mobile phone with Solar power?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</link>
			<description>As the world shifts toward renewable energy, solar power is becoming an increasingly practical and eco-friendly way to charge everyday devices&amp;mdash;especially mobile phones. Whether you&amp;#39;re off the grid, on a camping trip, or simply looking to reduce your environmental impact, solar charging offers a convenient solution.  This article will walk you through how to charge your phone using solar </description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 19:29:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-charge-a-mobile-phone-with-solar-power.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Dal Bhat Recipe - Nepali Style</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</link>
			<description>Dal Bhat or Nepali Dal Bhat, is a dish made of lentils and rice, actually It is considered that this is the national dish of Nepal. Generally the rice is either boiled or steamed and It is served in the middle of the dish and surrounded by the dal or lentils and sometimes with some other curries or chutney or with a pickle.  For people, Dal Bhat is easy to cook and it can be cooked with other flav</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 27 Jul 2025 11:43:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Reddamma D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/dal-bhat-recipe--nepali-style.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Bangalore to Makalidurga - Trekking</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</link>
			<description>One-day trek from Bangalore to Makalidurga to Bangalore. If you are a couple riding on a Bike or you are a Family driving in a Car, then this trek plan works very well. Below is the route mentioned where you can plan accordingly. Makalidurga is a hill fort situated 60 km north of Bangalore. The fort at the summit has an old temple of Shiva with Nandi and in legend, Markandeya Rishi performed penan</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/bangalore-to-makalidurga-trekking.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>