<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Unsolved-Mysteries - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unsolved-mysteries.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>The Mysterious Death of Actress Divya Bharti</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-mysterious-death-of-actress-divya-bharti.html</link>
			<description>Divya Bharti was one of Bollywood&amp;rsquo;s most promising actresses in the early 1990s, known for her beauty, talent, and meteoric rise to fame. However, her life was tragically cut short at the young age of 19 under mysterious circumstances. On April 5, 1993, she reportedly fell from the balcony of her fifth-floor apartment in Mumbai and succumbed to her injuries. Despite an official verdict of ac</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 18:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-mysterious-death-of-actress-divya-bharti.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Time Travel Possibilities in Quantum Physics</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/time-travel-possibilities-in-quantum-physics.html</link>
			<description>Time travel has long been a fascination in science fiction, but could it actually be possible? While classical physics suggests that time flows in a straight line from past to future, quantum physics introduces concepts that challenge our understanding of time. Some physicists believe that time travel might not only be possible but may already be happening at a microscopic level. In this article, </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/time-travel-possibilities-in-quantum-physics.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Malaysia Airlines Flight MH370 – Still No Answers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/malaysia-airlines-flight-mh-still-no-answers.html</link>
			<description>Malaysia Airlines Flight MH370 remains one of the greatest aviation mysteries in modern history. Despite extensive searches, countless theories, and global investigations, the fate of the 239 passengers and crew on board the Boeing 777 remains unknown. How could a modern aircraft disappear without a trace, and why has it remained unsolved for nearly a decade?  The Disappearance  On March 8, 2014, </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 10:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/malaysia-airlines-flight-mh-still-no-answers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vimanas in Ancient India – Were They Real Flying Machines?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vimanas-in-ancient-india-were-they-real-flying-machines.html</link>
			<description>The idea of Vimanas, ancient flying machines mentioned in Indian scriptures, has fascinated historians, scientists, and enthusiasts alike. Some believe these texts describe advanced aerial technology far ahead of their time, while others argue that Vimanas are purely mythological. But could ancient India have actually possessed flying technology, or are these references symbolic? Let&amp;rsquo;s explo</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 10:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vimanas-in-ancient-india-were-they-real-flying-machines.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>