<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Unsolved Mysteries - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/unsolved-mysteries.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>UFO Sighting Over Kanchenjunga – Mystery Above the Himalayas</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ufo-sighting-over-kanchenjunga-mystery-above-the-himalayas.html</link>
			<description>The towering Kanchenjunga, the world&amp;rsquo;s third-highest mountain, has long been surrounded by myths, spirituality, and intrigue. Rising over 8,500 meters across the borders of India and Nepal, it&amp;rsquo;s revered as a sacred peak by the people of Sikkim. But beyond its breathtaking beauty and religious significance, Kanchenjunga has also become the site of one of India&amp;rsquo;s most puzzling UFO </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 16:57:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/ufo-sighting-over-kanchenjunga-mystery-above-the-himalayas.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Magnetic Hill Illusion of Ladakh</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-magnetic-hill-illusion-of-ladakh.html</link>
			<description>High on the Leh&amp;ndash;Kargil&amp;ndash;Baltal road in Ladakh, at an altitude of about 14,000 feet, lies one of India&amp;rsquo;s most fascinating geographical puzzles &amp;mdash; Magnetic Hill. Known for its mysterious &amp;ldquo;gravity-defying&amp;rdquo; behavior, this stretch of road has captivated travelers, scientists, and photographers alike. Vehicles left out of gear appear to move uphill on their own, seeming</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 06 Oct 2025 17:06:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-magnetic-hill-illusion-of-ladakh.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Defiance of Gravity at Lepakshi Temple, Andhra Pradesh</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/defiance-of-gravity-at-lepakshi-temple-andhra-pradesh.html</link>
			<description>Nestled in the small town of Lepakshi in Andhra Pradesh lies one of India&amp;rsquo;s most intriguing architectural enigmas&amp;mdash;the Veerabhadra Temple, a masterpiece of the Vijayanagara period. Built in the 16th century by the brothers Viranna and Virupanna, this temple is renowned not only for its exquisite carvings and mural paintings but also for its mystifying hanging pillar&amp;mdash;a stone column</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 01 Sep 2025 10:13:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/defiance-of-gravity-at-lepakshi-temple-andhra-pradesh.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Enigma of the Unfinished Kailasa Temple, Ellora</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-enigma-of-the-unfinished-kailasa-temple-ellora.html</link>
			<description>The Kailasa Temple at Ellora, carved from a single massive rock in Maharashtra, India, stands as one of the greatest architectural and engineering marvels of the ancient world. Dedicated to Lord Shiva, the temple forms part of the Ellora Caves, a UNESCO World Heritage Site. Unlike most temples that were built by adding material, this one was created through monolithic excavation&amp;mdash;workers remo</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 20 Aug 2025 11:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-enigma-of-the-unfinished-kailasa-temple-ellora.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Piri Reis Map – A 16th-Century Map Showing Antarctica Without Ice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-piri-reis-map-a-th-century-map-showing-antarctica-without-ice.html</link>
			<description>The Piri Reis Map, created in 1513 by Ottoman admiral and cartographer Piri Reis, has fascinated historians, scientists, and conspiracy theorists for decades. What makes this map so mysterious is its alleged depiction of Antarctica&amp;rsquo;s coastline &amp;ndash; without ice, centuries before the continent was officially discovered and explored.  Drawn on a piece of gazelle skin parchment, the map shows</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-piri-reis-map-a-th-century-map-showing-antarctica-without-ice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>The Mysterious Death of Actress Divya Bharti</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-mysterious-death-of-actress-divya-bharti.html</link>
			<description>Divya Bharti was one of Bollywood&amp;rsquo;s most promising actresses in the early 1990s, known for her beauty, talent, and meteoric rise to fame. However, her life was tragically cut short at the young age of 19 under mysterious circumstances. On April 5, 1993, she reportedly fell from the balcony of her fifth-floor apartment in Mumbai and succumbed to her injuries. Despite an official verdict of ac</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 21 Mar 2025 18:48:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-mysterious-death-of-actress-divya-bharti.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Time Travel Possibilities in Quantum Physics</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/time-travel-possibilities-in-quantum-physics.html</link>
			<description>Time travel has long been a fascination in science fiction, but could it actually be possible? While classical physics suggests that time flows in a straight line from past to future, quantum physics introduces concepts that challenge our understanding of time. Some physicists believe that time travel might not only be possible but may already be happening at a microscopic level. In this article, </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 18 Mar 2025 12:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/time-travel-possibilities-in-quantum-physics.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Malaysia Airlines Flight MH370 – Still No Answers</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/malaysia-airlines-flight-mh-still-no-answers.html</link>
			<description>Malaysia Airlines Flight MH370 remains one of the greatest aviation mysteries in modern history. Despite extensive searches, countless theories, and global investigations, the fate of the 239 passengers and crew on board the Boeing 777 remains unknown. How could a modern aircraft disappear without a trace, and why has it remained unsolved for nearly a decade?  The Disappearance  On March 8, 2014, </description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 10:05:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/malaysia-airlines-flight-mh-still-no-answers.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Vimanas in Ancient India – Were They Real Flying Machines?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vimanas-in-ancient-india-were-they-real-flying-machines.html</link>
			<description>The idea of Vimanas, ancient flying machines mentioned in Indian scriptures, has fascinated historians, scientists, and enthusiasts alike. Some believe these texts describe advanced aerial technology far ahead of their time, while others argue that Vimanas are purely mythological. But could ancient India have actually possessed flying technology, or are these references symbolic? Let&amp;rsquo;s explo</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 15 Mar 2025 10:08:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vimanas-in-ancient-india-were-they-real-flying-machines.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>