<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>Vegetable - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/vegetable.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>What percentage of Indians are vegetarian?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</link>
			<description>Approximately 30-40% of the population in India is estimated to follow a vegetarian diet. However, this percentage can vary depending on the region, cultural practices and religious beliefs.  Why Indians Follow Vegetarianism:   Religious Beliefs:   Hinduism: Many Hindus follow a vegetarian diet as part of their religious beliefs, which promote compassion and non-violence (ahimsa). They believe in </description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 02 Apr 2024 20:28:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-percentage-of-indians-are-vegetarian.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What are recommended servings of fruits and vegetables?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-recommended-servings-of-fruits-and-vegetables.html</link>
			<description>The recommended servings of fruits and vegetables can vary slightly based on factors such as age, sex and activity level. However, general guidelines provide a useful framework for individuals to ensure they&amp;#39;re incorporating enough fruits and vegetables into their diet.  According to dietary guidelines, a common recommendation for adults is to aim for:   Fruits:   Quantity: 1.5 to 2 cups per d</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 15 Mar 2024 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-are-recommended-servings-of-fruits-and-vegetables.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>How to make a compost without worm/kitchen composting/organic composting</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</link>
			<description>Composting is a great way to reduce waste and create nutrient-rich soil for your garden. While worm composting and kitchen composting are popular methods, there are other ways to make compost without using worms or organic kitchen waste. Here are some options:   Leaf Composting: Fallen leaves are an excellent source of carbon and can be used to create a nutrient-rich compost. Simply pile up the le</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 05 Apr 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/how-to-make-a-compost-without-worm-or-kitchen-composting-or-organic-composting.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Eight vegetables that can be grown at Home</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see eight vegetables that you can grow at your home easily. Chili pepper, Tomato, Garlic, Peas, Raddish, Cabbage, Cauliflower and Carrot are the few vegetables that you can grow at home with less effort.  1. Chili pepper  Chili pepper can be easily grown from seeds, so we need to buy good seeds for better results. Sprinkle seeds over the soil surface, then cover with a</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Dec 2023 11:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/eight-vegetables-that-can-be-grown-at-home.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Onions to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Onions are easy to grow, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. They need less attention during the growth when compared to other plants.  Onions will be having flavonoids, which have both an antioxidant and anti-inflammatory effect. By eating them regularly in sufficient quantities, these components will help people to protect themselves from chronic conditions such as ca</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2025 14:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-onions-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Tomatoes to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>In this article we are gonna see how they can grow tomatoes at their home and with the help of just other tomatoes at home. We have a few other articles which help to grow vegetables at home, you can read them from here.  Generally tomatoes are used in the kitchen for almost all the curries in South Indian dishes.  Tomatoes are rich in Vitamin B9, Vitamin C and Potassium and these Antioxidants pro</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-tomatoes-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Pudina to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Pudina is easy to grow and hard to kill, which makes it one of the best plants for a beginning gardener. It&amp;#39;s especially known for its soothing effect on the stomach.  Pudina is a fast growing plant, it&amp;#39;s good to keep it in a pot or a container with some boundary, so that it doesn&amp;rsquo;t take up all your garden or yard.  If people buy Pudina from a market or get Punida from a neighbor&amp;#39</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-pudina-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing enough Broccoli to Feed a Family by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</link>
			<description>Broccoli is worth growing for its nutritional content value. This is rich in Vitamins and Minerals and is a good source of Vitamin A, Potassium, Folic acid, Iron and Fiber.  Broccoli is a cool seasonal crop, so it should be started in early winters. September and October are the best months for seed germination.  Germination Process?   You can start seeds in almost any type of container as long as</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-broccoli-to-feed-a-family-by-yourself.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Growing Enough Food to Feed a Family Year-Round by Yourself</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-food-to-feed-a-family.html</link>
			<description>It&amp;#39;s a great thought of growing enough food to feed your family year round by yourself. Certain things are really important for such a though, like how much food is needed for your family, which crops to plant, how to get the most from your plot and how to preserve your extra harvest.  How much food is needed?   Let&amp;#39;s say a 200 square feet plot will harvest the feeds for a single person al</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 15 Aug 2024 12:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/growing-enough-food-to-feed-a-family.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>