<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" version="2.0" xml:base="https://peoplesblog.co.in">
<channel>
	<title>World - Peoples BLOG</title>
    <link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world.html</link>
    <description/>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
			<title>The Piri Reis Map – A 16th-Century Map Showing Antarctica Without Ice</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-piri-reis-map-a-th-century-map-showing-antarctica-without-ice.html</link>
			<description>The Piri Reis Map, created in 1513 by Ottoman admiral and cartographer Piri Reis, has fascinated historians, scientists, and conspiracy theorists for decades. What makes this map so mysterious is its alleged depiction of Antarctica&amp;rsquo;s coastline &amp;ndash; without ice, centuries before the continent was officially discovered and explored.  Drawn on a piece of gazelle skin parchment, the map shows</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 21 May 2025 16:44:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/the-piri-reis-map-a-th-century-map-showing-antarctica-without-ice.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Water for Pakistan: Lifeline, Dependency, and the Shifting Control</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/water-for-pakistan-lifeline-dependency-and-the-shifting-control.html</link>
			<description>Water is not just a natural resource for Pakistan&amp;mdash;it is its lifeline. With over 90% of its water supply coming from a single river system, Pakistan is critically dependent on external sources. Agriculture, power generation, and daily life across the country rely on uninterrupted water flow, primarily from rivers originating in Indian-administered territory. In recent developments, however, t</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 11 May 2025 10:49:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/water-for-pakistan-lifeline-dependency-and-the-shifting-control.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Solo Travel to Rishikesh - Yoga Capital of the World</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-rishikesh-yoga-capital-of-the-world.html</link>
			<description>Solo travel to Rishikesh, known as the &amp;quot;Yoga Capital of the World,&amp;quot; can be a transformative journey offering opportunities for self-discovery, spiritual growth and adventure.  Here&amp;#39;s why, how and when to plan a solo trip to Rishikesh:  Why Solo Travel to Rishikesh:   Yoga and Meditation: Rishikesh is renowned for its numerous yoga schools, ashrams and meditation centers, making it an</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 20 Apr 2024 14:35:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/solo-travel-to-rishikesh-yoga-capital-of-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>What is the most expensive spice in the world when listed by weight?</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-the-most-expensive-spice-in-the-world-when-listed-by-weight.html</link>
			<description>The most expensive spice in the world, when listed by weight, is saffron. Saffron is derived from the stigma (the female reproductive part) of the Crocus sativus flower. It is renowned for its distinct flavor, aroma and vibrant color, which adds depth and complexity to dishes.  Saffron is used in various cuisines worldwide, particularly in dishes such as paella, risotto and certain desserts.  Seve</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Mar 2024 09:10:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/what-is-the-most-expensive-spice-in-the-world-when-listed-by-weight.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Monkeypox Outbreak around the World in 2022</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</link>
			<description>The outbreak of monkeypox, which is a viral disease, was confirmed in May 2022, once few cases were found in the United Kingdom. The first case was detected on 6th May 2022 and confirmed this case had travel links to Nigeria (where the disease is endemic).  From 18th May 2022 onwards, there was an increase in cases in Europe, North and South America, Asia, Africa and Australia.  As of 23rd July 20</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Jyothi Karthik D</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/monkeypox-outbreak-around-the-world.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>World Wildlife Day</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-wildlife-day.html</link>
			<description>On 20 December 2013, United Nations General Assembly (UNGA), in its resolution UN 68/205, decided to proclaim 3 March, the international day of the adoption of the Convention on International Trade in Endangered Species of Wild Fauna and Flora (CITES) on the planet raise awareness and benefits fauna and flora in 1973, as World Wildlife Day, which was proposed by Thailand, to celebrate and raise aw</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/world-wildlife-day.html</guid>
    </item><item>
			<title>Reduce the Risk of Becoming a Sexual Assault Victim!</title>
			<link>https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</link>
			<description>To Reduce the risk for you to becoming a sexual victim, you have to take some preventative measures, which will help you to avoid a risky situations from escalating. Anyone can be the target of sexual assault, regardless of age, gender, race, ethnicity, sexual orientation, sexual history, or social class. There is no stereotypical victim or rapist.                                What's bad? - Near</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 01 Dec 2023 08:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
			<dc:creator>Karthik Kumar D K</dc:creator>
<guid isPermaLink="true">https://peoplesblog.co.in/articles/reduce-the-risk-of-becoming-a-sexual-assault-victim.html</guid>
    </item>
</channel>
</rss>